Chapter 1132: Plenary Meeting and Provocation

"There are a lot of souls of powerful individuals of the exploration era war stored in the Underworld dimension, not just the Primordial Ones, but also Supers of various races, mostly Calamity Grades. They're all antiques…"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled brightly.

These people were not just combatants. They were also the people who witnessed the various times of the exploration era and reliable sources of first-hand information. They possessed a lot of ancient secrets.

"Aurora can only make bodies for these Hero Spirits and turn them into combatants when she's Beyond Grade A. Speaking of which, the Underworld dimension is kind of similar to the Indestructible Mechanic Empire… Although the Hero Spirits can't have bodies now, it shouldn't be a problem just communicating with them. I wonder how much Hila has repaired the Underworld."

Han Xiao still remembered that he had an Underworld dimension mission. Once the Underworld was fully recovered, he would receive a [Mark of The Underworld].

"I shall find a moment to ask Hila if what I'm thinking is right…"

Hila was now in the secondary dimensions, so it was not easy to contact her. However, she should return in the next Beyond Grade A plenary meeting. Han Xiao planned to ask her then.

It just so happened that the next plenary meeting of the development union was not far away, so he did not have to go to the secondary dimensions to find her.

He suspected that Soul Emperor faked his death and Oathkeeper was Soul Emperor, but he had yet to decide if he was going to test Oathkeeper the next time they met.

Beep beep!

This time, Harrison sent him a message saying Rody had settled in.

"Okay."

Han Xiao was very content.

My intuition was right. I did indeed get surprised when I returned to Planet Aquamarine this time. I discovered the secret of Destiny's Child, acquired a semi-transformed sub-body of it, and obtained some key information from Aesop.

However, Aesop's prophecy made him feel pressure too. Storms were secretly brewing.

The stronger he got, the more secrets he came to know, and the more he could sense the hidden chaos and instability under the peace and prosperity of the explored universe.

Han Xiao pondered.

"I've got to think of a way to ask about the Crimson Dynasty's study of the World Tree Civilization wormhole coordinates…"

…

After he spent a few days on Floating Dragon as a guest and visited Bennett, Han Xiao and his fleet departed again and headed to the Flickering World.

At the dock, Ames stood. The stream from the thruster of the spaceship made her black dress sway like a cluster of black fog. She had brought along the Floating Dragon officers and watched the Black Star fleet leave, disappearing from sight.

"He left again."

Ames exhaled slightly and looked down on the data storage device in her hands. This was a gift Han Xiao had given to her before he left. Inside was an Esper Ultimate Knowledge.

She turned around and saw Jenny's conflicted expression. She was squeezing tightly on a syringe in her hands. That was a gift from Han Xiao too.

"What's wrong? What did he give you?" Ames was curious.

"…Nothing!"

Jenny forced out a ferocious smile and hid the magical hair growth potion behind her back.

Aesop stroked his beard, smiled, and said, "Black Star gave me a gift too. I'm starting to like him more and more."

Beside him, eight fist-sized sphere-shaped weapons swiftly flew around.

This was a product personally built by Han Xiao. He named it 'Explorer—Multifunctional Life Guarding Formation'. It had a full set of functions, including combat, defense, enhancement, life-sustain, stealth, healing, hyperdrive, radiation block, and many more. It was perfect for solo explorers.

With this set of devices, it was equivalent to carrying around a guard team, logistics team, and a galactic carrier. Even an ordinary person would be able to survive for a very long time in Grade B dangerous environments. They would even last quite a while against Calamity Grades with a chance of retreating unharmed. It was expensive to build and very powerful. Just one set was enough to wipe out ordinary surface civilizations, and Han Xiao had given a total of ten sets to Aesop.

Ames blinked and suddenly said, "I heard that you privately asked Black Star to protect me."

Stunned, Aesop grabbed his beard and said, "Who told you?"

"Who else?" Ames' brows raised.

"Tsk, this Black Star, doesn't even know to keep it a secret for me…" Aesop had a slight headache. He nodded with resignation and said, "That did happen, yes. I foresaw that a drastic change is going to happen. My capability is limited. Only Black Star has the ability to…"

Before he finished, Ames interrupted him and said with a slightly heavy tone, "I'm a Beyond Grade A. I can protect myself. Next time, discuss it with me first before thinking for me. I don't like others making decisions on my behalf."

"Alright, alright, I've overstepped." Aesop raised two hands and expressed that he did not want to argue.

Seeing this, Ames nodded. She then smiled faintly and softly said, "… But still, thanks, I appreciate it."

She knew that Han Xiao had told her about it because he did not want Aesop's kind intentions to not get recognized.

Furthermore, Han Xiao was the only one who could mention this. Aesop was never going to tell Ames and ask to be appreciated; he was not that kind of person.

Aesop figured out Han Xiao's intentions too, and his tiny bit of unhappiness disappeared. He was a little touched and appreciative. His impression of Han Xiao was even better.

…

The fleet travelled for ten days and finally entered the Flickering World through the military stargates. On this day, the Beyond Grade A Association hosted another plenary meeting.

Due to the fact that the Mechanics had been dealing with the Intelligent Plague for quite some time, they had missed quite a number of meetings. This was the first meeting for Han Xiao and the others in a while.

In the development union's headquarters on Planet Finn, Han Xiao's remote projection landed outside the conference room in the army commander's gold-edged black cape, looking respectable.

There was still some time till the official start of the meeting, so not everyone had arrived yet. People gathered in small groups outside the conference room and chatted casually.

One of the purposes of the development union was to build a platform that was convenient for Beyond Grade As to communicate with each other. Other than official meetings, their private communications were just as important.

As soon as he appeared, the space outside the venue instantly turned quiet. Everyone looked over with various expressions on their faces. The atmosphere was a little odd.

This time, Milizaus and several dynasty allies approached.

"Yo, Black Star, you've finally returned," Milizaus said loudly.

Han Xiao turned and looked over with a smile. He then greeted Beyoni, Silver Shadow, and his other friends one after another.

After a round of greetings, Milizaus praised, "What you did in the Ancient Star Desert really made me see you in a new light. Sadly, I'm not a Mechanic and could not witness it with my own eyes."

"That's right. To think that we could not participate in such a historic moment, what a shame." Viru looked regretful.

"If I was there, you wouldn't have fought alone. I'd definitely have fought Manison with you," Beyoni said.

Lotus Swordsman was merciless. She said coldly, "Nonsense, if you were there, you'd be the first one to die. You're a burden just like Kohler."

Kohler frowned. Why bring me into it? I didn't say anything!

"Not a big deal. It's not worth mentioning, hehehe…" Hearing compliments from everyone, Han Xiao waved humbly.

One consequence of him destroying the virus core was that the allies saw that his position had increased again, and he was more trusted by the three Universal Civilizations, so they all came to give their compliments.

This time, Milizaus looked left and right, lowered his voice, and said, "Everyone thinks you're now totally opposed to Manison. The president and the vice president having different philosophies will definitely lead to arguments. The atmosphere in the association now is very sensitive."

"No wonder everyone was looking at me strangely earlier." Han Xiao smiled and was not surprised.

"Today is the first time you and Manison will attend the meeting together after the two of you confronted each other, so most people are now waiting to see what will happen."

Han Xiao shook his head and said, "Don't worry, the development union's purpose to the outside world is to solve conflicts between Beyond Grade As, so Manison will definitely not publicly disobey the rules. Otherwise, the foundation of the association will be damaged, and that's unacceptable for him. Therefore, he has to set an example. The most he'll do is cause trouble for me verbally. There's no way he'll use the association's powers to cause problems for me. As for me, I have even less of a need to provoke him…"

After all, I grabbed even Mechanic Emperor's trump card. I'm not the one who lost anything.

Han Xiao giggled in his mind but did not say the second half of the last sentence.

Milizaus said slowly, "Yes, that's for the best. Don't provoke him. Actually, after Manison expressed his goal, there aren't that many people supporting him in the association anymore.

"What he did this time was too risky. Many people don't agree with it. Had he succeeded, we would all have been dragged down by him too. Therefore, quite a number of them are unhappy with Manison now.

"On the other hand, there are a lot of members supporting you. Most people hope to use the development union to stick together in groups and obtain better safety assurance, as well as more benefits. But to completely oppose the three Universal Civilizations? That's too unrealistic; not many are willing to take the risk! Therefore, since you stopped Manison and also built a closer relationship with the three Universal Civilizations, many people are appreciative of you and recognize you for what you've done, and they stand on your side."

Hearing this, Han Xiao looked around, and in many eyes around the room, he saw friendliness.

"Hmm, as expected," Han Xiao responded. He had figured all this would happen long ago.

At this time, a raging voice suddenly sounded from beside.

"Black Star, you're such an *sshole!"

The people looked at the source of the voice, Secret Master was walking over to him with a blaming expression on his face.

"What did I do to you?" Han Xiao was confused.

"Still playing dumb!" Secret Master was furious. "You messed up my black market forces in the Ancient Star Desert during the Star Field lockdown!"

"I was just following orders to prevent the virus from leaking." Han Xiao blinked.

"Do you think I'd believe you‽" Secret Master said with rage.

Only after the three Universal Civilizations stopped the lockdown did he know that his forces in the Ancient Star Desert had become a mess because of Han Xiao. He almost vomited blood.

"You really have misunderstood me," Han Xiao explained slowly. "The three Universal Civilizations wanted me to control the black market to prevent the virus from leaking. Since it was an abnormal situation, I had to use an abnormal method, so I had no choice but to be aggressive. Furthermore, the Intelligent Plague has already been dealt with, and I've moved out of there. It's the three Universal Civilizations that are trying to continue to control the Ancient Star Desert's black market. I only took on this sinful job for the sake of the safety of the universe. Even if I didn't do it, someone else would have, right?"

Secret Master clenched his teeth. "… The thickest thing I've ever seen is your skin!"

He did not really want to blame Han Xiao. He knew that the three Universal Civilizations would not compromise even one bit in the face of such a large disaster. At this matter's roots, he could only blame himself for being so unlucky that the location of the virus outbreak happened to be the Ancient Star Desert.

Secret Master also realized that ever since he crossed paths with Black Star, he kept getting unlucky.

I'd better stay away from Black Star so that I won't get affected if he's struck by lightning one day!

As they were chattering, another remote projection arrived. It was Manison, who was at the center of the storm.

Buzz!

In an instant, the entire place became silent.

Everyone looked over at Manison and Han Xiao with eyes that had various emotions.

The only similarity these eyes had was that they were all looking forward to a show.

Manison turned around and calmly looked Han Xiao in the eye.

As if the fight between two of them never happened, Manison slowly greeted Han Xiao with a calm expression. "We meet again, Black Star."

"What a coincidence, Mechanic Emperor. I thought you'd be too ashamed to attend the meeting today." Han Xiao chuckled.

At this point in time, he felt he looked more like a villain than Manison.

On the side, Milizaus rubbed the dragon horn on his head with confusion.

… Didn't you agree not to provoke the Mechanic Emperor? Did you completely forget what I literally just said?

Chapter 1133: Confrontation

Manison did not get baited. He sized Han Xiao up and nodded. "You're quite humorous. I'm the development union president. I wouldn't miss the meeting even if you might."

Han Xiao stood with his arms crossed and said, "As the president, what you did doesn't really live up to your position though. Not everyone supported you, yet you made the personal choice of kidnapping their interests and gambling with it."

The moment he saw Manison, he completely forgot about not provoking him. In fact, all he wanted to do now was provoke him.

Knowing about the side the association was leaning to, he deliberately tried to bring up the dissatisfaction of the people around, which proved to be quite effective. Many people looked at Manison with even unfriendlier eyes. They were all important people, so none of them liked having anyone else make decisions for them.

The two of them had now clearly drawn the line and gone back to being competitors. Damaging Manison's reputation was not the main goal; satisfying his guilty pleasure was… Wait, it seemed like it was supposed to be the other way round.

The allies of the federation present felt the most awkward. Manison was still the federation's ally on paper, but they did not want to be on Manison's side either. Those who supported Manison before were feeling uneasy.

Manison completely ignored how the people around him looked at him and coldly said, "I've finally seen through you after this. The purpose of us creating the association was to gain more power and not be controlled by advanced civilizations. You claim to be thinking for the Beyond Grade As, but you're actually just a dog of the three Universal Civilizations. Everything I do is for the Beyond Grade As in the long run, and it's impossible not to take risks… Sadly, you want to suck up to the three Universal Civilizations and not lose your reputation among the Beyond Grade As, so you chose to destroy our hope. In my eyes, that's nothing but a selfish act of an opportunist. I will never have any hope in you anymore."

"Oh, I didn't expect the great Mechanic Emperor to have to resort to bullsh*tting. Being old surely has benefits. Even your way of twisting the facts is so skilled." Han Xiao did not mind at all and said, "Sadly, the audience's eyes are clear. The things you're trying to frame me for won't stick. Everyone has their own opinions about the truth. As the vice president, I have a duty to stop you from forcing everyone to take one path till the end."

"Hehe… do you really think of yourself as the hero just because you're wearing the coat of public opinion the three Universal Civilizations have weaved for you?"

"You've got a lot of things to say now, but I'm very curious, will you have the face to attend the award ceremony sometime soon that'll be broadcast to the entire universe?"

"Why not? If not for me, how could the three Universal Civilizations have discovered the virus so soon? How could the special antivirus program have been invented so quickly? Without me, the Intelligent Plague would still be running rampant even now. In terms of contribution, I'm not much inferior to you, but the three Universal Civilizations never said a single word about it. How obvious are their intentions?"

As the conversation got a kick start, the two of them started to argue without holding back.

They started arguing… and the various Beyond Grade As watched with popcorn from the side.

After arguing for a while more, Manison looked around and said coldly, "I didn't come to argue with you today. The purpose of the association is to solve conflicts between Beyond Grade As. As the president, I have to set an example, so don't worry, although we have our differences, I won't do anything to you."

"You say it in such a nice way. I think you're so busy dealing with the three Universal Civilizations and simply don't dare to mess with me anymore," Han Xiao said with a mocking tone.

Manison narrowed his eyes and said, "You seem to think that our tie was real. We both know the truth, but you seem to have misunderstood something. Do you really think you can fight on par with me?"

"That's the truth, not a misunderstanding." Han Xiao chuckled and said with a taunting tone, "If you don't approve of it, I'm available anytime."

He had gotten quite a lot of good stuff from Manison, including even his core Unique Talent, so he even wanted to fight Manison more.

"The purpose of the development union is to solve physical conflicts between Beyond Grade As. I won't lower myself to your level."

Manison turned and walked into the venue with an expressionless face, no longer bothering with Han Xiao.

Seeing this, Han Xiao secretly curled his lips.

Old Man Manison really is patient. If I provoked him like this in the past, he would have undoubtedly come looking for me to have a talk with a forty-mile-long sword in his hands.

However, the Mechanic Emperor should feel frustrated too. He was so certain he could defeat me, but he was forced to stop at a tie by the three Universal Civilizations, and now he has to patiently wait for the opportunity to regain his position. Until then, he will have to watch his reputation get weakened with his own eyes.

I, however, not only acquired his core Unique Talent but also secretly acquired the incomplete blueprint of the virus technology that he dreams of having. I even got a new ability that counters him… but in his mind, my strength is still the same as when we fought.

If I fight him again, I'll certainly give him a 'surprise'.

While Han Xiao was smiling in his head, Kasuyi came over and said, "I've not seen Manison get forced to do something for a very long time. You're one of the very few people who can give him a loss."

Han Xiao turned to look at him and said with surprise, "I thought your relationship was quite good with Manison, but you seem quite happy."

Kasuyi smiled with narrowed eyes. "Hehe, don't misunderstand, I have known Manison for many years, and we are indeed quite close friends. However, he's him, and I'm me. To be frank, I don't agree with what he tried doing either. Even if you didn't stop him, I would've drawn the line with him after the incident."

Han Xiao nodded. "Without this matter, the Mechanic Emperor and I might still be friends. Sadly, our philosophies are too different. I only hope this did not affect the relationship between us."

"Don't worry, your conflict with him won't affect our relationship. I don't mind differences in philosophies because I think everyone has something they want… However, although Manison's method was not the most righteous, he did say one thing right. The three Universal Civilizations are just using you to damage him, and when you're no longer of value too one day… his present might become your future."

"I know my lines. You don't have to worry about that.

While the two of them spoke, a third voice appeared. "Therefore… while we're still being used by advanced civilizations, we'll have to quickly get any benefits we can. This comes from my personal experience."

The two of them looked over and saw Sorokin, who had come too. Sorokin added his almost symbolic fake smile to the conversation and greeted the two shareholders.

"Oh, it's you." Han Xiao glanced at him. "What other ideas do you have?

"You're flattering me, Your Excellency Black Star. I'm just an ordinary Beyond Grade A. I'm in no place to take part in such a big topic. I don't have any good ideas. I'm just giving my suggestion from the perspective of a businessman, hoping to provide Your Excellency Black Star with some ideas to deal with the current situation." Sorokin's tone was passionate.

Han Xiao crossed his arms and sized Sorokin up.

"It doesn't look like you're just here to have a chat. What do you want?"

"Haha, nothing can escape Your Excellency Black Star's eyes indeed," Sorokin said with a bright smile. "I'm hoping to talk about a partnership with you…"

Han Xiao listened to him for a while and finally understood what he meant. He was not even surprised about how shameless Sorokin was.

He had become the consultant of the three Universal Civilizations, so he now had support from all three of them. Sorokin saw a business opportunity, so he wanted to forge a deeper partnership with him, a shareholder.

Han Xiao had gotten this shareholder position basically by robbing it, and Sorokin was not happy about it at all initially. However, now that he saw he could profit from it, he instantly put all that behind him without hesitation and came to speak with Han Xiao. The beef between them was not even cleared, yet he could act as nothing happened.

Over the past few months, Han Xiao had been busy dealing with the Intelligent Plague, while Sorokin had been dealing with how displeased the three Universal Civilizations were with him. After paying a hefty price, he was finally able to mitigate the damage.

Not only that, through some flashy moves, Sorokin was able to prove that his stand was the same as that of the three Universal Civilizations, as well as connect with some of the officials of the federation and the church who had real power. He also used his director position in the association to build new profit networks.

Han Xiao suddenly thought of something. "By the way, Manison is also a shareholder of the Limitless Financial Group, so won't the things he did affect you too? Can the three Universal Civilizations allow him to continue being a shareholder?"

"Well, it did have some impact. However, that doesn't stop me from continuing my partnership with him, and the scheduled dividends won't stop for him either."

"The three Universal Civilizations allow that?"

"Firstly, my financial group is private and legitimate, so I have the right to freely choose who's in my financial group. Secondly, hehe…" Sorokin giggled but did not say anything and gave Han Xiao a knowing look.

Then it occurred to Han Xiao. No wonder the three Universal Civilizations did not mind the two of them having a partnership. They were using the Limitless Financial Group as a way of acquiring information about Mechanic Emperor's forces. This had to be one of the terms Sorokin had to provide to regain the three Universal Civilizations' support.

Of course, he did not want to develop a deeper partnership with Sorokin, so he never gave any direct answers to any of Sorokin's questions and just dragged on the conversation.

The people chattered for a while, and it was finally time to start the meeting. They swarmed into the venue and sat on their seats.

Han Xiao did not continue insulting Manison. Following the theme of this meeting, the two of them dealt with matters one after another just like the usual plenary meetings.

However, although the two of them were minding their own businesses, the atmosphere was still very strange. After what happened outside the venue earlier, most people were influenced and acting completely normal would be quite difficult.

Very soon, the last topic arrived. Manison looked around at everyone and said with a deep voice, "Due to the sudden outbreak of the Intelligent Plague, the conflict between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance was postponed for more than half a year. Now that the plague has been dealt with, these two sides are about to start fighting. Our Beyond Grade A Association needs to pick a side.

"As all of you know, the three Universal Civilizations have been holding tight to the Ultimate Knowledges. The terms they gave was to have us deal with the Super Star Cluster Alliance in their place, which I don't intend to agree to. Therefore, I suggest we hold our original stand and do not take part in the war between advanced civilizations."

The people nodded. Although they were unhappy with Manison, this decision was agreed upon by most of them previously, so there was not much argument.

As for the direct members of the three Universal Civilizations, they usually did not express their opinion at times like this. After all, there would be no point even if they did.

However, this time, Manison turned to Han Xiao and suddenly asked, "Vice President, what do you think?"

Han Xiao's eyes flickered, and he started pondering. He noticed what the Mechanic Emperor intended to do.

He was now at the center of public opinion. The reasons behind the three Universal Civilizations' recent compliments of him might not exclude them wanting him to become the representative of the development union who stood on their side. Not only did they hope he would compete with Manison, but they also hoped that he would speak for them in the association.

However, one of the very purposes of building this association was to help the Beyond Grade As escape from the faction lock the advanced civilizations had set up for them, so they did not have to murder each other as tools. On this matter, Han Xiao realized that no matter which side he picked, he would still be negatively affected.

Supporting the overall agreement of the people present was not a problem on the association's side, but although the three Universal Civilizations would not be surprised about it, they would feel somewhat disappointed, which would reduce the support he would receive. The other allies could make this choice because they were the 'crowd', while he was the 'representative' whom the three Universal Civilizations had high hopes for. The impact was different despite the choice being the same.

If he spoke for the three Universal Civilizations and encouraged everyone to deal with the Super Star Cluster Alliance, it would be even worse. He would look like he had completely taken the side of the three Universal Civilizations and become the 'dog' that the Mechanic Emperor claimed he was, which would undoubtedly displease everyone. Furthermore, the philosophy he represented would look different. It would turn from peaceful co-existence to sucking up to the three Universal Civilizations, which completely went against the purpose of the association and was exactly the same as the original path everyone was taking.

Han Xiao looked up. Everyone present, including the direct members of the three Universal Civilizations, was focused on him. They clearly knew what impact this decision he made would have, so they waited for him to make a stand.

Manison's question could not be considered dirty or anything. It was just rightfully using the opportunity.

"Of course, I agree with everyone. That's why we gathered here in the first place… However, I'm going to deal with one of the Super Star Cluster civilizations. I have some private beef with them," Han Xiao said calmly. He was very realistic, so he would not pick the wrong side at times like this.

When the three Universal Civilizations were praising and supporting him, Han Xiao had known a moment when he had to prove to the other Beyond Grade As he did not 'change his heart' would come.

Hearing his answer, the people were satisfied.

After the business was done, the plenary meeting ended, and the Beyond Grade As went offline one after another.

Han Xiao, however, did not leave immediately. He dragged Hila, who had been only watching, to the said, found a room, and closed the door.

"You've returned." Hila sized Han Xiao up and said, "You seem to have lost weight."

"I should be the one saying that to you. How's the Underworld?" Han Xiao smiled.

"It's getting stable and slowly recovering… By the way, I have something to tell you. It's about the Underworld too."

"What a coincidence, I have something I want to ask you about the Underworld too, but you go first."

Hila nodded.

"Okay, have you heard about the Sanctum?"

Han Xiao's face was filled with shock. He subconsciously pressed his hand on his chest where his heart was.

At that moment, he finally understood how Oathkeeper felt.

Chapter 1134: That Must Be a Fake Black Star

"Where did you hear about the Sanctum?" Han Xiao asked with a shocked tone.

"The Underworld told me…" Hila briefly repeated what Onicelu had said. Seeing Han Xiao's reaction, she said, "Humph, so you knew about the Sanctum long ago but didn't tell me."

"Ahem, that's because I didn't know everything about it either, and I'm still privately investigating." Han Xiao coughed and quickly worked his brain.

Hila's message gave him a surprise. He initially only wanted to ask the Underworld Hero Spirits about Soul Emperor, but he was also able to acquire new information about the Sanctum.

According to Hila, someone once invited the two sisters to participate in an operation targeted at the Sanctum. This meant that some Primordial Ones possessed more information about the Sanctum, only that those two sisters did not go in the end. After that, for some unknown reason, the information about the Sanctums seemed to be cut off. Fewer and fewer people knew about it.

Furthermore, Han Xiao also acquired an important piece of intelligence from Hila—one of the Sanctums' functions was reviving the dead. This was the first function of the Sanctums he had discovered, and it finally opened the mysterious curtain for a bit.

The Holy Accord organization, revived Primordial Ones, the Sanctums…

Han Xiao finally felt like all these things were connected.

No wonder Oathkeeper was acting that way…

Previously, he did not connect the two of them because he did not know the exact use of the Sanctums. Now, he finally had a clearer image of the Holy Accord organization.

One of the rewards of My Primal Esper Ability Collector Milestone Mission was the Third Sanctum Ability Fragment, which means these two are connected in some way. Then the true goal of the Holy Accord organization in collecting Primal Esper Abilities should be to open the Sanctum and revive people from the past…

Seeing that Han Xiao looked like he was deep in thought, Hila frowned and asked, "Was this information useful to you?"

"Useful, very useful." Han Xiao regained focus and said, "Actually, I've been secretly collecting information about the Sanctums, and you've helped me a lot this time. Great job."

"As long as it's helpful for you." Hila stopped frowning and nodded. She then asked, "Then what were you going to tell me earlier?"

"Haha, I happen to want to ask the Underworld Hero Spirits some questions, and now I have one more question to ask."

"Do you need me to awaken the Hero Spirits right now?"

"That'll affect your growth, won't it?"

"As long as you need me to, I don't mind it." Hila did not hesitate at all.

"You don't have to do that. The Underworld is inherited by you after all. Don't only think of me." Han Xiao shook his head, sighed, and said, "Let's not rush. We'll talk about it when the Underworld recovers."

"Alright, just tell me when you need it. I'll help you anytime," Hila said softly.

"We'll talk about it then." Han Xiao nodded, changed the topic, and smiled. "By the way, I brought you a present this time. You should like it."

Hila's eyes sparkled. "What is it?"

"I've made an agreement with the three Universal Civilizations, and I can now acquire three Esper Ultimate Knowledges for you. I brought one for you this time. I'll let Phillip send it to you later."

"Okay." Hila smiled faintly. She was very satisfied with this present, even more glad that Han Xiao still remembered about her even when he was out on business.

…

Han Xiao only logged off after chatting for quite a while more.

His sight returned to his body, which was in the main ship's command room.

The fleet was advancing in the Dawn Star Cluster of the Flickering World. They would reach the edge of the Garu Star Cluster in a few days and return to the army's territory.

Standing beside the enormous floor-to-ceiling porthole, Han Xiao looked at the stars passing by outside and thought back to the meeting earlier.

Manison's risky actions caused him to lose support in the association, and his connections were damaged. Without any accidents, during the next election in fifty year's time, it's going to be very tough for him to have two consecutive terms.

However, that old man Manison isn't one to wait for doom to arrive. He's now busy dealing with the three Universal Civilizations' pressure, but he won't stay passive like that. He'll certainly come up with other plans to improve the situation he's in. Given his philosophy, it's impossible for him to admit he was wrong and go back to the arms of the federation. That would only cause even more problems. The situation can no longer go back to what it was before for him.

He might regain his position as an independent faction like he did in my previous life, but this time, the duration of that will not just last throughout the Calamity of the Supers versions. He will become completely alone. Even if the alliance he had with the federation was not dismantled on paper, the three Universal Civilizations would not give him any more important responsibilities.

Manison's actions caused him to no longer have a Universal Civilization backing him up. However, he could back himself up, so he had the confidence to do this.

If not because Han Xiao had told the three Universal Civilizations about the virus core to reduce the damage caused by the disaster, Manison would not have taken the risk and would still be a comfortable ally of the federation.

Thinking of that, Han Xiao opened the interface and looked at [Key of Adeptus Mechanicus].

The impact of their battle was clearly visible. As the Machinery Faith believers on Planet Magnetic Cloud spread this news as much as they could, the news of him fighting Manison that ended up in a tie was spread in the Machinery Faith very quickly. This had shaken a small part of people's faith in Manison, and Han Xiao attracted a new group of believers.

After the recent events, the bonus of [Key of Adeptus Mechanicus] had increased by quite a lot. The range of bonuses provided by this talent was comprehensive, basically covering all bases of mechanical abilities. Currently, his Machinery Affinity was about 600%, and he also received hundreds of Attribute Points other than in Luck. Furthermore, his ability in the armed, virtual, and many other classifications also improved depending on the believers' preferences. Other than that, his efficiency in building, repairing, and enhancing machines was also improved by a lot. He could also use various machines more efficiently.

The bonuses of the talent were so comprehensive, and the bonuses were still increasing as his believers increased. Han Xiao did not know if there was even an end to it.

"The bonuses I'm receiving aren't the most important part…" Han Xiao chuckled.

His [Key of Adeptus Mechanicus] receiving more bonuses meant he had taken away the Mechanic Emperor's believers, so the Mechanic Emperor's bonuses from this talent decreased.

The more I get, the less Manison has.

As this carried on, Manison's advantage over everyone else would decrease.

I might not have earned the most, but Manison definitely lost the most.

…

After travelling for several days, Han Xiao and the fleet finally arrived at the entrance of the army's territory, Planet Black Gate. He planned to rest there for half a day and then head to the venue of the Black Star Cup.

While he was not around, the construction in the army territory had carried on steadily. The Black Star Cup was going smoothly. The members who were eliminated went back to their posts, and the eliminated players returned to the fourth stage free competition zone in the Flickering World to continue to occupy strongholds… Everything was going well.

Currently, most of the matches of the Black Star Cup had already ended. Only the last two most popular matches were left. They were the duel finals of the Calamity Grade group and the square group finals of the players group.

The two contestants of the former were both elite Black Star Guards. One was the old bootlicker Hadavy, and other was the newbie bootlicker Jotina. Both were Beyond Grade A seeds, and they stood out from the various Calamity Grades of the army.

Not considering Han Xiao and Hila, these two were recognized as among the strongest in the army.

Originally, both Lagi and Lothaire would also be qualified enough to fight for the top place among Calamity Grades, but Lagi, being Lagi, had already given up in the qualifiers.

As for Lothaire, it was not suitable for him to appear in front of the public due to his job, so he did not participate in the Black Star Cup.

As for other Calamity Grades, none were a match for Hadavy and Jotina. Even Feidin and Nero could not make up for the difference in direct strength with their Advanced Luck Glow.

As for the square groups contestants on the players' side, they were Frenzied Sword's Team Rivervale, King Admiral's Team Dynasty, Rainy Kim's Team Thunder Storm, and a group of very highly skilled players' Gold Team.

Only one of the Chinese clubs entered the finals of the Pro League, but this was different because the rules of the Black Star Cup were less strict, more random, and more dramatic compared to the official league. Usually, the big clubs would always face attacks from the other three sides at the same time in square scrimmages. Hence, Long Sky, Temple of God, and Fried Eggplants with Fish all got eliminated by their passionate fans.

The fleet docked at Planet Black Gate.

As soon as Han Xiao walked down from the spaceship, he saw Sylvia welcoming him on the dock. A security perimeter was set up. The crowd watched from behind it with curiosity, including some army warriors and players.

Not only that, they even held up a set of banners. The left one said "Holding loyalty with iron shoulders", the right said "Carrying lives with a merciful heart", and the middle said "Welcome home, hero of the universe"!

"What the hell…" Han Xiao's eyes opened wide with shock. He turned around, walked back to the cabin, closed the hatch, and opened it again, making sure he was not seeing things.

Did I open the hatch wrong?

While he was being stunned, Sylvia approached him, saluted with the officers, and yelled as if they were afraid the others could not hear them, "Welcome back, Army Commander!"

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. He did not even have to ask to know that this was definitely Sylvia's idea.

Never mind when others praised him, but his own subordinates doing it was too embarrassing, not to mention the fact that this was a public area.

Han Xiao dragged Sylvia aside and whispered with a speechless expression, "What's with the welcome?"

"This welcome ceremony is necessary so that the entire army knows you've returned victorious. It's beneficial for enhancing the members' sense of recognition," Sylvia said with a serious tone, but her barely-suppressed grin sold her heart out.

Speechless, Han Xiao quickly dragged Sylvia toward the dock exit and changed the topic.

"The Black Star Cup is coming to an end. How are the preparations for the closing ceremony?"

As this was a business matter, Sylvia wiped the smile off her face and said, "It's all been settled. When the time comes, you'll have to make a speech and compliment the winners of every contest."

"There are so many items. How many people is that going to be?"

Sylvia rolled her eyes. "You asked for this, hero."

"Alright, I'll be there," Han Xiao said with resignation.

"Also, I suggest that you watch the last two matches live at the venue. Since you've returned, it's best for you to show up at the finals to show how much you care about the competition."

"Well, I'm in no hurry. Might as well."

The group hastily left the dock. In the crowd, a group of players were looking at Han Xiao with extended necks. Many people around them recognized that these people were the Gold Team, which had entered the finals of the square scrimmage. They were all highly skilled players, and their excellent performance during the Black Star Cup attracted quite a lot of fans.

After watching Han Xiao leave, the members of Gold Team all turned to look at their Mechanic teammate, who stood in the middle.

"We actually really got to meet Black Star by waiting here."

"How was it? Were you able to create the Character Summon Card?"

"What ability did you get?"

Their goal of gathering there was to get their Mechanic teammate, who had a Blank Character Summon Card, to copy Black Star's ability. It would be a trump card for the finals.

As Beyond Grade As were very difficult to find, they were initially planning to just copy from a Calamity Grade. However, the army commander coincidentally returned, and no one was a better target for the Blank Character Summon Card than Black Star.

"Don't be so impatient. It's still randomizing."

This Mechanic teammate displayed his interface and looked at it nervously with everyone else.

After about two to three seconds, a notification finally popped up on the interface. The group hastily looked at it.

You have received [Character Summon Card—Black Star].

Ability: [Billion Mechanic Empire—Manison]

Uses: 0/1

Everyone was at a loss.

What's going on?

Wasn't the target Black Star? Why is the ability from the Mechanic Emperor?

At this point, the few of them suddenly trembled. They exchanged looks and saw horror in each other's eyes. They felt they had just discovered a gigantic secret.

There was only one explanation for this situation!

The army commander had been swapped!

That Black Star must be fake!

Chapter 1135: People, It Is Our Turn to Save the Army!

An hour later…

Inside a dark room, the tiny dark green candle was the only source of light. The flame swayed and flickered, illuminating the faces around the table, leaving shadows on the wall. It looked quite scary and creepy.

Above the candlelight, an interface that was displayed to the people around was floating, showing the introduction of the Black Star Character Summon Card.

Gold Team's captain was 'Fly Free', a top non-professional player who started playing all the way back in Version 1.0. He looked worried and troubled as he said in a low voice, "I didn't expect to discover such a big secret. Guys, what should we do now?"

"What else? Publicize it!"

"But this is the trump card we're going to use in the finals. If we make it public, won't we have exposed ourselves?"

"Oi, priorities! Compared to the safety of the entire army, the competition is no longer that important!"

As they were arguing, a female player gently raised her hand and said, "I have a question. Why don't we turn on the lights, instead of this one candle?"

"This kind of dark and mysterious environment is needed for something this important. That's how they play it in the movies."

Another team member scratched his head and asked, "I understand that and all, but why only light one candle?"

"We might be the only ones who've discovered the truth. The atmosphere has to be serious, understand?"

Another teammate gave a long "oh" and then said, "I see, but why only light one candle?"

"Enough!" Fly Free could not take it anymore. He stood up and stopped the replay. Then he went to turn on the light and pulled the rest back on track.

After acquiring the Black Star Character Summon Card, the fragile hearts of all the Gold Team members were shaken. They quickly returned to the stronghold to discuss what they should do.

On dealing with the issue, the opinions of the team were split in two. One side felt they should keep the secret till after the finals; another side felt that the matter was too important, and they should immediately publicize it on the forums to warn the army players that their faction boss might have been swapped.

Although they had worked hard to finally enter the Black Star Cup finals, after discovering this secret, the competition did not seem that interesting anymore. Their attention was completely absorbed by the mystery of the army commander.

The Character Summon Card had a 'Black Star' prefix, but they had no way of knowing if this was also part of the target's disguise. After all, the prefix of Character Summon Cards usually only displayed the target's current identity. It did not have the natural ability to see through disguises.

For example, if they used a Blank Character Summon Card on Sorokin or Oathkeeper, it would only be displayed as 'Sorokin Character Summon Card' or 'Oathkeeper Character Summon Card', not their true identity.

Therefore, this 'Manison' suffix was clearly more convincing!

Boom!

Fly Free slammed the table heavily and said with a firm tone, "I think we should immediately publicize this information. We would never have a chance of getting into the finals of any official league, but the Black Star Cup gave us this opportunity. Even if we lose in the finals, we're still top four, and we'll still have gained a lot of fame. Without the Black Star Cup, all this would not have happened. We cannot forget where we came from. The reward of the competition is nothing compared to the safety of the entire army!

"Plus, throughout the versions, just how many benefits has the army commander brought us? How many of us love this character? He might be in danger now. How can we ignore that! The chance of saving the army lies in our hands!"

The players present were mostly senior Chinese players who had strong feelings for the army. They had come to see it as their home faction long ago.

For example, in order to protect the army and Black Star, Fly Free was even willing to give up their advantage in the final just to tip everyone off. He knew that just a few of them were far from enough to make a difference, so he wanted to unite the army players' power, have them come together to find a way, and expose the Mechanic Emperor's 'conspiracy'!

Hearing this, the people present were reminded of the past and suddenly felt a burning flame of faith in their hearts.

Fly Free reached out his hand. The others understood this gesture. They all reached out their hands and stacked them together. They looked each other in the eyes and saw the strong sense of responsibility in everyone's gaze.

"Now, it's our turn to save the army commander!"

Fly Free immediately opened to forums to start writing a post. Without hesitation, he gave it this title…

'Revelation of the Century! The Unspeakable Secret Between Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor!'

…

The fleet rested for half a day on Planet Black Gate. Then, it very soon started to head toward the venue of the Black Star Cup finals.

Inside the cabin, Han Xiao chatted with Sylvia about business for more than half a day, and only then did Sylvia leave.

Alone in the room, Han Xiao comfortably sat in his chair, casually opened up the forums, and started his daily idiotic players observation time.

"Let me look at the happy meal today…"

Han Xiao hummed in a great mood as he entered the forums, but he was instantly stunned.

With a glance, the titles were all along the lines of 'Extremely Urgent, Please Share! The Army Commander's Identity Has Become A Mystery!', 'Mechanic Emperor's Horrifying Conspiracy!', 'Danger! The Black Star Army's Owner Might Have Changed!', and 'Please Save the Army Commander!'. The entire Flickering World panel was filled with posts similar to those.

What in the world is this‽

It's not even been a day since I last looked at the forums. What happened?

Confused, Han Xiao opened the most viewed post. The original poster was surprisingly an ID he knew, the captain of Gold Team, Fly Free.

The post started directly with a high-resolution screenshot, the introduction of the Black Star Character Summon Card. As soon as Han Xiao saw the [Billion Mechanic Empire—Manison] ability, he had a rough idea of what was going on, and his lips started twitching uncontrollably.

You can't be serious. I have thousands and thousands of abilities, and he somehow copied this ability to the Blank Character Summon Card? How lucky can these people be? Speaking of which, I've only just returned. When did they use the Blank Character Summon Card on me? Was it at the docks?

He continued reading. As he expected, Fly Free explained what happened.

"Comrades of the army, I'm Gold Team's Fly Free. About an hour ago, we discovered a shocking secret!

"Not long ago, when the army commander returned to his territory, our team was in the crowd, and we planned to use one Blank Character Summon Card to copy Black Star's ability. Initially, we planned on using it as the trump card in the upcoming Black Star Cup final. However, as everyone can see from the screenshot, never could we have expected to get the Mechanic Emperor's ability from Black Star! This completely appalled all of us!

"We could not understand the situation. After some discussion, we came to a shocking conclusion. The army commander now might be the Mechanic Emperor in disguise! His goal is to replace Black Star and take over our army!

"In the end, we decided to immediately publicize this crucial information. We need everyone to unite, find the truth, and destroy this conspiracy! Comrades, the future of the army is in our hands!"

Han Xiao looked like he was constipated.

I mean, this deduction isn't complete nonsense, but why do I still feel like these people are mentally challenged?

He looked at the responses below, which had already exploded. Countless people expressed their doubts.

"Is this real? Is this screenshot photoshopped?"

"It has to be. Youngsters are trying to come up with big news every day."

"Are you guys trying to make the news and attract some attention while it lasts because you know that you have no chance at winning?"

"Bullsh*t."

"It's over. Someone is going to have to change his name into Mechanic Emperor's Big PP."

Facing the doubts, Fly Free responded to these comments.

"I know everyone definitely has doubts. On the day of the final, we'll use this Character Summon Card and display it, so everyone will believe that we need to save the army!"

Save your ass!

Han Xiao ground his teeth and returned to the panel, quickly browsing through the related posts. He realized that other than those who doubted it, there were also quite a number who made posts to seriously analyze the possibility of it being true.

_____________________

[Reinhard: Perhaps it's true. The Mechanic Emperor totally has motive. Didn't the two of them fight with each other some time ago in the Ancient Star Desert? Could it be that the Mechanic Emperor attacked the army commander after that?]

[Pikachu: If this one is fake, then where's the real army commander? Did he die?]

[Wolf Flame: That shouldn't be possible. After all, just think about how tanky the army commander is. I think that Mechanic Emperor might have just exiled him, and he can't come back anytime soon, which is why Mechanic Emperor dares disguise himself as Black Star!]

[Hippo: Are you guys all going with the story that the army commander has been swapped by default? Why can't Black Star have learned the Mechanic Emperor's ability somehow?]

[Smelly Feet Slayer: That's too unlikely. This is the first time in so many years that the Blank Character Summon Card has gotten an ability from Black Star with a suffix.]

[Zero Square Foot of Zero: Could it be that they've made some kind of deal to teach each other their abilities?]

[My Dog's Name Is Lagi: Hmm, so… if we use Blank Character Summon Cards on Mechanic Emperor now, we might get 'Indestructible Body—Black Star'?]

_____________________

You really are a genius… Han Xiao's teeth were almost starting to hurt from all the grinding.

_____________________

[Ice Tornado: Wait, there are other possibilities too! Could it be that Black Star was taught by the Mechanic Emperor from the beginning‽]

[Blueberry: Holy sh*t! That does sound possible. If Black Star has been Mechanic Emperor's secret disciple since long ago, that'll explain his extremely quick rise!]

[Shadow Song of Execution: If that's true, their conflict some time ago might just be a show. They appear to be on opposite sides, but they're actually on the same side! What a plot twist… I figured it out! The Mechanic Emperor is planning something huge, and he's playing a gigantic match of chess!]

_____________________

Figured your ass out!

Veins popped up on Han Xiao's forehead.

_____________________

[Blood Rose: No, my curiosity can't be suppressed any longer. What happened between Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor?]

[Paradise Disco: Just a tiny question, will I get killed if I ask the army commander directly? Although I'm not afraid of that…]

[Bun-Hit-Dog: Ah, my eyes see through all. A storm is brewing. This secret might lead to a new enormous main storyline… I have a feeling that the theme of the next version is going to be the Black Star Army's split! I'm going to have plenty of material again!]

_____________________

What split! You're the one that's going to split!

Han Xiao had a feeling that if he caught these players and shook them hard enough, he would most certainly hear the sound of liquid flowing in their empty heads.

Then, he suddenly saw a new post. The title was 'Army Rescue Operation—Recruitment Post'.

He clicked in and saw that it was a post from Free Sh*t again.

"Brother and sisters, the Black Star Army has accompanied us over four versions. This is our faction, and we can't allow others to rob what we've worked so hard for!

"However, sadly, the army's officers will not believe what we say. Only us players can see the evidence.

"Because of that, I've decided to start a righteous mutiny. When the closing ceremony of the Black Star Cup is broadcast live to the entire universe, I'm going to step out and expose the Mechanic Emperor's real identity to everyone!

"Therefore, I need all of your power!

"Although we're far from being able to match Beyond Grade As, we can use our lives to show the entire universe the Mechanic Emperor's conspiracy!

"All heroes who are willing to participate in the operation, leave your name under this post and contact us.

"Comrades, unsheathe your swords. We're the only ones who can save the army now!

"Even in death, I'm still a member of the Black Star Army!

"Mechanic Emperor Manison, show us your HP bar!"

Han Xiao was completely astounded.

He looked down, and the comments of this post were growing by the hundreds each second. Countless people were thrilled and signed up for it.

What the hell? Are they planning to backstab me‽

Should I feel a headache now, or should I feel touched?

This proves that what I've done in the past four versions has been very effective. I've already built a strong emotional bond with the Chinese players. The fact that these players are willing to go this far for me, it's really touching…

Touching my ass!

What kind of turn of events is this‽

He looked at the post again for two more times and clenched his teeth.

"Frankly, this post did indeed make me quite heated… Damn it, smaller brains do indeed occupy less space in the brain to give room for more stupidity!"

Chapter 1136: This Is Love

Han Xiao could not help but rub his temples.

Players were the incarnation of anarchy. Even though they were already members of his own faction, they could still not be fully controlled. Although their intentions were good, what they did would always end up causing all kinds of strange things to happen.

The atmosphere of the entire forums got carried away by this topic.

After being frustrated for a while, Han Xiao suddenly laughed.

"These guys really can't seem to stop causing problems… but this might not be a bad thing."

He pondered for a while and suddenly realized that he did not have to stop the players.

Not to mention that the players were communicating on the forums and there was no way he could use that as evidence to catch them, this was not a bad thing for building a sense of belonging for the army.

If not because the senior players loved and cared about him, they would not try to 'save' him.

He did not have to operate a universal armed force like a tinker, fixing any problems that appeared. Instead, letting the players cause some trouble during the closing ceremony would even bring the Black Star Cup more attention, and he did not even have to plan anything.

The players were led by Fly Free, who wanted to backstab him in the name of justice, but this was completely harmless in Han Xiao's eyes. He was happy to put on a show with them.

The Black Star Army's public image in the universe was basically an ally of justice recognized by everyone. The people were extremely forgiving toward the army, so even if something like this happened during the Black Star Cup closing ceremony, it would not affect the army's reputation. Instead, it would feel interesting to most people. The Black Star Army basically had the public opinion armor.

Actually, Han Xiao figured out easily that he did not have to explain any rumors spreading among the players to anyone, they were non-issues to him.

I'm the faction leader, a top warlord in the universe, and I didn't really get swapped. If I even have to explain myself in the face of such a weird accusation, it will be a joke.

The evidence of the players' doubts was the Character Summon Card, which actually seemed to make sense from their perspective. However, as long as they could see the big picture, this kind of suspicion would not be able to stand its ground at all. If the Mechanic Emperor really disguised himself as him, there would be way too many flaws in that theory that could not be explained. For example, why did none of the other Beyond Grade As sense it? Why did the three Universal Civilizations not notice it? How could the army's artificial intelligence, Phillip, not respond to it at all? And if he was the Mechanic Emperor, how could the Mechanic Emperor use his secondary dimension army box?

No one in the entire universe could disguise himself as another peak Beyond Grade A perfectly. Even a shapeshifter like 'Illusory Deity' Kant could not.

The players did not understand what seemed like common sense to anyone who could see the big picture, so maybe their accusation would be an interesting topic for galactic residents to discuss over meals. Only completely clueless people would believe it. Their evidence that was on the interface was something that did not exist to ordinary people.

Han Xiao knew very well that the main reason the players believed this theory was that it was still fresh. Once the blind passion faded and they saw that everything was continuing as usual, this kind of ridiculous rumor would collapse on itself.

All important people would be involved in strange and wild rumors. There was no need to explain himself, so he decided to give the players some room for imagination.

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

To the players who only cared about the benefits of the faction, it did not matter who owned the faction. Therefore, being willing to expose the Mechanic Emperor's 'conspiracy' while bearing the risk of being punished by the faction was basically a sacrificial act.

Then does it mean that the more people who take part in this mission, the more united the army is‽

Furthermore, since the players used this reason to cause trouble, the Mechanic Emperor will be the one getting the negative image here!

Having thought of that, Han Xiao smiled and summoned Phillip.

"Phillip, watch the Immortals of the army closely for some time. Report any and all situations to me."

"Okay, hum!"

"By the way, invite the Beyond Grade As to come and watch the ceremony in my name while you're at it. Send one to the Mechanic Emperor too."

"Hum… will the Mechanic Emperor come?" Phillip tilted his little head with confusion.

"How would I know? Just send it to him. It's best if he comes. I'll have a chance to provoke him again." Han Xiao giggled.

"Alright then, hum…"

Seeing Han Xiao's evil smile, Phillip obeyed him without asking anything.

"Black Star invited me to attend an event?"

At a secret base somewhere in Primeval Star River, Manison, who was trying to simulate the Virtual Mutiny Virus, stopped and looked at his artificial intelligence with confusion.

"Yes, he's invited you to attend the Black Star Cup closing ceremony."

What's wrong with this guy?

What makes Black Star think I will give him face after what happened?

Manison could not understand it at all.

Is he trying to fix our relationship?

Or make me lose face in public?

"I'm not going. Reject it," Manison replied and continued to reverse engineer the technology.

"Okay, message sent."

Manison replied with a soft grunt and then stopped what he was doing for a moment. "By the way, remind me to watch the stream on the day of the Black Star Cup closing ceremony."

Although he did not plan to give Han Xiao face, he still wanted to find out what Black Star was attempting to do. There was definitely a reason he had received an invitation.

While the discussion about whether Han Xiao was 'real or fake' raged on the forums, the last two finals of the Black Star Cup started as scheduled.

Countless audience platforms floated above the venue planet, covering the sky. They were all fully occupied by army members and spectators who had bought live tickets.

The audience platform specially made by the army was in the form of an oval shaped cabin. All the walls were transparent, so the spectators inside could see the outside from any angle. The walls also had the function to zoom in.

These audience platforms were also protected by transparent energy shields that could block all kinds of impacts and radiation so that there would not be any spectators lucky enough to get hurt. They could also fly at Mach speed twenty-four to ensure the spectators would be able to keep up with the Calamity Grade battles. With the advanced technology the platforms had, the spectators inside would also not feel any turbulence even when flying at such a high speed and always feel as if they were on the ground.

Today, Han Xiao personally came to watch the competition at the venue. He arrived at the extremely crowded venue and hovered in front of the various audience platforms.

As soon as he showed up, he felt like electricity was running through his skin, as if he was being stared at by countless people from behind.

Han Xiao was not surprised. He knew this was the countless players in the audience seats using 'Detect' on him.

In the eyes of the players, Han Xiao's detailed attributes were still all question marks, but the players' goal was to see the color of Han Xiao's name. The result of that was still green, which showed that Han Xiao was on their side, and they started chattering.

"Let's begin." Han Xiao was not concerned about the players' discussion. He turned and signaled the host to start the finals.

The host coughed and said with a loud voice, "Greetings, everyone. Today is the last day of the official Black Star Cup competitions. There will be a total of two finals, the duel finals of the Calamity Grade group and the Square Scrimmage final of the Immortals group. Without further ado, the first match today will be the fight between two Calamity Grades. Contestants, please enter the venue…"

As soon as he said that, Hadavy and Jotina appeared. After a brief introduction, the two of them went to their own positions and waited for the match to start. Their battlefield was the surface of the entire planet.

As time passed, the atmosphere became more and more tense. The moment the host announced the start of the match, two silhouettes left afterimages in their place and clashed.

Boom!

A shockwave expanded. The two of them instantly started attacking each other. Their movements were extremely quick as they moved across the planet's surface. Everywhere they passed, they would leave cracks and deep claw marks hundreds of meters long on the ground.

Boom!

Violent Pugilist flames continuously landed on Hadavy, shattering all the hills and forests around like a dragon crawling on the land. Disasters such as earthquakes, landslides, and tsunamis erupted.

Hadavy was a hardening-type Esper, while Jotina was a Pugilist. Both of them were good at melee combat. The battle between them was violent and savage, basically just the clashing of muscles and muscles, like two beasts fighting each other. To be more precise, Jotina was attacking, and Hadavy was enduring the attacks. The battle would only end when the one enduring the attacks could not take it anymore or when the one attacking got exhausted.

The impact of a Calamity Grade battle was exciting and beautiful for most of the spectators, but in Han Xiao's eyes, the movements of the two of them were like a slow-motion video. He could easily count how many times Hadavy's skin rippled after he got punched.

With Han Xiao's current level, battles of Calamity Grades had absolutely no suspense. Hence, he decided to look at the forums while occasionally glancing back.

Under the eyes of countless people, the result was finally decided after the two of them fought for a very long time. The surface of the planet looked like it had been hit by a meteor shower. It was tragic. In the end, Hadavy was victorious. Although he was covered in bruises and wounds, Jotina had collapsed from exhaustion first.

After decades of combat training, or rather, getting beat up, Hadavy's defense was now extremely high. In combination with his two Molding Talents, True Damage Immunity and Low Strength Attack Immunity, there was not a single person tankier than him in the Black Star Army other than Han Xiao.

"Haha, I'm the pillar of the army who His Excellency Black Star personally trained for decades. You're still too young."

Hadavy was very proud as he wagged his finger at Jotina, who was on the ground.

If not for his bruised face, this would have been quite convincing…

"Damn it!"

Jotina was not satisfied with the loss at all. She slammed the ground and created a crack dozens of meters wide.

She could not win the championship, which meant that Black Star would not notice her strength. Black Star not noticing her strength meant she would have less time to communicate with Black Star during the award ceremony. Less time to communicate with Black Star during the award ceremony meant it would be more difficult for her to build feelings. More difficulty building feelings meant the chances of her carrying out reproductive activities with Black Star would be lowered. As a new member of the army whose goal was to sleep with Black Star, she was extremely unhappy.

Han Xiao watched as the two of them were sent to have their injuries taken care of. He touched his chin and started pondering.

In my previous life, Hadavy did not reach the Beyond Grade A realm, and Jotina even died at the hands of Beast Ancestor, but now they're both under my command. I've trained Hadavy for decades. His chance of reaching Beyond Grade A, well, isn't zero. It's just that his ability is too monotonous. Even if he does become a Beyond Grade A, he'll probably be at the lowest level like Kohler and Beyoni…

As for Jotina, other than her wild and open personality, Han Xiao quite liked her.

In terms of just potential, the chance of Jotina becoming a Beyond Grade A was probably even higher than Hadavy. However, it would be basically impossible for her to reach Beast Ancestor's level. Han Xiao felt that the limit of Jotina's growth was probably somewhere around the level of 'Star Slasher' Viru, or 'Tyrant' Heber…

Not very strong but not among the weakest.

As Han Xiao was reminded of Heber, he started thinking of him.

Ever since Heber was defeated by him, he had been keeping a much lower profile and quietly growing in the Shattered Star Ring.

Speaking of low profile, Han Xiao was reminded of Psyker again. He felt that this guy's presence had gotten even lower in the universe. He might want to visit the Star Pupil Civilization some time. After all, he was now the Special Consultant of the three Universal Civilizations, so visiting Psyker would be totally within his duty.

While his thoughts ran wild, Black Star Cup's logistics department entered the venue and started using tons of industrial devices to operate on this almost destroyed planet.

After a new venue was built, the host announced the start of the last final. Rivervale, Dynasty, Thunder Storm, and Gold's teams entered one after another, greeting the spectators.

However, all the players' eyes were focused on Gold, even including the other three teams. Clearly, they were waiting for their proof.

"Captain, should I use the Character Summon Card now?"

Fly Free looked around the entire place and firmly said, "Use it! This is the perfect time to prove we were not lying."

The Mechanic player took a deep breath, opened the interface, and activated the Black Star Character Summon Card. Then, he enlarged his status bar and made it public.

Of course, as the interface was displayed, ordinary people would not be able to see it. Only the players could see the name of the effect given by this Character Summon Card.

Black Star Character Summon Card—[Billion Mechanic Empire—Manison]!

"It's true!"

The players became excited. Some even stood up and made the other spectators confused.

Han Xiao floated in midair with his arms crossed and listened to the discussions of the players from the feedback of the cameras inside the audience platforms. He smirked.

After a while, many players calmed down and looked up at Han Xiao's back view. All kinds of emotions appeared in their eyes.

Originally, since this was the last final, it should have been the center of attention. However, many players were in a state of shock and confusion and could not focus on the match. The NPC spectators were as excited as usual, cheering for the four teams, completely ignorant of the emotional rollercoaster the Immortals were going through.

Han Xiao did not focus much on the match either and was looking at the players' comments on the forums. The match ended very quickly. Dynasty was the winner, and Gold Team was the first to get eliminated.

Gold Team had exposed their trump card in advance, so as expected, they got focus fired. Furthermore, [Billion Mechanic Empire] was not very powerful in the hands of the players yet.

The players did not have those high-level Mechanic abilities and could not benefit from the specific bonuses. Furthermore, the duration was only a short hour, so the most powerful production and invention abilities of this ability were completely useless. The only things the player could benefit from were bonuses to their Intellect, Machinery Affinity, and Mechanic ability levels. These were just the basic bonuses. Though strong, it was not so powerful it would immediately turn the tide.

This ability was totally wasted in the hands of the players. Only peak Beyond Grade A Mechanics would be able to fully utilize the power of [Billion Mechanic Empire].

"… All the events of the Black Star Cup have now ended. Thank you for watching, and thank you, army commander, for attending the matches today. In three days, we're going to host the closing ceremony of the Black Star Cup. The army commander will be personally congratulating all those who've achieved great results in the Black Star Cup. Ladies and gentlemen, see you then!"

The host then left the venue and ended the broadcast.

The spectators also left the venue, including the players. They kept looking back at Han Xiao while leaving.

Han Xiao smiled and watched them leave. He saw the players' reactions clearly. He uncontrollably raised his brows and felt anticipation for some reason.

I would like to find out how important I am to the players and how many are willing to sacrifice themselves for me.

Chapter 1137: Die! Mechanic Emperor!

It was as if a tide of sacrificial spirit was sweeping across the Black Star Army players.

As the Character Summon Card was proved to be real, the forums temporarily became the intelligence center of Operation Saving Black Star. Many army players gathered in groups and expanded their teams here, making posts under Fly Free's Operation Command Center.

Many senior players who had played since Version 1.0 had a sense of responsibility and faith; they felt they had to do something to solve the crisis of the army falling into the hands of the Mechanic Emperor. Crowds gathered, and even some professional players such as Frenzied Sword and Maple Moon took part. Operation Saving Black Star had become a large event held by the army players themselves.

Of course, there were also those with other motives among the participants. Some just wanted to make the news bigger, some wanted to show their loyalty so Black Star would notice them after 'returning', and some wanted to try to trigger hidden missions.

The atmosphere on the forums was like a war was going on. Everyone thought they were making a difference. However, the majority were just rubbernecking and adding spices. There were not only Chinese players in the army anymore. There were also a ton of international players who joined only in Version 4.0. Most of them were just watching with excitement.

Even among the Chinese players, there were also some who did not think it was worth risking the time and effort they had spent in the Black Star Army and did not take part.

Everything happening on the forums over the past three days was witnessed by Han Xiao. Operation Saving Black Star had absolutely no secrets to him.

Although these players were planning on how to backstab him the next day, not only did Han Xiao feel angry about it, but he even found it interesting.

At this time, Phillip popped out and said, "Master, hum… There are a few Immortals who want to see you. They said they have found out that the Immortals are planning a mutiny, so they want to report it to you."

"Oh?" Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Traitors?

Hmm, come to think of it, since they're players, it'd be weird to not have traitors.

"Tell them to come here," Han Xiao ordered.

After staying for a while in the office, a few players in flashy armor came in. They were clearly foreign players judging from their IDs.

"Yo, army commander." An Ice Demon Race player who seemed like their leader greeted Han Xiao in a very hip-pop style.

Han Xiao acted like he had no idea. He looked confused and asked, "You said that the Immortals are planning on a mutiny? Tell me, what is this about?"

"Yo, here's what it is. We're all good people, but some Immortals are ambitious people. They're not happy with your ruling now, so they plan to use a ridiculous excuse to incite the army. Wow. At tomorrow's award ceremony, they'll attack you definitely."

Han Xiao rose his brows. "What excuse?"

"From what I heard, they said you're the Mechanic Emperor in disguise. Ain't that funny? Hahaha."

"Interesting." Han Xiao sized him up, smiled, and said, "Got it, I'll investigate the matter. If it's true, you'll all be given rewards."

"Hehe, I'd like more Contribution Points." This person was very straight forward.

Han Xiao acted as if he did not hear them. He waved and told them to leave. This time, Phillip reported again, saying there were more people who wanted to see him.

He did not reject any of them and patiently spoke to one group of traitors after another. Most of them were foreign players, and what they said was mostly the same, exposing Fly Free and the others' plan and twisting their motive, claiming the motive of the mutiny was ambition.

After sending off the last group of them, Han Xiao smiled.

"Some of these are pure opportunists, but the rest are probably the spies the foreign professional guilds have placed inside the army. Hehe, they're trying to cause more problems."

He had always known that there were spies of foreign guilds in the army, and this was unavoidable. The motive behind Fly Free and the other senior players' actions was positive, but these spies definitely did not have positive motives.

Han Xiao knew instantly that these spies were trying to make the situation worse. On one hand, they wanted the Chinese players to be heavily punished, so the Chinese guilds would be affected too. On the other hand, they also wanted to reduce his trust in the Immortals so that the army players would receive fewer benefits.

Clearly, the foreign players did not care if he was really the Mechanic Emperor or Black Star. If he was the Mechanic Emperor, he would be alarmed, discover the mutiny in advance, and take action. If this was all a misunderstanding and he was still Black Star, reporting the mutiny to him would also be an act of loyalty. They thought they were killing two birds with one stone.

Without the forums, Han Xiao might have fallen for it. However, Han Xiao already knew everything about this through the forums, so he easily saw through these spies' plan to use him.

Looking at these traitors' satisfied expressions thinking their plan had worked, Han Xiao looked normal but was laughing inside.

I'll let you guys laugh for a while and deal with you after the ceremony.

Han Xiao tapped the table and ordered, "Phillip, secretly dispatch the mechanical soldiers in the warehouse and put them around the venue, especially the VIP area, audience seats, and the news stand. The moment anyone attacks the guests tomorrow, arrest them immediately."

This order was not targeted at Fly Free and the others. Their target was only him, and their motive was to protect the Black Star Army, so their plan did not consist of hurting the innocents.

However, there would most likely be some people who would use this opportunity to cause problems, damaging the army's reputation by hurting the audience. Han Xiao was quite sure that only those foreign pro guilds would do something like this.

Han Xiao did not want to stop Fly Free and the others from 'expressing their loyalty', but he was not going to watch people with ulterior motives damage the army.

Speaking of which, Version 4.0 is in its middle stages now, about to step into the late stage. The national war will probably occur the same time as the Super Star Cluster Alliance battle, just like my previous life. I wonder if those alliances formed by player organizations will still be founded.

Three days passed very quickly. The competition planet had already been turned into an open stadium for the award ceremony.

The main stage was a large floating platform. Only the most important guests were sitting there. It was surrounded by many smaller platforms, where the audience, media, and the winners of various items were seated.

Spherical shields shrouded the venue, blocking the cold wind in the sky and unrelated people from disrupting the closing ceremony. The inside of the shield had a virtual screen that made the venue look like a closed theater.

All kinds of spaceships floated in the exterior atmosphere. The formally dressed spectators, guests, and contestants arrived at the venue on the carriers provided by the army, found their seats, and sat down. Very soon, the venue became crowded. It was a true festival.

Fly Free and his team sat in the contestant seats, looked around, and occasionally exchanged looks with the players on the same floating platform.

Fly Free's shoulder was tapped. He turned around and realized it was the Rivervale team's captain, Frenzied Sword.

"When do we move?" Frenzied Sword lowered his voice. As a real loyal follower of Black Star, he also took part in the operation.

"It's still early. No hurry. Just like the plan, when it's our turn to receive the reward, everyone just wait for my signal and move at the same time," Fly Free said quietly.

"How many people do you think will be with us?"

"Although a lot of people signed up on the forums, it'll be amazing if even one tenth of them actually do carry out the plan." Fly Free shook his head.

"Okay, we'll be waiting for your signal."

The players who were taking part in the Saving Black Star Operation communicated privately. On the other side, there was also another group of people planning for a different operation.

On a floating audience stand, a player with the ID of 'Winter Wolf' asked his friend beside him through a private channel, "Are our men scattered out yet?"

"Yeah, don't worry. Our men are scattered throughout the platforms. Some are very close to the celebrity guest seats. When those Chinese make a move, we'll be able to act in the midst of all the chaos. We'll definitely cause quite a lot of destruction."

"Good." Winter Wolf nodded and said with a low voice, "The Black Star Army faction is too strong. We have to weaken it. This is the first field operation our Northern Battlefront has carried out since its secret founding. We have to make it count to open the path for our national war plans."

"Understood."

At the same time, Han Xiao was welcoming the Beyond Grade A remote projections at the VIP seats on the main stage.

With his position and reputation, almost seventy percent of all Beyond Grade A members of the development union came to watch the event. They all sat at the frontmost seats. Han Xiao casually chattered and laughed with them.

As the seats at the venue were fully occupied, all the lights gradually dimmed, only leaving the main stage brightly illuminated.

Seeing this, the noisy venue quietened down. Everyone's eyes were on the main stage.

Sylvia walked up onto the stage. She was not in her uniform, instead wearing an expensive and elegant purple bare-back dress. She wore light makeup, making her face even more exquisite and beautiful than normal. Her hair was tied up, showing her long and snow-white neck. Her silver earrings swayed lightly, reflecting light from the venue. The bright but not blinding light colored her stunning and marvelous.

She took one look around and said, "Guests, contestants, and viewers behind screens, welcome to the closing ceremony of the first Black Star Cup. I'm the army's Chief Administrative Official, Sylvia."

Then, Sylvia paused as stated in the script. Han Xiao smiled and applauded her. The people around followed his lead. Very soon, the venue was filled with roaring applause.

Seeing this, Sylvia then said, "As the army expands, the number of members continues to grow. The initial purpose of the Black Star Cup was to select the elites of the various professions inside the army so that the new members who are capable but not senior enough can have an extra path to rise up. At the same time, it gives the older members a chance to improve themselves. Now, the Black Star Cup has come to a fulfilling end. To our pleasant surprise, we realized just how many elites the army has in various professions…"

Sylvia started reading the script. The image was broadcast to the entire universe through the media cameras present.

Of course, the Black Star Cup closing ceremony did not consist of only giving out the reward. The detailed order of the ceremony went Sylvia's speech; the Black Star Cup organizing committee's speech; the winners of various items going up onto the stage to accept their reward and each giving a speech; then last but not least, the army commander's concluding speech. There were also a lot of performances and shows in between.

The army had invited many galactic celebrities, such as singers, actors, and the like. All those invited were extremely famous.

Usually, normal events would be honored to be able to invite just one of those celebrities, given how famous they were. However, the Black Star Cup was way too high class. These celebrities were the ones feeling honored to take part in the closing ceremony. This was an entertainment event hosted by a universal-level warlord, so it was an extremely excellent opportunity to build connections with people at the highest level of the society. In order to obtain a spot in the performances, the companies behind many celebrities even had intense fights.

Han Xiao was invited to the stage very soon to give the awards to the winners personally along with some words of encouragement. The remote projections of the two Vice Commanders, Lagi and Hila, stood beside him. They did not speak and only nodded at the contestants to show encouragement.

However, the reasons behind the two of them not speaking were different. Hila did not like talking, so she did not speak, while Lagi's voice communication function was cut off by Han Xiao so that he could not speak.

The award ceremony had breaks, which were filled by the celebrity performances. As the closing ceremony was about halfway through, Han Xiao felt as if his face was twitching from smiling too much, and the spectators' palms were also getting red from clapping too much. Finally, it was time to give the award to the outstanding contestants of the Immortals' Square Scrimmage.

Here it is… Han Xiao focused.

The people walked onto the stage. Fly Free clenched his teeth and walked up. His back gave off a vibe as if he was walking up to an execution ground.

"Congratulations, you're all talents of the army…"

Han Xiao read the script once more, gave Fly Free a glance, smiled in his brain, and took two steps back, giving the stage to the contestants to speak.

No one on the stage stepped forward; they all looked at Fly Free.

Fly Free nodded at everyone and walked to the lectern with heavy steps.

The entire venue was extremely quiet. Everyone's eyes were on him, waiting for his speech.

The players all subconsciously straightened their backs and became nervous, paying attention to every movement of Fly Free.

Fly Free took a deep breath, prepared himself mentally, and spoke.

"I'm very proud to have achieved good results in the Black Star Cup, but that's not what I'm going to talk about today… Just a few days ago, we discovered a shocking secret—the army commander who's standing on this stage now is not Black Star! He's someone else in disguise!"

Hu!

It was like bombs were being set off everywhere.

All the spectators, army officers, guests, celebrities, and even the Beyond Grade As present were completely startled by this sudden change. They looked at this guy and could not respond.

W-what's going on?

"I'm a member of the Black Star Army. This is my home. I will only ever recognize Black Star as our army commander. I won't allow anyone to disguise as our dear army commander to control the army!" Fly Free's tone became firm as he yelled, "Today, right here, I'm going to use my life to expose this guy's conspiracy to the entire universe! Save our leader!"

As soon as he said that, Fly Free turned around, flames erupted all over his body as he charged toward Han Xiao, screaming at the top of his lungs, "Mechanic Emperor! Die!"

At the same time, in a secret base at an unknown location, Manison's hands trembled, and popcorn splashed all over the floor.

Chapter 1138: Players Not Causing Trouble Have No Soul

"Go!"

A sudden change occurred. With a loud shout, the audience platforms erupted into chaos. About one fifth of the players suddenly moved. Silhouettes rose into the sky and headed right toward Han Xiao on the stage. They were all heroic players who had answered the call.

Like a taut string suddenly snapping, the rest of the players became excited about what was going to happen.

In the crowd, Winter Wolf's eyes sparkled. He quickly ordered in the channel, "The chance is here! Let's go!"

The next moment, several hundred players suddenly moved again and were about to attack the audience platform around them.

Winter Wolf flew up from his seat. Layers of frost condensed on his skin as he dashed right toward the celebrity seats.

Excitement appeared on Winter Wolf's face as the reflection of many celebrities' shocked faces entered his sights. Without hesitation, he raised his hand and was about to activate his Esper Ability and release an ice storm to turn these celebrities into ice sculptures.

At the same time, the heroes who were rushing toward the main stage also noticed this group of people who were using this opportunity to attack the innocents. Shock and rage appeared on their faces.

This was not in their plan at all, and subconsciously, some people were about to turn around and stop Winter Wolf and the others guild spies from hurting the innocents.

All these changes happened in an instant. As chaos was about to erupt, a bright electric light blasted in the middle of the venue!

Snap!

Countless bolts of Mechanical Force lightning shot out like a spider net. The mechanical soldiers that were hiding in the various audience platforms activated instantly and pounced at the players who were causing trouble around them.

These mechanical soldiers were all 'Restrainer—Modified' that could disassemble into advanced restraining suits and capture the target alive. Now that they had received Mechanical Force bonuses from Han Xiao, their attributes completely exceeded the players who were Grade B at best.

Buzz!

Black silhouettes crisscrossed everywhere, and electrical sparks flickered. All the players who were rushing toward Han Xiao from all over the place were suddenly controlled by the Restrainers' electromagnetic chains and the restraining devices, unable to move like birds without wings.

Fly Free and the rest of the contestants who were on the main stage were instantly blown away by the exploding energy, falling down at the edge of the stage.

The group of them were just about to climb up and continue to charge when Han Xiao softly flipped his hand over. A powerful energy shockwave pressed onto them and slammed them all flat on the ground. The next moment, the metal floor turned into robes made of nanoparticles under the effect of Han Xiao's Mechanical Force, tying Fly Free and the others up tightly.

Before the guests had time to react, the sudden danger was resolved by Han Xiao, who was prepared.

Whew, fortunately, I'm prepared.

Han Xiao secretly breathed a sigh of relief.

The players were not even at the Calamity Grade, so they were no different from ordinary people to him. They would not be able to cause any threat to him with numbers, but if they were to attack others, the ordinary spectators would definitely be hurt.

Even if he could react quickly, he could not ensure there were no casualties. However, since he was prepared and the players did not know, he was able to restrain all the players the moment they started to move, and no guest was hurt.

This operation was caused by Fly Free leading the momentum; that was all. These people were no different from a group of brutes with no proper unity and plan. Furthermore, most of the participants only took part on impulse, which was a common occurrence among the players. Plus, the time to prepare was too short, so there was no way they would be able to come up with a detailed plan.

The entire operation felt like a suicide mission.

"His responses are way too quick!" Winter Wolf could only feel a flash before his eyes, and he was captured without being able to resist at all. He was shocked.

He struggled to turn around and take a look and saw that all his friends had been captured by mechanical soldiers and restrained, unable to move.

Sh*t, not even one person died… Still, what we did was enough to anger the army and reduce its trust in all the players, which will in turn make the players in this faction receive fewer benefits…

Winter Wolf was a little regretful that his plan had failed to reach the optimal results, but judging from their goal, this was not a total failure.

These changes happened quickly, and the danger was resolved even quicker. The guests present and the spectators from the various Star Fields were stunned for quite a while before realizing what had happened.

Wait a minute, did we just slip past the gate of death?

"What just happened?"

"Looks like the Black Star Army's men started a rebellion?"

"They said Black Star isn't Black Star. Why do I have no idea what that means‽"

"That startled me. To think it wasn't a performance!"

As the guests finally realized what had happened, they became surprised. It had all happened too quick; they did not even sense danger arriving, and it was already resolved. They did not feel scared at all, only surprised and confused.

All the people started discussing the incident while staring at Han Xiao with confusion.

Many army officers quickly came to Han Xiao and stood around him, staring at those players with extremely hostile looks.

Hila stepped forward, her face filled with murderous intent as she yelled, "Arrest all of these rebels. Escort them away and interrogate them thoroughly. I want to know who ordered them to do this!"

"Hey, don't get all tensed up. I still have some questions I want to ask them. Plus, I think the guests would like an explanation too."

Han Xiao pulled Hila back and signaled for the officers to step back.

Feeling the confused and curious looks of the people around, he calmly raised his finger. Nanoparticle robes then separated from the metal ground and slowly flew to before Han Xiao, holding Fly Free and the others.

Deliberately showing a somewhat confused expression, Han Xiao curiously asked, "What did you mean by what you just said? Why would you think I'm the Mechanic Emperor in disguise?"

Fly Free was quite frustrated. The sudden act of so many people had absolutely no impact, and they were instantly wiped out. They had become prisoners of the 'Mechanic Emperor'.

However, at least he yelled what he wanted to say to the entire universe, so his goal was achieved. What was left in his heart was only self-sacrificial emotions, so he yelled, "Mechanic Emperor! No matter how good your disguise is, I know you're fake!"

"Do you have any evidence?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

Only players could see the Character Summon Card screenshot, so this evidence would not work on NPCs. Furthermore, that particular Character Summon Card had already been used to prove what they said, so this reason was not convincing at all.

Fly Free had guessed he would face this question long ago, and he knew he would not be able to convince anyone but the players. He was prepared to insult the 'Mechanic Emperor', so he shouted, "Your vibe!"

"Huh?" Even Han Xiao was stunned for a moment.

"Humph, our Black Star army commander is a man of justice and honor. Just looking at him will make people uncontrollably admire him. But you, Mechanic Emperor, you ignored the safety of the universe for your own sake, attempting to keep the source of the Intelligent Plague for yourself! Your despicable vibe has exposed you!"

"The Mechanic Emperor is despicable?" Han Xiao deliberately raised his tone.

"Very despicable!" Fly Free was not afraid at all. "Who is Black Star? He rose in just a few decades and can already fight you on par. You call yourself an Ancient One? All the years you've spent alive have gone down the toilet! Compared to our army commander… you are nothing!"

Quite many Beyond Grade As touched their nose awkwardly… Why does it feel like we're being insulted too?

Han Xiao's face twitched. He had to do everything he could not to laugh.

Beautiful!

That's right, buddy, keep going!

"So… this is the reason for your mutiny?"

"It's not a mutiny! Don't even think about twisting our motive! We've fought and bled for the army; we're inseparable from the army! Only Black Star has the right to lead us. If anyone else attempts to put their hands on it, we'll definitely retaliate! Even if you kill me today, I'll still continue yelling these words in my grave—never compromise!"

Fly Free said it with so much emotion that even Han Xiao was almost touched.

The infectious words made quite a number of senior players' blood boil. The emotions from many versions rushed to their heads. They were fearless, as they would not die anyway, and they started shouting.

"This is the Black Star Army! F*ck off, Mechanic Emperor!"

"Black Star will shine forever!"

"Captain is the best!"

"Immortals will never be slaves!"

The voices echoed in the venue. The faith inside these words moved many viewers.

So, is this what it's like in the armed forces? How beautiful.

On the other hand, the Beyond Grade As were all at a loss.

From their perspective, this was beyond ridiculous.

At this time, Kant suddenly said, "Actually, I can somewhat understand the mindset of these Immortals…"

The others turned to him with expressions of disbelief.

Kant coughed and said, "I've recruited some Immortals. Most of the time, they're quite normal, but sometimes, they'll show signs of being mentally challenged and do things I cannot understand at all…"

"Such as?"

"… There was one guy who asked me directly to turn into a naked female human. I accidentally killed him… three times."

Kasuyi agreed. "I have some Immortals under my command too. Even I can't understand what's in their heads. Someone actually tried to steal my undergarments. Do you believe that?"

"I recall hearing a theory. Experts say that the Immortal Race's undying trait caused their minds to undergo synchronized mutation, which makes them have intermittent manic episodes, delusions, logic disorders, and other mental disorders."

"Oh, then it makes sense…"

Suspecting that their boss was fake just because the vibe was not right? What kind of normal person would ever do that‽

However, when it was the Immortals who did something like this, the people would instantly accept it. It seemed that no matter what outrageously weird things the Immortals did, the others would not think of it as abnormal.

As soon as the topic was brought up, many Beyond Grade As who also had Immortals under their command started chattering. Very soon, they came to the pleasant agreement that the Immortals had mental issues, and they really respected Black Star for being able to effectively manage the Immortals, who were so unpredictable.

Secret Master snorted and said, "What are you all talking about? This clearly was directed by Black Star to deliberately embarrass the Mechanic Emperor. My eyes have seen through it all."

"It's a shame the Mechanic Emperor isn't here. His expression would be a sight to behold." Milizaus chuckled.

They then imagined what it would look like and giggled with glee.

While they were chatting, Han Xiao had many exchanges with Fly Free, insulting the Mechanic Emperor from head to toe in all styles.

"Come, kill me." Fly Free looked heroic.

Seeing that it was about enough, Han Xiao said, "Although for some reason you are so sure that I'm the Mechanic Emperor in disguise, you really are mistaken… The Mechanic Emperor isn't capable of disguising as me. He's far from it."

Hearing this, Kant laughed and said, "Wouldn't we know if he's Black Star or not? You guys are too young and naïve. At least get some solid evidence before you act."

We do have solid evidence… but only we can see it.

Seeing the reactions of Han Xiao and the other Beyond Grade As, Fly Free and the others started to get shaken. They started to doubt themselves. Those who did not fully believe in the theory that this Black Star was fake started agreeing.

The effects of Character Summon Cards would not be fake, so the possibility of another theory was higher—Black Star had learnt the Mechanic Emperor's ability somehow.

Seeing that they were pondering and hesitating, Han Xiao waved and said, "Escort them away for now. I'll have a proper talk with them after the closing ceremony ends."

He did not do anything to them for the time being. Dealing with these people was the army's internal affair, so it was not suitable to handle it there.

The Restrainers took all the players who caused problems out of the venue. After Sylvia came up to calm everyone's emotions down, the Black Star Cup closing ceremony continued. However, most people's attention was no longer on the ceremony but on this tiny incident.

The closing ceremony was initially just a standard affair, but then it immediately sparked more conversations, attracting more attention. Han Xiao's goal of using Fly Free and the others was achieved.

There were no other twists and turns to the closing ceremony till it ended. Everything that happened there was broadcast to the entire universe through the media groups.

The actions of Fly Free caused a new meme to be born in the galaxy—'Pointing at Black Star to insult the Mechanic Emperor'.

…

After the stream ended, Manison's expressionless face was reflected on the now dark screen.

His eyes were narrowed, and a tint of irritation flashed past his pupils.

Mistaken? As if I believe you! This is clearly a show you directed!

I knew you did not invite me for nothing. It was just a plot to embarrass me in public.

Manison clenched his fists.

Black Star, you're too much!

One day, I'm surely going to cut you up and turn you into a Felon!

Chapter 1139: Compliments from the Big Boss

As the closing ceremony ended, spaceships took off one after another, sending the audience away.

Han Xiao told Sylvia to take care of the guests who had come to show their support in his place, while he led the various officers and Black Star Guards to the main ship in orbit. All the players who had caused trouble were temporarily locked up there, waiting to be dealt with.

Swoosh!

The cabin opened. Han Xiao and the officers swarmed in and immediately saw the intense situation inside. The players locked there were separated clearly into two groups—the majority of the players led by Fly Free surrounded the spies led by Winter Wolf.

Herlous stepped forward and demanded, "What's going on?"

The guard quickly approached and replied, "Your Excellency, they have been arguing for a while now. It seems like they're having an internal conflict."

"An internal conflict between a group of rebels?" A Black Star Guards snickered.

Although Fly Free gave a great speech during the ceremony and expressed that they did what they did for the sake of the army, most of the army officers did not buy it at all. They felt that this was just an excuse for their mutiny. Attacking the army commander in public and attempting to disrupt the ceremony did not look like things someone would do for the sake of the army at all. The army officers did not know the details like Han Xiao, so they would not be easily convinced.

Han Xiao knew what was going on, but he did not explain it. He walked to the players, did not speak, and just looked at them with an expressionless face.

Seeing that Han Xiao had arrived, the two groups stopped arguing and looked at him.

After seeing Han Xiao's reaction and listening to the Beyond Grade As' explanation, the 'loyal' players led by Fly Free were starting to feel shaken, doubting their speculation, but they had yet to fully change their minds. They still felt that this might be a show the 'army commander' had put on to prove his fake identity was real.

Therefore, many people quietly started video recording at this moment, capturing his expressions and actions while they were in private. If he acted completely different from before, something was definitely wrong, and they would upload the video to the forums to once again warn the other army players. They had yet to give up exposing the 'Mechanic Emperor'.

Fly Free stepped up and said with a fearless tone, "What do you plan to do with us?"

"No hurry, I want to hear your explanations again," Han Xiao said casually with a normal tone.

"What else is there to say? We've already expressed our intentions very clearly," Fly Free yelled.

Without any changes in his expression, Han Xiao calmly said, "Even if this was a misunderstanding, your actions will still be punished. Have you thought of the consequences of all this?"

"Of course."

"Even so, you still decided to take the risk for me?"

"It's for Black Star. As for whether you're really him, we still don't know yet." Fly Free crossed his arms.

"Then how do you explain attacking the audience? Was that for the army commander too?" Hadavy said coldly.

Fly Free's expression turned stiff and then to rage. He turned and stared at Winter Wolf and the others angrily. "Our plan was only to expose the imposter. We're not the ones who attacked the audience. These people are not with us!"

Winter Wolf looked shocked. "What are you talking about? Isn't this a secret mission you gave us? Now you're trying to deny all of that?"

"Still bullsh*tting!" Fly Free was furious. "I did not plan this at all. Why did you guys do it‽"

"Tsk, you totally asked us to do it, and now you're throwing us away after using us?"

Winter Wolf did this on purpose to make the Black Star Army think they were together. This way, they could transfer the blame for attacking the audience to Fly Free and the others, and the Black Star Army's trust in the Immortals would be reduced.

The two groups of players started arguing again. These guild spies had made agreements before; they all insisted they were on the same side. The 'loyal' players felt that their motive was repugnant and were furious. Elegant and kind greetings of each others' parents and ancestors kept coming out of their months. If not because of the Restrainers, this would have turned into a brawl.

Seeing this, many army officers curled their lips and looked unconcerned. They felt that this was just a show the Immortals had prepared in an attempt to prove they were innocent.

Hila turned to Han Xiao and softly said, "Black Star, more and more Immortals have joined the army. I think it's time to tighten our control over them, to prevent things like this from happening again."

Someone added from the side, "That's right. We've been too lenient with the Immortals.

Hearing the army officers' discussion, the joy of his plan working flashed through Winter Wolf's eyes.

However, at this time, he suddenly saw Han Xiao looking over with a faint smile.

"You're the leader of these people, right?"

"Me?" Winter Wolf was shocked inside but acted confused.

Han Xiao snapped his fingers. The Restrainers surrounded the hundreds of players who attempted to attack the audience, leaving the rest of the players alone.

"I have video recordings of everyone who attempted to attack the guests. I won't accuse anyone unjustly," Han Xiao said slowly. "As punishment, you will be locked inside Spacetime Amber, and you basically shouldn't think about ever coming out again."

"Unfair!" Winter Wolf yelled and looked at the others. "We're with them! Why are you only catching us‽"

"Bullsh*t!" Fly Free and the others were furious.

"Stop arguing, I knew about what was going on long ago." Han Xiao waved. His expression suddenly became serious as he said, "While you guys were plotting, someone told me about it. I could have actually stopped you guys long ago, but I let you act during the closing ceremony. Do you know why?"

"You knew long ago?"

The people's expression changed. They then thought about it for a moment and realized that there was nothing strange about that. Having traitors among them was totally normal.

However, Black Star not stopping them in advance was something they did not understand, so they were curious about it.

"I briefly know your motive, and I don't really believe you guys would start a mutiny." Han Xiao stopped into the crowd. He patted some people on the shoulder and dragged Frenzied Sword and Maple Moon out from the crowd. He smiled and said, "You're all pillars of the army from the earliest days, and I remember all of you, especially you two. We've known each other for decades. Although we haven't interacted much recently, I'd never doubt you guys."

The people were stunned and greatly surprised. They did not expect Black Star to say something like this, not to mention remembering them.

In this instant, many people felt very touched.

Especially Frenzied Sword and Maple Moon, the two of them were stunned for a few seconds and suddenly looked extremely excited. They were so touched that they were almost ready to sacrifice their lives for Han Xiao right in this moment to show their loyalty and appreciation.

Franky, Han Xiao was quite touched to see these two participate in this little incident too. The two of them were professional players now, yet they took such a big risk to take part in this. They must have deep emotions for him…

Looking at everyone's excited expression, Han Xiao smiled. Then, he turned to Winter Wolf and the others, and his expression instantly turned cold and fierce.

"Ever since the army's expansion, I've known of spies of other organizations managing to infiltrate the army. The reason I didn't stop you was that I was hoping to lure out these spies of the army using this opportunity, and it looks like that worked. I can clearly differentiate the army's pillars from the spies, so don't try to fool me."

Hearing this, Winter Wolf opened his mouth wide with disbelief all over his stiffened face.

Oh my god. Even this got seen through? Are NPCs this difficult to fool‽

They were already mentally prepared to have their accounts permanently 'banned' when they acted. Since they were all employees who received salaries from the various professional guilds, they did not care that much about their accounts. However, now that their plan had been seen right through, it would mean that their sacrifice was completely meaningless, and the plan had failed miserably, which would be a huge loss.

Not wanting to listen to any more words from those spies, Han Xiao took out the Spacetime Amber and sealed the hundreds of them one after another, turning them into more samples. Even if they logged off, their bodies would remain inside.

Looking at this, Fly Free and the others were both touched and excited.

Han Xiao did not explain too much, but him taking out the Spacetime Amber and acting in this way immediately changed Fly Free and the others' minds. They were now basically certain he was the real Black Star.

Possessing Han Xiao's Universal Treasure was one reason, but it was more because Han Xiao had washed away the crime they were framed with committing, and he did not blame them for it. They were very appreciative of that and felt a sense of satisfaction.

"As for you people…" Han Xiao turned around and briefly smiled. "Though I do believe you, rules are rules. Your actions have caused trouble, so there must be punishments. The punishment shall be… you guys have to carry out some missions to make up for what you did, and you will not be able to enjoy the army discounts for three months. What do you say?"

"We deserve it. I have no objections." Fly Free waved his hand.

The rest also agreed. Although they were punished, they felt good about it.

Compared to what had happened to Winter Wolf and the others, this punishment was nothing. The contrast was too strong.

Han Xiao waved and ordered the Restrainers to back off, letting the players leave.

After the players left, Herlous said, "Black Star, is that it?"

"Didn't I punish them?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"What kind of punishment was that? It's basically the same as nothing. When the others see that the punishment is so light, won't they keep attempting to do the same thing?"

"Don't worry, I know what to do."

Han Xiao waved and smiled in his head.

He knew that these players were definitely recording, and they would certainly upload the video to the forums. His actions earlier would not only make the players admire his judgment but also make the faction's sense of recognition go through the roof. It was the exact way of gaining people's hearts.

The method of dealing with Winter Wolf and the other spies was a warning. He was expressing that he could differentiate between friends and foes. With friends, he could be lenient, but if anyone attempted to harm the army, he would be merciless and give them a free lifelong ride inside the Spacetime Amber.

"As long as you have a plan." Hila nodded.

She extremely rarely doubted Han Xiao. Since Han Xiao had made his decision, she did not express any more doubts and deactivated the remote projection after bidding Han Xiao farewell.

Everyone left one after another. Han Xiao looked at the hundreds of amber samples in the place and pondered.

Winter Wolf, I have an impression of this guy. He seems to be a pillar of the Northern Battlefront… Looks like these guild alliances will still appear. The national war is probably about to begin.

In his previous life, a large-scale national war erupted in Version 4.0. It was also called the First World Server War.

It was called the national war, but it was not purely based on nations as factions. As the method of playing Version 4.0 mainly revolved around the players grouping up, as the version developed, the players gathered in bigger and bigger groups. In the end, some professional guilds and non-professional guilds created large guild alliances to form official organizations.

For example, there were ones consisting of mainly Europeans such as Northern Battlefront, Denland, and September Conference; some consisting of mainly North and South Americans such as Galactic Business Alliance, 5C Alliance, and Plateaus Eagle; and the Asian ones such as Southeast Asia War Alliance, Golden Alliance, and Northern Tropic of Cancer Light.

These alliances were not just grouped in nations. The different guilds of one nation might belong to different alliances. Other than the guilds, the casual players would also join different alliances based on their likings.

In Han Xiao's previous life, the army did not exist. The World Server War was not only targeted at one nation but at each other. However, as the Black Star Army was way too strong this time, they became the common target.

Part of what triggered the national war was that the factions were developing. The factions the players of various nations belonged to started to grow into more advanced factions. For example, the conflict between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Civilizations in the Flickering World became one of the fuses of the national war.

The root of conflict between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance was territory distribution, and the intensity of the conflict gradually escalated. The conflict did not start with direct confrontation between their direct armies; the agent war was also a very important part of it. The Immortals were one of the agents. They fought nonstop in the free competition zone.

"The national war is a great opportunity to harvest leeks. However, because of the army, it's definitely going to be very different. I wonder what it will be like…" Han Xiao caressed his chin.

At the same time, Fly Free and the others who had left the cabin quickly uploaded the recording to the forums with excitement.

Chapter 1140: This B*stard Has No Virtue

During the closing ceremony, Fly Free and the other 'loyal' players carried out the operation. After that, almost all the army players were waiting on the forums for what would happen to them.

To many neutral players, these people were reckless and impulsive, so they would certainly suffer heavy consequences. God only knew how severe the faction's punishment would be.

However, when the private recordings from Fly Free and the others were posted, it shocked quite a number of people, and the post instantly garnered millions of views.

The video recorded the full process of Han Xiao's private meeting with them. Seeing how confident and clear-minded the army commander was, the atmosphere on the forums instantly changed into one-sided praise.

[Fly Free: From today onward, the army commander is my brother, and anyone who dares to touch my brother shall feel my wrath! That's all. Who's with me? Who's against me?]

[I'm The Northern Gods' Idiot: +1.]

[Raylei's Gaze: Our Army Commander was way too cool…]

[Mechanic Emperor's Small PP: Although we're just bullsh*ting most of the time, it isn't too much to use the word 'amazing' to describe what the army commander had done today, is it?]

[The Frog Has Seen Through Everything: Honestly, the chances of these spies successfully framing the others shouldn't be low at all. It would have at least led to a thorough investigation from the army. But Black Star's judgement is way too impressive, seeing through the differences between the two groups right away and providing decisive and accurate solutions. Those who really had ulterior motives got their accounts banned, and you guys, the loyal pillars, only got symbolic punishments. This row of decisions by the army commander is quite amazing.]

[Tomorrow Won't Be Better: Sigh, to think that Black Star still remembers us old timers from Version 1.0. It's so touching. Praise Black Star!]

[Bun-Hit-Dog: I'm a newbie who just joined this version. Is the army commander actually this amazing? Wow, how interesting. I'll have to binge watch Bun-Hit-Dog's must-see Black Star Series now.]

[I Love The Dawn: You dog, remember to use your smurf account next time when you do promotion acting as a noob…]

The video got uploaded to the forums as Han Xiao expected, so his goal of getting the hearts of the players was already achieved. Not only did his decisions make him have more 'leadership appeal', but the sense of recognition a lot of army players had for the faction also went through the roof. This nostalgia-inducing, fair, and wise series of decisions he made had planted a seed in the many players, forming a bond with the army.

Although Han Xiao did not deliberately explain his identity in public, his actions had already indirectly cleared the players' doubts. The focus of the forums at this point was no longer if Han Xiao was fake or real but why Black Star had the Mechanic Emperor's ability.

There had always been a rumor among the players about Black Star being able to replicate and imitate other characters' abilities, and this rumor was finally proven true.

The majority of the players felt that this special talent Black Star had was the key reason he could grow stronger so fast, being able to 'steal' abilities from opponents.

In some respects, the players' guess was very close to the truth. However, no matter how much they guessed, they would never know the truth.

Furthermore, as this theory lacked solid evidence, for the NPCs, it only passed between the players and was not convincing enough for normal people even if they heard about it.

As the one who single-handedly initiated this event, Fly Free became famous overnight. He was seen as the number one loyal member of the army. He expressed his intention to form a Black Star Fan Group on the spot and to communicate with the army commander about making it a team Black Star Guards with only Immortals.

The atmosphere on the forums was festive. Other than praise for Black Star, there were also many who were laughing at Winter Wolf and the others.

[Mario's Little Mushroom: Tsk, some people just can't bear to see others live a good life and will try their best to pull you back using all kinds of dirty and filthy methods, yet they're not ashamed but honored by it, acting as if it's all for everyone's own good. They're the best definition of the word 'hypocrite'.]

[Master of Bondage: Hehe, sadly for them, our army commander is wise and fair. He won't be deceived.]

However, while all this went on, the Northern Battlefront surprisingly stepped up and announced they were responsible for it. It instantly triggered a verbal war on the forums and attracted the focus of the players. That was how it should be. Compared to praising Black Star, the players were still more interested in arguing with others online.

While the forums were heated, the influence of the Black Star Cup was also fermenting in the galaxy. Army members backstabbing Black Star sparkled a lot of conversations and discussions, leading many galactic residents who were not originally interested to curiously find out about the details of the incident.

Not long after the closing ceremony ended, on behalf of the army, Han Xiao made an official announcement to the entire universe to explain this incident, answering their questions while satisfying their curiosity.

He basically publicized Fly Free's insults toward the Mechanic Emperor on that day with some exaggeration and more details so that the galactic residents could properly enjoy watching it.

At the same time, the announcement emphasized that he really hoped the Mechanic Emperor would not be angry about this. This was just someone's most sincere true opinion from the deepest part of his heart. It did not represent the army's opinion. The army would always respect the Mechanic Emperor, even if he was an evil man. At the same time, he hoped that the Mechanic Emperor would uphold his position as an elder and not take the words of such young people seriously.

The galactic residents were just happily watching on, while the Beyond Grade As who attended the event only had one thought about Han Xiao in their hearts.

Wow, you b*stard, you really have absolutely zero virtue!

We like it!

Chapter 1141: New Blueprint and World Tree Progress

Word of the Black Star Cup incident spread around the universe rapidly. Tons of insults toward Manison appeared, but Manison did not respond at all. He completely ignored Han Xiao.

The popularity of news could only last a few days usually, which was even more true in the galactic society. News about the Black Star Cup lasted for a while in after dinner conversations, then followed the pattern and gradually faded out of popularity.

However, the army elites who became famous during the Black Star Cup gained a solid reputation that did not fade away. The base members had seen more army officers. The members in various Grades were given a position on the list of the strongest individuals.

For example, among the Calamity Grade officers, Hadavy was publicly recognized as number one, and Jotina number two, and so on according to the results they achieved in the Black Star Cup. As for those who did not participate or forfeited, the public were unaware of them.

After the closing ceremony ended, Han Xiao returned to Black Star Palace to deal with all sorts of affairs and settled Destiny's Child's sub-body Rody down to carry out all kinds of studies.

Initially, he wanted to try and have 'Second Generation EsGod' Evans make an attempt to absorb Destiny's Child' sub-body, but after some pondering, he abandoned this plan.

Firstly, it was still unconfirmed whether the sub-body transformation of Destiny's Child was considered an Esper Gene awakening or a physical mutation phenomenon. Evans' Esper Ability could only target the former and not the latter.

Secondly, Destiny's Child was very mysterious, and the Information Form was a very deep and complex territory. Han Xiao was not sure if Evans would suffer from any side effects after absorbing it. He might even turn into a new sub-body, so he did not want to take the risk.

"I'd better ask the Holy Accord organization. They're the experts."

Inside the lab, Han Xiao looked at Rody, who was sleeping inside the cabin, and shook his head.

The extent of how mysterious Destiny's Child was exceeded his abilities. He was not an expert in this area. He had yet to find a way to resolve Rody's sub-body transformation. The only thing he could do for now was to use regular Information Form Restrainers to stabilize Rody's body and slow down his transformation speed as much as possible.

Han Xiao touched his chin. Speaking of which, the new date of the deal with the Holy Accord organization was quite soon. As long as he completed the trade, he would be able to freely spill the secrets of the Holy Accord without any worries.

For this, he had already operated on the Holy Light Particle in advance. After that, the Holy Light Particle had shrunk completely inside Aurora and isolated itself.

"Including the two Universal Treasure blueprints from Holy Accord, as well as two from the federation, I'll have seven Gold blueprints…"

Han Xiao opened the interface and looked at it. Some time ago, he had released the last too Beyond Grade A captives of the federation and received the bailing fee for them—two new Universal Treasure blueprints.

One was equipment for the Mechanical Deity. It was called 'Titan Spinal Center'.

The Mechanical Deity was formed by assembling countless mechanical soldiers, so it could change into any shapes or forms, basically like a pile of mechanical slime. What connected all the parts of the Mechanical Deity was Mechanical Force and special magnetic fields that acted as the neural network of the Mechanical Deity. The bigger the Mechanical Deity was, the more energy it consumed.

As the name suggested, Titan Spinal Center was a tool that acted as the body center. It would be installed inside the Mechanical Deity. Following the user's mind, it could become a full bone structure in different forms. Human forms, beast forms, and all kinds of forms included. It would support the Mechanical Deity's body. Controlling the Mechanical Deity with Mechanical Force through this device, which built a neural network for the Mechanical Deity, would largely decrease the energy cost and extend the duration one could use the Mechanical Deity.

As Universal Treasure Grade class-exclusive equipment, of course, it also provided all kinds of bonuses. The Titan Spinal Center could comprehensively enhance the basic strength of the Mechanical Deity, making it strong and faster than other Mechanical Deities of the same size. Also, it enhanced various abilities as well as the user's Machinery Affinity.

Not long ago, during the fight with Manison, Manison's Mechanical Deity that was equipped with tons of Universal Treasure Grade equipment made Han Xiao very jealous. He felt like he was like a blank piece of paper in comparison, and the Celestial Punishment Edge in his hands did not feel as powerful anymore.

Therefore, he decided to obtain more Mechanical Deity equipment, as the Mechanical Deity was the strongest trump card of Mechanics at this level. For others, it was a temporary last resort because its cost was too high, but for him and the Mechanic Emperor, they could both use it as a regular combat method. Hence, the more exclusive items the Mechanical Deity had, the better.

The other Gold blueprint was a special device called 'Mechanical Territory'. From its effects, it seemed similar to Beyoni's Land of the Fire Core and the Extinguish Army's Land of the Ice Core. It was even somewhat similar to the Evolution Cube.

This was a large device that could increase the machinery production efficiency, mechanical life form enhancement chance, machinery power output, and so on within its range. It was a territory-type equipment. To Beyond Grade A Mechanics, the best way to use it was to put it in their machinery civilization or the Dimension Factory. It was basically like the machinery version of Evolutionary Totem.

However, the requirements for building it were rather tough. The fundamental principle of this device was the Secondary Dimension Theory, by forming a territory that had special operating rules within its range like the advent of a secondary dimension. Therefore, the core material of it was the core fragment of a secondary dimension—the higher the quality, the better. Furthermore, depending on the fragment, the product would also possess a small part of the secondary dimension's special traits.

There were countless unstable new secondary dimensions born every day, so core fragments were by no means in shortage. The only problem was the harvesting of it since the dimension might collapse after its core fragment was taken. Nonetheless, with money, these were all non-issues.

Han Xiao had an Evil Convergence core fragment in his hands, so he could use it on this.

"Two new blueprints, both with quite good effects. Most importantly, after I successfully build the finished products, I'll be able to get two more God's Trait Transformation Points… In addition to the deal with Holy Accord, I'll obtain four in total."

Han Xiao was excited and almost wanted to immediately isolate himself inside the factory for days on end.

Beep beep!

At this time, his communicator rang.

It was surprisingly a call from the dynasty's Exploration Army Commander, brother Tarrokov.

"What's up, Old Tar?" Han Xiao glanced at him and went back to what he was doing. The two of them were very close, so there was no need to be formal.

"I've got some news regarding what you previously asked me to ask around about," Tarrokov said.

Han Xiao's movements paused.

Not long ago when the two of them chatted, he had asked Tarrokov to ask around the dynasty's science institute about their progress on the study of the wormhole coordinates EsGod left behind. He was worried that that was the trigger to Aesop's prophecy.

"What about it?"

"They have made several breakthroughs." Tarrokov's answer made Han Xiao's heart skip a bit.

"… Any details?"

"They've already confirmed which area this wormhole coordinates led to in the unexplored universe, but they have yet to find the accurate location, only a rough range."

Hu, so they did not fully discover the World Tree or get discovered by the World Tree. That's still fine.

Han Xiao was secretly relieved but also troubled.

The later the three Universal Civilizations came into contact with the World Tree Civilization, the better it would be for him. This was his biggest wish at this point.

He did not dare expose the existence of the World Tree Civilization because given the three Universal Civilizations' character, once they knew there was a powerful civilization in the unexplored universe, they would undoubtedly make contact with it actively and prepare for it in advance.

Emphasizing the danger of the World Tree Civilization would not work either, and explaining why he knew the details was not even the biggest problem. The problem was that the three Universal Civilizations might become more cautious and wary because of his reminder, but they would certainly not give up making contact. If they knew that there was a dangerous advanced civilization in the unexplored universe, they would not wait till the other side found them but would surely attack first.

Therefore, no matter how he leaked any accurate information about the World Tree Civilization and what method he used, it would only make the time when the two sides made contact come sooner.

EsGod was already sealed, so no one but him knew anything about the World Tree in the explored universe. He was the only one who could influence the World Tree version's overall path, and he had to be cautious.

"How did the dynasty react to this?"

Unsuspecting, Tarrokov said, "The upper echelons did not react to it much. The study project of these wormhole coordinates isn't a secret, which is why I could ask around about it in the first place… EsGod has been captured for decades. He's already in the past. Most of the studies about him are not important right now."

"Then, what does the science institute plan to do?"

"Continue to search for the accurate coordinates, of course. Although we don't know why EsGod treated this set of coordinates so importantly, the science institute will most likely do what was already done before. They will try to activate a wormhole with a fixed coordinate, throw a few detectors over, and wait for the results to come back."

Han Xiao hesitated before subtly saying, "I think that this kind of study should be stopped temporarily. The unexplored universe is full of danger, so no one knows what they'll find there. Now is the crucial time when the three Universal Civilizations are competing with the Super Star Cluster Alliance. If an incident similar to the Intelligent Plague happens again, it's going to be very bad for the dynasty."

Tarrokov looked at Han Xiao suspiciously and said, "Everything you said is filled with concern about this project. Do you know something?"

"If I say it's my intuition, will you believe me?"

"Hehe." Tarrokov fake laughed, expressing he was absolutely not convinced, then continued casually. "I'll pass on your suggestion. As for whether they listen to it, it doesn't have anything to do with me."

"That'll be enough."

"Alright, I'll go do my things then. Also, don't forget to attend the three Universal Civilizations' award ceremony in two months' time."

"Hmm."

Han Xiao nodded, turned off the communication, and Tarrokov's remote projection disappeared.

After a short pause, he gave the order to the team escorting the Holy Light Particle that they could depart now and head to the agreed location to carry out the deal with the Holy Accord. It was located in the free competition zone of the Flickering World.

…

"The day of the deal is about to arrive."

Inside a certain secret base of the Holy Accord organization, Oathkeeper opened his eyes and looked at the officers below him.

"Was the emissary carrying out the deal dispatched?"

"He was sent out long ago, absolutely loyal and reliable."

"I don't just want loyalty but also capability. I know Virtual Mechanics all too well. Black Star will certainly use the opportunity to attempt to track us, so we must be prepared. Has the emissary's escape route been prepared properly?"

"The Black Star Army's forces are too powerful in the Flickering World, so it's not suitable to spark any conflict. We've already equipped the emissary with Information Form Invisibility Coating. As soon as he gets his hands on the item, he'll activate the coating and evaporate from the spot."

"What about the guards?"

"There are guards but not many, only to prevent accidents from happening on the way there… After all, any number of guards will be meaningless in the Black Star Army's territory."

"Hmm… not bad." Oathkeeper nodded with satisfaction and said, "As long as the Holy Light Particle is acquired, we can start to fuse the Third Sanctum Key and start the preparations for the awakening ceremony. Therefore, after we complete the deal, we'll fully enter 'The Darkest Time' and completely cut off any of our connections with the outside world… I'll meet Black Star one more time after the deal is completed, probably for the last time. There most likely won't be any need for us to cross paths in the future."

"Understood!"

Hearing the subordinates' response, Oathkeeper grunted and started daydreaming.

Honestly, if not for the deal, he did not even want to see Black Star's face.

Even till now, he was still confused about who leaked their information. Did the spy or traitor exist at all?

Chapter 1142: Flawless Deduction

The deal location agreed by Han Xiao and Oathkeeper was a certain transit station planet in the Flickering World's Dawn Star Cluster.

Feidin was appointed as the deal emissary, representing the army to wait and meet with the Holy Accord organization's emissary there. The entire process would be monitored by Han Xiao from the headquarters.

Oathkeeper had also used spiritual projection long ago to meet with Han Xiao. The two of them both maintained communication to ensure that this deal would be carried out smoothly, clearly showing sincerity.

Inside the office, a virtual screen hovered on the table and played the footage from the surveillance camera. Inside the footage was a prosperous area with a lot of people. Feidin stood beside the wall of a building wearing a mask, looking at the pedestrians passing by. The Holy Accord emissary had yet to arrive at the designated location.

"When will your man arrive? We've been waiting for almost two hours." Han Xiao leaned back in his seat and looked at the screen with boredom.

"Soon."

"You've said that seven times already."

"… Really soon this time."

A while after, a man also in disguise finally appeared on the screen carrying a silver alloy suitcase. He walked right toward Feidin.

The two of them met, but neither carried on to the next step.

"Is he the emissary?" Han Xiao asked.

"That's right. What you want's in the suitcase."

Han Xiao nodded, contacted Feidin, and told him to exchange the item. Oathkeeper also used his ability to give the same order.

The two people on the screen received the order and exchanged the items right away, then backed off a few steps to check them.

An armor suddenly appeared on Feidin's body, shrouding both him and the suitcase. The next moment, with a flash of light, he disappeared right on the spot and suddenly appeared in Han Xiao's office.

"Here's the stuff."

The armor opened up, and Feidin placed the suitcase on Han Xiao's table.

This was the King mechanical suit Han Xiao had temporarily lent to Feidin. The Throne was in his hands to ensure he would take the item right after the deal was completed.

Han Xiao opened the suitcase, and cold air flew out. Inside were two cylindrical containers that contained two clusters of Primal Esper Ability Entities. One was green, and the other was blue.

There was also a data storage device beside the two containers. Han Xiao turned it on and looked at it. It stored the data for two Gold blueprints. Everything Oathkeeper had promised in the deal was there.

This time, a notification also popped up on the interface.

_____________________

Primal Esper Ability Entities Acquired: 4/4

[Primal Esper Ability Collector] Milestone requirements met.

Effects: When you fight Espers, all your attributes will increase slightly. -12% to 20% damage received from Espers.

You have received 1 [The Third Sanctum] Ability Fragment.

_____________________

The mission is completed, which means these two were real.

Han Xiao was relieved. He waved at Feidin.

"Go back."

The three-minute duration had yet to end. He activated the King again and sent Feidin back to the location of the deal.

Oathkeeper turned and looked over. "Black Star, how is it?"

"Hmm, there are no problems. What about you?"

"What you gave me was indeed part of the Holy Light Particle."

Han Xiao raised his brows and extended his hand.

"So… nice deal?"

Although Oathkeeper's spiritual projection had no physical form, he still made the gesture to shake Han Xiao's hands and said, "Nice deal."

The next moment, the Holy Accord emissary on the screen seemed to have activated some device and disappeared all of a sudden.

"Oh? Your man fled really quick. Are you that worried about me?" Han Xiao asked with a joking tone.

"Caution is a necessity." Oathkeeper did not deny it.

Seeing that his emissary had followed the plan strictly and left the scene, Oathkeeper finally heaved a sigh of relief and relaxed his tense nerves.

This deal was extremely important for the Holy Accord, and he was worried about a lot of things. Most importantly, he was worried about Black Star not fulfilling their agreement and attempting to chase the Holy Accord emissary by any means necessary. Now it looked like Black Star had no such plan, and the deal was carried out smoothly.

With the Holy Light Particle, the success rate of opening the Third Sanctum would basically reach their expected percentage.

Oathkeeper suppressed his excitement and said, "I will remember Your Excellency Black Star's generosity. Since the deal is complete, it's time for me to leave."

Every time he made contact with people like Black Star, it was a risk. The more he spoke, the more information he might leak.

Luckily, there was no need to ever make contact with Black Star anymore in the future. All Oathkeeper wanted to do now was immediately turn off the spiritual projection and never meet Han Xiao ever again.

Since Oathkeeper had always contacted Han Xiao using the method of spiritual projection, this meant that only he could contact Black Star while Black Star could not contact him. As long as he never contacted Black Star ever again, Black Star would never have the chance to see him in the future.

At this time, Han Xiao suddenly smiled and said, "Don't be in such a rush. Who knows when we will meet again? Let's chat for a while. Also, I have some questions I'd like to ask you before you leave."

Oathkeeper's heart skipped a beat.

Oh, come on, why do you have questions again?

You asking questions make me panic, every time!

Oathkeeper tried to be patient and said with a cautious tone, "… Ask on then. I'll answer as much as possible."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes and smiled faintly.

Just like Oathkeeper, he had nothing to worry about now that he already had what he wanted from the deal.

After he acted like he was pondering for a few seconds, he decided to start from the questions that would probably shock Oathkeeper the least.

"Do you… know about Destiny's Child?"

Oathkeeper's eyes turned around, and his entire body became stiff.

Animal! What have you discovered again‽

He started into Han Xiao's eyes, hoping to figure out what he was thinking. However, Black Star's clear eyes were filled with sincerity, as if he was really just asking casually.

Unable to calm his emotions down, Oathkeeper suppressed his shock and asked, "Why are you suddenly asking me? Did something happen?"

"Well, there's no need to hide it really. I once met a special individual who called himself Destiny's Child. Sadly, he died in a nuclear explosion. Then, not long ago, I came across a similar individual. After some investigations, I discovered that there seems to be a Primal Esper Ability called Destiny's Child that exists in the universe. It seems to be able to transform some life forms into special sub-bodies. You guys happen to be the experts in studying Primal Esper Abilities, so I came to consult you."

"That's it?"

"What else? But from the way you reacted, your Holy Accord organization seems to know quite a lot of things." Han Xiao sized Oathkeeper up and wondered, "Could it be that Destiny's Child is in your hands? The way your emissary disappeared earlier does seem similar to Information Form-related technology. That was invented by you guys too, wasn't it?"

Oathkeeper was having a headache. He regretted his overreaction earlier. It was like he was infected with Black Star PTSD.

"It's not, nonsense."

"Really?"

"Nope." Oathkeeper denied it completely.

"Alright then, I don't really care if it's in your hands I just want to know some information. You guys specialize in studying Primal Esper Ability Entities, so you guys definitely know something, or you wouldn't have asked me back earlier." Han Xiao tapped on the table, his tone casual.

He looked like he believed what Oathkeeper said, but actually, he was about sixty percent sure that Destiny's Child was in the Holy Accord's hands from Oathkeeper's reaction. Nonetheless, Oathkeeper would certainly not admit to it, so the Great Mechanic Han decided to not continue asking. The most important thing was to ask about the mechanisms of Destiny's Child.

Oathkeeper pondered with resignation, selected some information, and said, "Destiny's Child is a very ancient Primal Esper Ability. We don't know much about it either. Most of what we know came from the other Primal Esper Ability Entities. It's said that Destiny's Child's ability is related to the changes of Information Form and strings of fate, and it has an unbelievably powerful foresight ability.

"Strings of fate are also called 'cause and effect' in some cultures. Like a huge net, if you touch one of the strings, the vibrations will certainly pass onto more strings. Therefore, every time it uses its ability, Destiny's Child will have to read a lot of information and carry out an analyzing process similar to computing large groups of data. It is able to calculate the various possibilities and results that a certain event can produce, then use that to foresee the future.

"In this process, in order to read the so-called strings of fate, it will release special Information Form particles to collect information, and these particles will often cause information state disturbances. They will produce partial projections of themselves in random information bodies, take over part of their information, and that is how the sub-bodies are born. The targets are mostly life forms.

"Some Primal Esper Ability Entities say that Destiny's Child can turn into a High Dimensional Information Form. If it doesn't want to be discovered, no one can discover it. That is why no one had been able to capture it even till now… Therefore, you having met two sub-bodies is purely because you were lucky."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled, and his thoughts spun quickly.

The information of Destiny's Child Oathkeeper provided was almost identical to the mechanisms he had speculated it would have. However, he felt that Destiny's Child's ability did not stop there.

Just foresight? Probably not!

Since Destiny's Child could produce sub-bodies, could it produce something else? Or even change the direction the strings of fate would take? There were many forms of the so-called 'information state disturbance', even physical mirages. Han Xiao did not forget how the Domino Virus that caused the Intelligent Plague appeared.

In Version 1.0, the information he obtained from the Germinal Organization said that the ability of their Destiny's Child was 'influence' over the future, not just 'foreseeing' the future. Han Xiao once thought it was only because the natives were not knowledgeable enough, but now that he thought about it, that might not have been a misunderstanding.

Han Xiao asked a few more questions, to which Oathkeeper said he did not know, clearly not willing to expose more information.

Seeing this, Han Xiao had no choice but to change the topic. He narrowed his eyes and casually said, "By the way, last time you told me about how your spiritual projection ability works. After that, I did some research. There seems to be a Primal Esper Ability called Soul Flame that fits what you said."

Hearing this, it seemed like this was no secret. Oathkeeper surprisingly nodded and said directly, "That's right. I'm the master of Soul Flame."

"Hmm, I did some further research following this information, and it seems like the last Soul Flame master in the universe was a Beyond Grade A Esper nicknamed Soul Emperor. His name was Rovell Sissock… Do you happen to know him?"

Then, Han Xiao stared closely at Oathkeeper, wanting to see every slight reaction he had.

However, Oathkeeper did not look surprised at all this time and said, "I've heard about him too, but I don't know him."

Han Xiao frowned in his mind. Unlike the question about Destiny's Child, Oathkeeper did not have any strange reaction to this question.

He did not know if this was because Oathkeeper was completely mentally prepared about it, or Oathkeeper did not care about his identity being exposed, or he guessed wrong and Oathkeeper was not that Soul Emperor who might have faked his own death.

Han Xiao then asked, "Since Soul Flame once spent time with this master, it must know more. Help me ask it then…"

Han Xiao felt weird as soon as he asked this. It sounded like asking a man to ask his current girlfriend about how her ex-boyfriend was.

"About what?" Oathkeeper did not agree nor disagree.

"Hmm, I'm very curious about after Soul Emperor died, who took Soul Flame, and how did you obtain it?"

Oathkeeper's tone became slightly more serious, and he said, "Don't you think these questions are too personal?"

"As a man of science, is it wrong for me to be curious?" Han Xiao used a very justifiable excuse.

Oathkeeper shook his head with resignation and said, "Alright, I know you're curious about who I am, and you think I'm Soul Emperor or one of the Beyond Grade As who killed Soul Emperor back then and took Soul Flame. But you've guessed wrong. I'm none of them. I did not rob Soul Flame from anyone. When I met it, it was already free, and it took me some effort to acquire it."

"Then can you help me to ask it, what did it experience after Soul Emperor died?" Han Xiao then asked.

"…It's not willing to say." Oathkeeper shook his head. He suddenly paused for a moment before saying, "However, it told me that Soul Emperor did not die in battle. Since you've already looked at information about him, I won't go into detail. Anyway, during Soul Emperor's last battle, his body was indeed destroyed. However, due to the specialty of his Esper Ability, his soul did not die and escaped. As for where he went, Soul Flame has no idea either."

Han Xiao pondered.

He did not know if what Oathkeeper was true, but from his tone and the content, it did not seem like a lie.

In Han Xiao's previous life, Soul Emperor did not revive, which meant that there was a very high possibility he was still alive. If Oathkeeper was not Soul Emperor, then who was? Could it be that he had run into the secondary dimensions and was never able to come back?

"Do you have any other questions? If not, I shall leave."

Oathkeeper was getting impatient.

He did not want to continue chatting with Han Xiao. He had more important things to do now. All his mind was focused on the awakening ceremony. The promise of many years was finally going to be fulfilled, so he did not want to wait another second.

To him, chatting with Han Xiao for a while was already very respectful, or he would have directly deactivated the projection and left right after the deal was complete. He would never come into contact with him again in the future anyway, so he did not mind being rude.

"Alright, you do indeed have more important things to do. I won't delay you." Han Xiao stood up, did a farewell gesture, and deliberately sighed. "Sigh, buddy, I have quite a good impression of you. After you leave this time, god knows when you'll contact me again. I won't say much. When you revive the Primordial Ones, remember to send my regards to them."

Oathkeeper's movement to deactivate the spiritual projection stiffened in an instant.

The entire spiritual projection suddenly trembled like radio noise, which represented the extreme emotional turbulence Oathkeeper was going through.

The sudden shock made Oathkeeper's spiritual frequency lose balance, so much so that he suddenly lost full control of his ability!

He opened his eyes wide with disbelief.

How can you possibly know about our top secret‽

I have already investigated all the upper echelons. There are no spies at all!

When this thought appeared, Oathkeeper was suddenly stunned.

Wait, I've fallen into a thinking blind spot. There's actually one upper echelon left who has not been investigated!

Someone once said, when you have eliminated all possibilities, no matter how unbelievable and impossible the last possibility is, that's the truth.

Therefore…

Am I the spy‽

Oathkeeper's brain exploded.

Chapter 1143: Purpose and Partnership

"H-how did you…"

Oathkeeper's heart was heavily shocked, and his mind was in a bit of a trance. He was filled with questions.

Black Star definitely knew this secret all along but had been hiding it, and I was totally fooled.

This b*stard is so evil!

Seeing Oathkeeper was appalled, Han Xiao looked surprised. "Hmm? Why are you still here? Weren't you leaving?"

"I…"

"I know you don't want to leave me, but since you're in such a hurry, you'd better go back quickly."

"Act—Actually, I'm not in that much of a hurry. We can chat for a while… a while more…"

Oathkeeper laughed awkwardly.

This dog is definitely doing this purposely! How can I leave before I find out the whole truth‽

Han Xiao's words made Oathkeeper immediately give up on wanting to leave as soon as possible. Instead, he insisted on staying and making sure his questions were answered.

"Since you're so enthusiastic, it'll be rude for me to refuse you then."

Seeing that Oathkeeper looked emotionally unstable, Han Xiao stopped kidding and invited him back to his seat.

Oathkeeper took a deep breath and cautiously asked, "So you know about our goal. Where did you hear about it?"

Black Star directly pointed out the Holy Accord's purpose, so he knew that there was no point in hiding it anymore. Furthermore, he felt that Black Star definitely had a motive, or he could have hidden the fact that he knew about this. Deliberately exposing their goal did not seem like something an enemy would do. He wondered what Black Star was planning.

"I have my intelligence channels." Han Xiao gave a perfunctory answer, clearly expressing that he would never reveal his sources.

Oathkeeper did not hold any hopes for it anyway. If he was in Black Star's position, he would not expose who the spy was either. Oathkeeper had no choice but to clench his teeth and accept that. He said, "Since you already know our goal, what are you planning?"

He put himself at the lower position, which he had not done in a very long time. If he was facing an ordinary Beyond Grade A, Oathkeeper would most likely have thought of killing him. However, facing Black Star, he really did not have complete confidence he would be able to—Black Star was too damn tanky.

On the other hand, if Black Star wanted to, he could leak this intelligence out any time he wanted. Since his weakness was in Black Star's hands, he had to be cautious.

"What do you think I'm planning?" Han Xiao smiled faintly.

"I don't know." Oathkeeper had several guesses, but he did not dare to say them out loud.

From the way he looked at it, there were only a few reasons Black Star would do this, including extortion or interrupting. It was not like Black Star only did this to scare him out of boredom… right?

"Why not take a guess?"

"… I have no guesses."

"Tsk, you're so boring." Han Xiao shook his finger. "Why are you so nervous? Since I did not reject your deal, don't you understand my stance?"

Oathkeeper's eyes flickered. "You're saying… you don't plan to stop us?"

"Why should I?" Han Xiao crossed his arms, narrowed his eyes, and said, "I'm the leader of the Black Star Army and the three Universal Civilizations' Special Consultant, but I'm also the vice president of the Beyond Grade A Association. If you'd paid attention to the Meeting of the Gods a few years ago, you'd know that the Mechanic Emperor and I have come to an agreement…"

Oathkeeper hastily thought back. Suddenly, a flash of insight passed through his mind and cleared the fog.

"You're saying… there are too few Beyond Grade As?"

"That's right. The Mechanic Emperor and I both said that. Now you understand." Han Xiao smiled.

Oathkeeper suddenly felt that everything made sense now, and most of his questions got answered.

No wonder despite knowing our goal, Black Star still chose to let it happen. This might be the only chance of tremendously strengthening the Beyond Grade A level in the short run, so it fits his goal.

However, Oathkeeper still had some questions.

"I thought you were on the side of the three Universal Civilizations. I didn't think you'd do this."

"That's just because of the promotions recently. Of course, in terms of overall stand, I'm on the same side as the three Universal Civilizations, but that doesn't mean I've become their vassal. I stand against Mechanic Emperor only because his methods are too radical, but we both have the same wish for the total number of Beyond Grade As."

"So, you plan to work with us on a deeper level?"

"That's right. I won't stop you from executing your plan, but I have my demands too. I hope that the Beyond Grade As you revive will all be on my side."

Oathkeeper nodded before shaking his head. "This isn't that simple. They all have their own minds. Even if I'm the one who revives them, they won't become my puppets."

"By the way, I've always wondered, why do you guys want to revive the already dead Beyond Grade As?" Han Xiao asked.

He had been curious about this question in his previous life. Logically speaking, the Holy Accord organization should have been very ambitious since they revived so many extremely strong individuals. However, the Holy Accord and the Revivors only appeared to fight the World Tree Civilization during the World Tree war, and they seemed to appear just because they had no choice. God only knew what they were doing before.

As for that group of Beyond Grade As who were revived during the Calamity of the Supers, he was still unsure whether they also came from the Holy Accord.

"Because of a promise, an oath…" Oathkeeper's voice became low and spoke in a storytelling tone.

"Tell me about it." Han Xiao was very curious.

Oathkeeper stayed silent for a moment, seemingly hesitating over whether he should leak more information. Then, he thought of his position, and he had no choice but to slowly explain.

"The Holy Accord was founded toward the end of the exploration era by some of the Primordial Ones. Our purpose is to revive those who died in the war… Although when we talk about that history now, we say it quite casually, but Black Star, you should understand the frustration of the Primordial One. They spent their lifetime breaking through the limits of individual strength, only to be used as new tools of war, killing each other, dying one after another.

"Even if they did not want to take part in the war, the unstoppable tide of the era still dragged them in. You can do some research. How many Primordial Ones met a good end?

"At the same time, because we've evolved to a new level, countless people envied us, feared us. You know what it's like. When an individual becomes too powerful, the masses will surely be wary about the individual. This has never changed… We're just the extreme minority in the universe who are both admired and feared.

"Among the Primordial Ones, some regretted being born in the chaotic war era and hoped to go to the prosperous peaceful era, but they were limited by their life span. Some regretted dying in the war. Even after they were scarified, they tried to be reborn in the future. Therefore, many people started to look for ways to revive them secretly, and these people were separated into different factions.

"Some of those people created the Holy Accord organization, and that's our origin, also our promise…"

"I see…" Han Xiao started pondering.

He could understand why the Primordial Ones hoped to get through the exploration era using the method of getting revived in the future—they had reached the absolute peak of individual strength in the galaxy, yet they had become mere tools of war. At that time, there was no room for Beyond Grade A organizations. Other than the extremely few exceptions, most of them could only become the warriors of civilizations; maintaining a neutral stance was an extravagant wish. Anyone would feel frustrated in their position.

Furthermore, as the Beyond Grade As had just appeared, no civilization did not want to study them further. The environment the Primordial Ones were in was extremely harsh, far less free, safe, and comfortable compared to the modern Beyond Grade As.

The Primordial Ones had thought of all sorts of ways of reviving, and the Underworld might have been one of them, but very few chose to use that method. After all, not everyone was willing to become a subordinate of the sisters who were the former owners of the Underworld, and they were not that reliable either.

No wonder Onicelu said that the two sisters were once invited to take part in a plan related to the Sanctums that probably had something to do with the Holy Accord organization. However, the two sisters rejected it; they did not seem to want to be revived.

Han Xiao caressed his chin and pondered. "So, how do you plan to revive those Beyond Grade As?"

"I-I can't tell you that." Oathkeeper shook his head.

Han Xiao said with a dissatisfied tone, "Humph, I can guess even if you don't say it. It probably has something to do with the Sanctums. Come on, I've already made my stance clear. Show some sincerity."

Oathkeeper hesitated for a while before nodding solemnly. "Yes, it's the Sanctums. I really can't go into further details now. After I fulfil the promise, I'll share the method with you."

Han Xiao curled his lips and changed the topic.

"Then let's talk about our partnership. I can provide convenience for your plan and keep it a secret for you, and you will have to give me some things in return…"

Han Xiao then stated his requirements. Resources and intelligence were not the most important. What he mainly wanted to obtain was the way to revive the dead through the Sanctums, as well as a part of the special technology the Holy Accord organization had, while at the same time being on the good side of these Revivors.

Whether Oathkeeper was willing or not, he had no choice but to trust Han Xiao and accept him as a partner. Otherwise, if Han Xiao leaked any of their secrets, there would be even more trouble.

Oathkeeper had no certainty that Black Star had no ulterior motives, but he was not to be trifled with either. He did not want to fight now, but he would not be afraid to fight if he had to.

The two of them negotiated for a while and settled on the partnership agreement. Oathkeeper had no choice but to leave a stable communication channel so that Black Star could contact him anytime and not just wait for him to contact him.

After all this was complete, Oathkeeper went offline with a belly full of questions. He might have to see a therapist after he returned.

Han Xiao stayed in the office, crossed his legs, caressed his chin, and pondered.

Everything he told Oathkeeper was true but not the whole truth. He did indeed want to increase the number of Beyond Grade As. One reason for that was to make the Beyond Grade As' position more important across the universe while increasing his position in the association, and another was to deal with the World Tree. Aesop's prophecy and the progress of the dynasty's Science Institute led to him having no choice but to prepare in advance and find more helpers.

At the same time, he was also very curious about how the Holy Accord revived the Primordial Ones and wanted to find out more about the Sanctums' functions. Furthermore, he did not wish for the Holy Accord organization and a group of Beyond Grade As to hide out of sight. He suggested this partnership to have a stable means of contacting them, so he could monitor what they were doing.

The last motive was that the Great Mechanic Han wanted to try triggering a mission. He felt that the chance of that was quite high.

And as he expected, a notification did pop up on the interface.

You have triggered the hidden mission [Return to the History Stage]!

Mission Introduction: You found out from Oathkeeper that the Holy Accord organization's goal is to revive some of the Beyond Grade As who've died in history. You have chosen to work with Oathkeeper.

Mission Requirements: Assist the Holy Accord organization to successfully complete their awakening plan.

Reward: +25 Favorability of all the revived Beyond Grade As, +1 Legendary Point.

Remarks: This mission is a Series Origin Mission. Once accepted, you will have a higher chance of triggering more hidden missions in the same series.

"Series Origin Mission, meaning this mission is the entry point to a storyline… makes sense. If I did not work with the Holy Accord, what happens afterward would have nothing to do with me."

Han Xiao accepted the mission without hesitation.

He had a feeling that this series mission might be related to many version main storylines.

…

In a certain secret base of the Holy Accord organization, Oathkeeper retrieved his spiritual projection and took a long breath. He was still a little stunned, digesting what had just happened.

Law and Fay were standing below and saw Oathkeeper's expression.

"Boss, how was it?"

"Did Black Star complete the deal, or did he change his mind?"

Oathkeeper regained focus, straightened his facial expression, and said reluctantly, "From now on, Black Star is temporarily our ally."

Law and Fay's eyes widened with confusion.

What happened? Why so sudden?

The Holy Accord organization has never had a partner. This is the first!

Wasn't this just a simple trade? Why have Black Star suddenly become our ally?

We've heard a lot of Black Star's excellent skills in making friends. Did the boss fall to him too‽

Chapter 1144: Butterfly: Can You Not Make Me Flap My Wings Every Day?

In the dedicated factory for the Army Commander in Black Star Palace, Han Xiao walked in with a suitcase, placing it on the table. He opened the lid with a click, taking out the two cylindrical containers containing the Primal Esper Ability Entities, and held them in his hands.

The emerald green Primal Ability was sticky in texture like a liquid, whereas the sky blue Primal Ability was like a cloud of light mist with icy debris.

The emerald green one was known as 'Natural Spirit Power', which could control various plants and greatly accelerated their growth. It could also call on beasts and possessed various powers of nature, just like a druid. Its frontal combat capability was slightly weaker, but it could extract and synthesize toxins from a variety of plants, which was good for research. The Holy Accord had utilized this ability to cultivate various magical plants and toxins.

The sky-blue entity was named 'Frost Authority', which not only allowed it to manipulate the cold but could also temporarily turn ice and snow into ice golem warriors like a Magic Colossus. It could also produce ice armors and weapons, move with the frigid winds, spreading death through the lack of heat… It was said that a sufficiently powerful host could even allow it to freeze molecular motion for a short amount of time, creating the effect of freezing time and space.

These two abilities are actually pretty good. After all, they're composite Primal Esper Abilities, but their effect is second. The main thing is to activate my milestone, Han Xiao thought to himself.

The [Primal Esper Ability Collector] milestone allowed him to be strengthened when facing an Esper, allowing him to gain innate advantages. The effect was impressive.

As for [The Third Sanctum] fragments rewarded by the mission. While it seemed useless at the moment, Han Xiao felt that they would come into handy after he obtained the method to open the sanctum from the Holy Accord.

Who should I hand these abilities to?

Han Xiao searched his mind for candidates.

The first choice should be to give it to Evans, as with his talent, he should be able to ignore the issue of adaptability like EsGod and easily master the Esper Abilities.

However, thinking about it, Han Xiao rejected this idea. Right now, Evans' first mission would be to level himself up and develop his own combat style through absorbing various abilities. If he gave Evans the two Primal Esper Abilities, he would not have any energy to concentrate on his research.

Moreover, with Evans' current level, he had no chance to fight, and the Primal Esper Ability would only be used for display.

I should first look for a suitable host among the officers of the army. The last resort should be Evans.

Putting away the two Primal Abilities, Han Xiao opened the data storage and took out the two Gold Grade blueprints that the Holy Accord had given him to look through.

The blueprints provided by the Holy Accord were all relatively old technology, which were likely to have been preserved from the exploration era and not improved on much. One of the blueprints was called 'Psionic Obelisk', which had the effect of energy conversion and formation of energy barriers. What separated it from general psionic shields was that it had an extraordinary resistance to energy attacks and could absorb a portion of damage to restore its shield durability.

But this was only its basic function. The core function of the Psionic Obelisk was to provide a large field of energy that could be borrowed at will without a transmission pipeline. In simple terms, this item could increase the energy concentration of an area to become denser and more active.

Thus, this Psionic Obelisk was equivalent to a magic weapon which could increase the aura concentration of a place, similar to man-made blessings.

Because the Obelisk provided free energy that could be borrowed without any restrictions, it would be no different from what the surface civilization deemed as sacred objects or wonders. The extremely active energy factor would allow individuals to have more ways to utilize energy and also a higher probability of giving rise to other super systems. At the same time, obtaining a large-scale infusion from the obelisk could result in temporary transformations, allowing an ordinary person to possess combat power.

The effect of the Psionic Obelisk could be said to be somewhat similar to the Evolutionary Totem, but their focus was different. The former focuses on increasing the overall energy concentration within the area, while the latter focused on optimizing the genes of the individual. Comparing the two, the Evolutionary Totem was rarer.

But this little toy still had its uses. Putting it in each base of the army could improve the training efficiency of the members, spawning more powerful players and at the same time allowing him to sell it for his business. Even if the sales volume might not match up to the Evolutionary Totem, it would still be a good cornucopia.

Because the Holy Accord paid attention to its secrecy, they did not sell their Psionic Obelisks. All of these blueprints were merely accumulating dust in the warehouse. They were not good at mechanical technology, and since they made most of their money through their Esper Ability technology, they chose to provide Black Star with a path to fortune.

In actual fact, the blueprint that the Holy Accord wanted to take out was not this one. Oathkeeper, however, felt that Black Star was an unfathomable person, so he changed it to a better blueprint in hopes that it would serve as a 'protection fee' of some sort.

The other blueprint was named Getta Hadoken. While it sounded like a pugilist technique, it was actually a sort of compounded attack device.

This device required a combination of the Armed and Energy Branches. It had a complete set of complex equipment, but it was not assembled together like a firearm, scattered instead like an external carrier. Through special methods of energy gathering, compression, and transformation, this would launch a powerful attack, and the issued attack was known as 'Getta Hadoken'.

This equipment was also not a one-trick pony. According to the different operating routes of the device, the Getta Hadoken had many variations, including close, medium, and long ranged combat. Dozens of supporting operation routes were recorded in the blueprint, each operation route representing a method of attack. Each of them had their own unique names with the same prefix of 'Getta'.

"Rather than calling it a blueprint, this thing seems more like a pugilist manual for Mechanics. It seems like this is best suited for Mechanical Pugilists."

Han Xiao scratched his head.

With the Psionic Obelisk and Getta Hadoken being added to the other Gold grade blueprints Titan Spinal Center and Mechanical Territory obtained from the Federation, he finally obtained everything he was owed.

With the blueprints in hand, the next thing to do was to turn them into real objects.

"The public commendation ceremony for the three Universal Civilizations is about two months away. It's a good time to seclude myself and produce the four finished products, obtaining more God's Trait Transformation points… I've been in the limelight too much recently. It's better for me to stay low-key for a short period of time, to digest my influence and stabilize the reputation."

Han Xiao made up his mind, gearing up and hurriedly entering his manufacturing state.

…

In one of the secret training bases in the Crimson Dynasty, a group of officers were operating equipment in a room full of instruments. One of the walls of the room was a huge transparent viewing window. Two of the senior officers were standing in front of the viewing window; one of them was the supervisor of the base, and the other was the drill sergeant.

The two of them looked down the window, to see an inverted pyramid-like space below. A man was seated at the deepest point hundreds of meters down, releasing strong energy fluctuations and glowing energy particles. It spread around the walls before gathering back on top and falling back down, forming a cycle.

This was a special training facility for Supers that could improve the efficiency of their cultivation. At this time, the person within the facility was Gaud, and the instrument room was actually the monitoring room. The operators present were all paying attention to the energy fluctuations readings of Gaud.

"His progress is fast. This is a good seed." The drill sergeant stared down at the silhouette below as he nodded in satisfaction.

"That's right. He's the most likely talent to reach Beyond Grade A in his class. Not only does he have potential, but his own abilities are extremely powerful. Maybe one day he'll take on the position of Lord Clotti," the base supervisor praised.

"Black Star is still in line. It won't be his turn that soon."

"I'm just guessing, and besides, Black Star is not of direct descent."

The two of them conversed softly.

Gaud had already been training for many years, and he was making rapid progress. All sorts of barriers were easily passed, as though he had no bottlenecks. This sublimation in his life level in such a radical way was obviously dangerous, but he gave people the feeling that he was extremely familiar with this path.

In the eyes of both of them, even if Gaud's talent was not as good as Black Star, who had broken all records, he was not too far off.

The drill sergeant gazed at the instrument's readings, before exclaiming in amazement, "At this rate, I estimate he'll enter the Beyond Grade A realm in two to eight years. This is the most efficient person I've seen… if we exclude Black Star."

"It seems like we're witnessing yet another rise of a Beyond Grade A." The supervisor laughed, "The upper echelons have already sent down people twice. It seems like they're very concerned with the progress of Gaud."

It was a feat to be able to cultivate a Beyond Grade A of direct descent, so as long as Gaud completed his promotion, the supervisor would also experience a 'promotion'

After idly chatting a bit more, both men went back to work topics.

"Has the list of new trainees this semester been compiled?" the drill sergeant asked.

"It's been completed. I was preparing to hand it to you." The base supervisor called up a virtual screen to show a list.

This secret training base would select talents from the dynasty for a targeted training every once in a while. If there was potential, the dynasty did not mind raising even an infant all the way to the Calamity Grade, branding them a direct descent of the dynasty. Thus, they not only recruited Calamity Grades but also divided them based on different ranks and classes according to their Grade.

The lower their grade, the more intense the competition. In Grades below the Calamity Grade, there existed an implementation system. Either one passed the assessment, or they would pack up and return to the army.

If you cannot make it, then leave. Don't continue to occupy the pit even if you cannot sh*t.

The name list was quite long, and every one of them was accompanied by a resume and record. There were countless people with varying honors; they were the elites of each fleet.

The drill sergeant looked carefully, and when he came toward the end, he was taken aback. He saw that among the group of elites with gorgeous resumes, there was a person with almost no merits on his resume, and his bearing in his photos gave off a silly air without any class.

"Karlot? Where did this guy come from? Why would the top pick a completely ordinary fellow to come in?"

The drill sergeant had an expression of befuddlement, even scrutinizing Karlot's resume, but the whole thing basically screamed 'ordinary'.

While this secret training base did not only recruit elite students, they had to have some characteristics. How did such a guy who was indistinguishable from a grunt get in?

Could it be through connections?

Don't tell me that even the dynasty's upper echelons are also corrupted now!

The drill sergeant was heartbroken.

"I didn't understand as well, so I specifically went to inquire." The supervisor hesitated. "It seems that Black Star publicly expressed optimism about this person many years ago, but so far, there has not been any outstanding performance from him. The upper echelons plan to give him a chance to see if you can train him."

"So, it turns out it's like this…" The drill sergeant frowned. "I feel that this is a waste of space. So many years have passed. If he had the potential, then he would have shown it already. What's the point of cultivating him with the mentality of a gambler now?"

"If you strongly object to this, I'll help you pass him on." The supervisor could not care less. It was not him who was going to teach the students any way.

The drill sergeant frowned as he pondered, finally shaking his head. "Forget it. Since they've decided from above, I'll follow the orders and give him a chance… but I won't deliberately give him any slack. If he cannot pass the assessment, he'll still be eliminated."

There was no such thing as fairness in education here. The drill sergeant only liked the top students and was too lazy to spend energy on the poorer students. He even thought that it was a waste of time to look at them. Concentrating the resources on those top students with outstanding talents was the solution to maximizing resource efficiency.

"That's not bad." The supervisor glanced at the list before saying, "Then I'll put him in the most elite class and give him the most powerful opponent, so he won't stay long. I estimate that he'll leave in the first quarter."

The supervisor had the same mentality. It would not help his political performance to train a poor student into an elite. Only when an elite was trained into a top-tier combatant would they then gain merit.

Thus, he did not mind using his power within the rules to eliminate those poor students with insufficient talents to the greatest extent, in order to free up more places to recruit better potential stocks.

In his eyes, this was the proper use of limited resources, and the survival of the fittest was a natural law.

…

Within the Crimson Dynasty's Science Institute was the Wormhole Position Project Office.

The Science Institute was divided into many teams with different complex projects. The wormhole positioning was a large project, and any suspicious wormhole data collected by the dynasty was analyzed here.

The wormhole data left behind by EsGod was just one of the goals of the research team of this project, and it was a sample that was not so important.

As the research team leader was calculating the wormhole model in the laboratory, his secretary hurried in.

"Leader, the approval from above has been sent over. They rejected our batch of applications for the wormhole test."

"Rejected?" The team leader was surprised. "Isn't it just a procedure? Why did they stop us this time?"

After deducing part of the coordinates for a wormhole data, a directional shuttle test would usually be performed, and several multifunctional detectors would then be thrown through the wormhole for an on-site inspection and position to establish a more accurate coordinate system. This would allow them to test if there was any deviation in their data deduction, which was a conventional method of experimenting.

The team leader was quite interested in this batch of test samples, which included the wormhole data left by EsGod.

He did not care much about what was on the other side of the wormhole, and the reason was mainly because the sample was extremely difficult to calculate. After finally determining the scope, he was eager to know if his calculation was right.

The secretary pushed up his glasses, hesitantly replying, "I don't know the details, but it seems like this was a suggestion from His Excellency Black Star. The upper echelons thought his words made sense, so the review standards for most scientific projects have temporarily been tightened."

"What is this about Black Star again?"

"He seems to have mentioned something about the Super Star Cluster Alliance being ready to move. Once a conflict breaks out, the three Universal Civilizations will not have any time to take care of anything else, so it is best to reduce the possibility of any random risks. The management accepted his proposal about our wormhole project."

The team leader could not help but grumble, "Black Star is only a half-baked scientist. Isn't he just causing us more trouble?"

At this moment, one of the researchers carefully asked, "Team leader, then… do we still do the shuttle test?"

Hearing this, the leader huffed in annoyance.

"What do you want to do? Without approval from the upper echelons, do you dare study in private? You're really good, not even respecting your superiors. I must correct your teaching. Come here, take this uncalculated wormhole data and do the calculations! If you can't figure this out, then your holiday this year is cancelled!"

"… Eh, so we actually have holidays?" The researcher in question scratched his head in confusion. Then, where have all my past holidays gone?

Chapter 1145: The Third Sanctum and Awakening Project

In the Central Galaxy, the Abyss of Stars, the Shadow Realm…

The planet filled with dark gaseous air was still suspended here, as though it had existed since ancient times.

Streams of light could be seen a distance away from the planet, and a fleet arrived.

The dark planet suddenly became restless, the energy flowing on its surface rumbling and setting off a wave thousands of feet tall. Like shaking off a full body of lice, shadow servants appeared from the waves, ready to launch an overwhelming attack any time.

The spaceship at the head of the fleet suddenly released a burst of black-colored soul flames, which spread rapidly and quickly swept across the dark planet. The next moment, the pitch-black planet turned quiet, and the countless shadow servants returned to the black ocean, merging into the surface of the planet and disappearing.

Oathkeeper stepped out of the spaceship, hovering in space and staring at the dark planet in front of him whilst speaking through mental fluctuations.

"The date has been brought forward. We must perform the ceremony immediately, otherwise we will not be able to keep up with the agreed date…"

"But I haven't completely transformed all the materials yet…"

"There's no more time. If I miss the date of this appointment, even if I enter The Third Sanctum, I will not be able to bring anyone back. There's no set cycle to this date, and I am not sure how many years it will take till the next date. We cannot miss this opportunity."

"… Alright, I'll try my best."

Oathkeeper nodded before turning to the fleet and commanding, "Prepare to synthesize the final key."

As he spoke, the fleet moved. They spread out in the four cardinal directions, docking at different positions of the dark planet and forming a specific formation. The armor plates at the bottom of each spaceship shifted to reveal a circular device which let off a hazy light. These lights linked with each other to form a translucent energy cover, encapsulating the planet within.

A silvery white cannon muzzle then appeared from all of the spaceships, aimed toward the dark planet.

In the mental network built by Oathkeeper, the voices of the officers could be heard.

"The 12th-level energy stabilization and compression force field has been constructed, and the target has been covered."

"Transmitter has been activated. All Primal Esper Ability Entities have been loaded and sequenced."

"Information Form template is loaded. The reconciliation process has been calibrated. The preparations are complete."

"All standby, wait for my orders," Oathkeeper solemnly said as he raised his palm.

Everyone stared at Oathkeeper's palm, holding their breath. Law and Fay as well as the other officers clenched their fists, their chests rising and falling.

Seeing that the mission of the Holy Accord over these years would end with the wave of this hand, everyone had some sort of fluctuations in their mood.

Looking around, Oathkeeper slightly closed his eyes, waving his hand resolutely.

"Begin!"

Just as he spoke, it was as though they had pressed a start button on a sophisticated instrument. All the operators present had practiced this process thousands of times without any mistakes, and they started to synthesize in strict accordance with the steps of the ceremony.

Bang, bang, bang!

The silvery-white cannons shot out colorful beams of light, each beam representing a Primal Esper Ability Entity, which was submerged into the dark planet.

Thousand Shadows' abilities was the base behind the synthesis. Through its own ability mechanism, it began to compress and fuse the many Primal Esper Ability Entities. The dark planet changed in an instant, the energy of different entities shuttling and flowing in the black sea on the surface of the planet, as though painting on the canvas.

Various energies of a different nature reacted fiercely, and the color of the dark planet turned brighter, gradually transforming into an incandescent ball, like a super large light bulb.

The force field covering it shuddered violently as it withstood the impact. It flickered uncertainly, trembling as though it would be disintegrated at any time.

At this moment, the information form template came into play. It was as if an invisible big hand began to knead the ball of light, changing its shape and shrinking its original volume. Under everyone's eyes, it slowly decreased from a huge planet to a circle not past a hundred meters in diameter. However, the energy density was untold times higher in that slowly spinning circle, so dazzling that it could hardly be seen directly.

"Success!"

Seeing this scene, the members of the Holy Accord cheered.

Oathkeeper suppressed the excitement in his heart, loudly saying, "Put in the other keys and open The Third Sanctum!"

The troops acted again, taking out the 'keys' they had gathered before and putting them into the center of this white ball through the traction field. It seemed that there was a special force present within, holding up these objects and making them rotate around the light circle.

When the last 'key' was thrown in, the circle suddenly emitted a bright light, projecting a picture in the cosmic space not far away, like the reflection of the world in a mirror.

Within the picture, there were six vague doors of light, which were also slowly rotating. They did not look far away, but they appeared untouchable, just like a mirage, as though they were in another world.

This scene only lasted for a moment, and five of the light doors suddenly disappeared, the remaining one growing rapidly as though turning from illusory to reality. The edge of the doorway was still shaking slightly and seemed quite unstable. There was only the radiance of the door within the passage, and nothing could be seen on the other end.

"This is the portal to The Third Sanctum. According to the information handed down, the time flow inside is strange. It's not long to the agreed date, and I've to go in early now…"

This thought passed Oathkeeper's mind, and he took a deep breath, prepared to fly across the door of light.

At this moment, the white halo that was transformed from the dark planet suddenly trembled violently, and the black mist separated itself, turning into a face. Its mouth opened and let out an unwilling roar, which exploded in everyone's mind.

Buzz!

The sudden changes made the passage of The Third Sanctum turn fuzzy and illusory again, as though it was about to disintegrate any time.

"Thousand Shadows!"

Oathkeeper snapped his head around, his eyes spraying raging Soul Flames that instantly hit Thousand Shadows, burning the mist into nothingness.

This blow completely killed off the remaining consciousness of Thousand Shadows, and now, it was truly dead.

"He indeed counterattacked at the last moment…" Oathkeeper was not surprised and secretly sighed.

The Holy Accord initially wanted to wait until Thousand Shadows' consciousness was completely swallowed up before performing the ceremony, but the agreed date was pushed forward, so they had no time to wait.

While Oathkeeper could have easily destroyed Thousand Shadows' consciousness before, under normal circumstances, Thousand Shadows and its ability were one, unable to be forcibly separated. If he killed it, then even the ability itself would be wiped out, removing this Primal Esper Ability Entity forever from this world.

The synthesis ritual was able to eliminate anything superfluous to them, so Thousand Shadows had taken this chance to counterattack. It was only then that it briefly separated, giving Oathkeeper a chance to kill it.

It was just that even though Oathkeeper reduced the influence of the Thousand Shadows to the minimum, it still had a negative impact. Everyone saw that the portal to The Third Sanctum was turning unstable.

Without any delay, Oathkeeper rushed into the passage of The Third Sanctum, only leaving behind a sentence.

"Before I'm back, Law and Fay will be the temporary leaders. Keep a low profile until I bring the rest back."

The next moment, the passage toward The Third Sanctum collapsed, and the many keys disintegrated.

Other than the Primal Esper Ability Entities, the other keys were basically a one-time use, and what the Holy Accord had spent many years gathering all disappeared into smoke.

As Oathkeeper disappeared, the locators that he specially carried on his body all became invalid, as if they no longer existed in this world.

…

A little more than a month later.

In an asteroid belt somewhere within the Flickering World, two figures, one black and one red, shuttled through it, fighting fiercely.

"Torrent—Getta Hadoken!"

A bright blue ray was emitted, and the asteroids that were along the ray's path were instantly vaporized and annihilated, leaving behind a blank path.

The red figure teleported to avoid the attack before backhandedly fanning out a red energy wave to retaliate.

The space around them flickered as the two of them continuously exchanged blows. They were Han Xiao and Hila, who were enjoying a routine spar.

The two of them fought against each other many times, so they knew each other's bottom line. Following Han Xiao's hit to Hila's abdomen with a heavy knee drop, he smashed her down so she could not stand up before landing a heavy neck chop with his palm, ending the battle.

"Cough cough cough…" Hila kneeled on a small star as she grabbed her neck and coughed. She said in a muffled tone, "I lost again."

"There's no need to be discouraged. Your progress is already fast enough. The Underworld is really a good thing." Han Xiao felt a little jealous.

Since acquiring the Underworld secondary dimension, Hila's growth rate also began to skyrocket. The faster the Underworld recovered, the stronger her Esper Ability would get.

Thus, in Han Xiao's recent battles with Hila, he had gone as heavy as he could. If he relaxed, Hila would complain that he was going easy on her.

"My improvement is not as fast as yours." Hila stood up, pointing at the floating device beside Han Xiao. "Your new machinery is not bad. Even I cannot eat a few shots of this thing."

"I'm after all a Mechanic. Our systems are different."

Han Xiao smiled as he stowed the Getta Hadoken away.

In the past two months, he had succeeded in creating all four new Gold Grade items from the blueprints. With [100 Million Mechanic Empire—Manison], the success rate and efficiency of creating Universal Treasures had been greatly improved, which greatly saved costs.

The Evolutionary Totem could easily be mass produced, but it was difficult for the Psionic Obelisk. However, Han Xiao managed to produce a batch of finished products, which had been installed in many of the army bases, while the Mechanical Territory was only provided to his Machinery civilization.

The scope of application for the Titan Spinal Center was limited to the Mechanical Deity. Only the Getta Hadoken was the most practical. It was not only adapted to a variety of fighting environments but could also combine various tricks and utilize weapon-like combos, winning the favoritism of the Great Mechanic Han.

The attack strength of the Getta Hadoken depended on the Power Output of the energy core as well as the strength of his own input. It would have an attack enhancement effect, which would increase one's original attack power by a set percentage. Its lethality was impressive—other than concentrated firepower, the Mechanic usually did not have any other methods that could dish out high damage, and the Getta Hadoken made up for this gap to a certain extent.

Every time Han Xiao used this weapon, he could not resist shouting out the name, as though this would increase the strength further.

The two Primal Esper Ability Entities were also dealt with. The Natural Spirit Power found its host, namely Emerald Grass, the director of the Pharmaceutical Research Institute in the Logistics Department. Her abilities were extremely compatible with it, and she succeeded in adapting to the Entity.

As for Frost Authority, it did not manage to find a host, so Han Xiao allowed it to remain as a Mysterious Energy Host for the time being.

After cleaning up the battlefield, Han Xiao casually said, "After a while, the joint award ceremony of the three Universal Civilizations for the Intelligent Plague will be held. Do you want to attend?"

"I didn't participate in clearing the Intelligent Plague. Why would I go?" Hila shook her head. "In fact, you're the one who's going up to receive the award. Are you prepared?"

"There's nothing much to prepare. Isn't it just some ceremonial words? I'll make some up."

"Whatever." Hila rolled her eyes. She was normally dignified and grave, almost never engaging with her subordinates in idle chatter. She would only talk more when she was with Han Xiao. "Speaking of which, it seems like the free competition zone is a little weird nowadays."

"Why?"

"The fourth exploration phase is estimated to be around eighty percent complete at the moment, and the expansion of the Super Star Cluster Alliance is growing bigger, no longer just content with exploration but also starting to invade and seize the other territories of the surrounding organizations on a large scale. They not only encompass the central zone of the free competition zone and multiple resource rich planets—they've also established a stargate transportation system, connecting multiple borders, obviously with strategic intentions."

Han Xiao did not find that weird as he replied, "It's normal. The Super Star Cluster Alliance is now in preparation. It's estimated that the three Universal Civilizations will soon have a formal conflict with them. They wish to obtain a piece of land to act freely in the Flickering World, and the three Universal Civilizations are unwilling to allow the Super Star Cluster Alliance to do so. With the excuse of free competition and anti-monopoly, the contradictions between the two parties cannot be reconciled."

"Oh… there's also some strange movements of other organizations, including many non-legal Immortal organizations. It seems like they're preparing to move as well."

"Alright, I'll pay more attention to this." Han Xiao nodded. The World Server war was imminent, with the Super Star Clusters seen in the shadows of this event.

Both of them chatted a little more before returning to their respective fleets. Hila returned to the free competition zone, while Han Xiao's destination was toward the planet where the three Universal Civilizations would hold the award ceremony, located in the Dawn Star Cluster, which was the gateway to the Flickering World.

After arriving and announcing his identity, the fleet, led by the Dynasty Guards, took the VIP channel, skipping past the other guests, and docked at the port.

As soon as Han Xiao disembarked, he saw Tarrokov waiting for him.

Both of them walked closer, reaching out for a strong handshake.

"Have you been waiting for long?"

"Not at all, Your Excellency Black Star. You came early."

"Hehe, I have a good sense of time."

After a few greetings, Tarrokov lowered his voice. "Because of secrecy, I could not inform you earlier, but I can now say that the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations are attending this meeting, so you have to be prepared."

Han Xiao's brows jumped up. "You mean…"

"That's right. They'll appear in person this time, personally giving you the award."

Han Xiao felt surprised.

I thought that I would just be here to parade around once. To think that it would be such a huge event.

It seems that the three Universal Civilizations have set their hearts on pushing up my fame!

Chapter 1146: Presenting Honors and Difficulties

After waiting for several days on the planet, Han Xiao witnessed the increase in the planetary security levels. A regular military force arrived, taking over the responsibility of protecting the planet, sealing the line defense, and making it nigh impenetrable.

Around half of the planet had entered martial law, and various advanced defense measures had also been arranged to prevent long-range strikes from threatening the celebratory planet.

While the Intelligent Plague broke out in the Ancient Star Desert, and it was more reasonable for the ceremony to be held there, the three Universal Civilizations took into account the fact that many of the Beyond Grade As were currently in the Flickering World and changed the venue, quoting symbolic significance. After all, this was another major exploration result of the galactic civilization after so many years.

The leaders of the three Universal Civilizations attended the ceremony together, which was a rare scene. Due to their sensitive identities, such an event would generally be held in the Central Galaxy rather than other Star Fields. Even with careful security, life was unpredictable, so leaving the Central Galaxy was undoubtedly a risky move.

Han Xiao was sure that there would be some organizations with ulterior motives moving around. While the three Universal Civilizations had a mature operating system, such that their government would not be disturbed much even if their leaders were assassinated, there would still be some temporary chaos, which could be what these people were looking for.

Of course, if an organization really dared do this, then they would no longer have a place in the explored universe, as they would be hunted until every last one of them was dead. The relationship with the faction would forever be at 'Hatred'. Moreover, with so many armies and Beyond Grade As gathered in a place, the success rate of an assassination was negligible.

But well, this does not hinder them from scheming some deliberate framing.

Han Xiao suspected that the three Universal Civilizations might engage in a self-directed act, pretending to have some outsiders assassinate them during the ceremony, before using this to put blame on their targets to get an excuse for a crusade.

This method seems familiar, as though I've seen it somewhere before…

Could it be that I'm the one that inspired them‽

Han Xiao had experienced a 'back stab' not too long ago, so his memory was still fresh. At this moment, his thoughts could not help but be biased toward this aspect, and his imagination was running wild.

With his understanding of the three Universal Civilizations, it was not impossible that they would do such a thing. The chances of it happening was probably around twenty percent, and he could not ask Urranrell for verification just like that.

During the few days he stayed on the planet, he did not contact the head of the three Universal Civilizations but rather sat in the officially arranged guest house just like everyone else, waiting silently.

On the day the ceremony was held, Han Xiao and the guests were all transported to the ceremony site in official vehicles. The venue was a large hall decorated in the style of the dynasty. One could see countless invited guests lining up to enter the venue, but no loud noises were heard, only the rustling of quiet conversations. The entire atmosphere was quite serious.

Han Xiao's seat was arranged at the front table, with Kasuyi, Kant, and the other peak Beyond Grade As.

After greeting, Han Xiao sat down next to Kasuyi, glancing at the people, before whispering, "Mechanic Emperor didn't come?"

"He's here, but it's just his avatar." Kasuyi gestured toward the back.

A steel lump was sat at the edge of the venue, but even if it was covered in a layer of iron, Han Xiao could smell Manison's aura on it.

"He won't cause trouble during the ceremony, right?" Han Xiao blinked.

"Manison is not that crazy yet," Kant replied.

Today, Kant appeared as a handsome middle-aged galactic human, with a tall nose, deep eyes, and sharp facial features.

Han Xiao glanced at the security personnel at the edge of the venue before whispering, "I keep thinking that this won't go so smoothly. Maybe there might be an assassination."

"With so many of us Beyond Grade As here, who'd have such big guts?" Sun Hunter said.

"It might be a self-directed act…" Han Xiao winked.

Secret Master could not help but roll his eyes at Han Xiao as he coldly snorted, "Enough with that. You think the three Universal Civilizations are like you, to perform such a lowly act?"

"So what if it's lowly? What matters is that it's useful." Han Xiao clicked his tongue. "Wanna bet?"

"You dare bet‽" Secret Master was stunned.

Aren't you clear what sort of luck you have?

If one were to liken my luck to a flawless gemstone, then yours would be like the moldy green moss along the wall of a stinking ditch. How dare you bet with me, a master of luck? Are you feeling that charitable?

"Alright, then what are you going to give me?"

"I'll bet Sun Hunter. If I lose, then I'll give him to you. How about that?" Han Xiao reached out his thumb and finger, pinching the tiny guy's head and pulling him up.

"Huh?"

Sun Hunter, who was being dangled in midair, had the expression of the confused Nick Young meme.

What the f*ck does it have to do with me? Watch out before I blast your ass.

Secret Master was speechless, immediately patting Han Xiao to put Sun Hunter down. He apologized before whispering angrily to Han Xiao, "Who uses another person as a gambling stake‽ His Excellency Sun Hunter might be a little pocket-sized, but how can you make fun of his size."

"We have a good relationship, don't worry."

Han Xiao flicked his finger, bouncing it against Sun Hunter's head, earning him an angered glare from the other party before he sheepishly smiled and gave it up. He had always wanted to do so in his past life, and he had finally ticked it off his bucket list. With all of them being on equal footing, this little joke was harmless, but if it was an ordinary Beyond Grade A that did this to Sun Hunter, the person could probably apply for disability protection.

"Since you don't like this bet, then I'll change to something else."

"What?"

"I know you have some issues with me, so let's do it like this. If you win, I'll stand still for ten minutes and let you vent your frustrations. If I win, you do the same. Fair?"

Secret Master simply shut his mouth and turned his head away, not wanting to speak with Han Xiao any longer.

Forget about it, who here doesn't know of your Indestructible Body's tankiness? Fair my grandpa, I still want to live for a long time.

The group at the table chatted for a while, and suddenly, a group of officers strode into the venue, surrounded by their respective leaders. The venue immediately calmed down as the atmosphere turned solemn.

The Dynasty's Ruler Urranrell, the Federation's President Bader, and the Arcane Church's Pope swaggered to the high platform of the venue under the eyes of everyone present, sitting at the specially arranged seats with the podium next to them.

Han Xiao had only seen Urranrell personally, and this was his first time meeting Bader and the Pope. While both of them had different temperaments, they possessed the same aura of power like Urranrell, causing everyone to turn serious subconsciously.

However, the focus of his observation was not the two leaders, but the personal guards around them, all of which were of the same stature as the Dark Lord Clotti.

On Bader's side was a male with a white complexion and similar body structure to humans, except that he had a straight horn on his forehead, forcing him to keep his hair to an appropriate length. His hair color was golden and was tied into a twisted braid that hangs down to the waist. He seemed to have some elf blood as he had long ears, deep purple eyes, and a well-proportioned mouth but did not have a nose. The part that was his nose that was supposed to be flat was strangely not ugly—it instead appeared harmonious with his features.

This person wore a robe that was dotted with light gold and ice blue colors, revealing an elegant nobleness and gentle temperament. This person was the Personal Guard of the Federation, the peak Beyond Grade A 'Golden Ring' Oulou.

Oulou's ability was to borrow the power of a specific secondary dimension. It sounded like the dead Traveller's ability, but his combat power was not the same. This guy was at the same level as the Dark Lord, able to fight Kasuyi hand to hand and not lose.

Han Xiao turned his head to the other side.

Next to the Church's Pope was a huge guy, not the kind that got to this size through training but rather naturally huge, as though he had some giant blood running within. This was the Chief Guard of the Church, the one who was stationed at the Temple of God, 'God's Chosen' Wuornos.

Compared to Oulou's glamorous outfits, Wuornos' looks and temperament were low-key, as if he was just an ordinary middle-aged man with wrinkled eyes. He wore a silver-gray priest robe, and if not for the robe, one would probably not recognize him if they threw him into a crowd of people.

"Oulou and Wuornos…" Han Xiao softly muttered.

Both of them were just like the Dark Lord, generally only following the Head of State, hardly participating in activities other than their duties.

Glancing at Han Xiao, Kasuyi leaned over and casually said, "This is your first time meeting them, right? Here's a piece of advice, you can joke with Oulou and fool around, but don't go and provoke Wuornos."

"What's with that?" Han Xiao was curious.

"While Oulou is the chief guard, his personality is different to Clotti's, warmer and not so indifferent. Other than occasionally showing some superiority, he's not bad. However, Wuornos… heh, just don't mess with him."

"You're making me more curious. You're the ally of the Arcane Church. Do you know some gossip?"

"Even if I knew, I wouldn't tell you. I can only say that he's the Beyond Grade A publicly acknowledged to be the strongest, and naturally, there's a reason." Kasuyi blandly smiled.

At this time, Urranrell stood before the podium, surveying the scene before speaking.

"Dear friends and guests, today, we're holding a grand award ceremony to commend all the heroes who made great contributions in the Intelligent Plague disaster. The ceremony will honor every hero with an outstanding meritorious service.

"First, on behalf of the three Universal Civilizations, I would like to extend my warm congratulations to the heroes of the universe who will be receiving the Medal of Honor as well as the honorary titles, and I extend my highest respect to them.

"We've gone through many ups and downs, and today, we have united as one and once again eliminated another new disaster.

"Since the establishment of the galactic society in the last years of the exploration era, generations of heroes with a sense of responsibility have given up themselves to overcome difficulty after difficulty, shaping the cornerstone of today's galactic society. While many have passed away, their glorious deeds will always spread from generation to generation.

"Only by crossing new mountains can we see a wider distance. Under the leadership of the three Universal Civilizations, we have overcome obstacles, constantly explored the unknown universe, and expanded our territory. Now, we're in the Flickering World, a milestone achievement and a fruitful result of our external exploration.

"Such an achievement cannot be achieved with the cooperation of the entire galactic society. It's this bond of order that connects us and creates a never-ending pioneering spirit. Anyone who tries to disrupt this order and unity will become the enemy of the entire universe…"

The media was broadcasting Urranrell's speech to the entire universe. When she finished speaking, there was a tsunami-like applause in the venue. Han Xiao and the other Beyond Grade As also gave face to clap a little.

Han Xiao heard that in Urranrell's words she emphasized the importance of collectivism, on the correctness and achievements of the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations, vaguely throwing arrows at the Super Star Cluster Alliance as well as the Mechanic Emperor. While she did not explicitly mention anything, everyone knew who the so-called 'people who disrupted galactic civilization and society' were.

Bader and the Pope also gave some short speeches before entering the formal award process. One by one, the heroes came to the stage, accepting the honors and making a speech. Some also answered questions from the reporters.

Before long, the ceremony approached the end. There was only one person left, and everyone's eyes were focused on Han Xiao.

"Black Star limited the outflow of the virus during the disaster and discovered the true character of the virus core at the critical moment, reversing our erroneous strategy and allowing us to reformulate our plan. He alone changed the course of the disaster. He later captured the virus core and destroyed it, completely eliminating any hidden dangers, putting an end to the crisis of a second outbreak of the Intelligent Plague, saving countless lives. His contribution is huge and thus needs to be rewarded."

After Urranrell spoke, Han Xiao stood up, stepping onto the stage and shaking hands with the leaders. Numerous news media reporters in the audience took videos and photos, turning the stage white with their flashes.

"Black Star has many good qualities. He is determined, resolute, flexible, and strong in principle…" Bader gave a series of praise, finally coming to the conclusion. "In view of his achievements, we have decided to jointly award him the Galaxy Medal."

The moment he finished speaking, everyone in the audience paused.

The Galaxy Medal, which was the highest symbol of honor jointly set up by the three Universal Civilizations since their establishment, was the golden glory of the explored universe. There were only a few winners of this medal in history.

While many of them had this expectation in their hearts, they were still shocked to hear it. They always felt that although Black Star had great achievements, there was still a certain distance from this medal. Now it seemed that the factor behind this medal was if the three Universal Civilizations would support them.

But no matter what they thought, the honor was real, and the audience burst into applause.

Pa pa pa…

Amid the warm applause, Urranrell took out a star-like dazzling medal, placing it in her palm, while the other two held it by the edges, handing it to Han Xiao.

This image seemed to freeze, and the flashes under the stage flickered, recording this historic scene.

The commotion lasted a long time, and it took dozens of seconds before all movement gradually ceased.

Han Xiao reached out to accept the medal, pinning it on his chest before shaking hands with all three of them once more. He came up to the podium, clearing his throat.

"Many thanks to the Crimson Dynasty, Federation of Light, and the Arcane Church. To be able to receive this award is an honor for me. As part of the explored universe, I have the responsibility and obligation to maintain our stability and prosperity…"

Reading from his prepared script, Han Xiao raised his head to gaze at the clock on the venue before smiling.

"Since I'm the last person, it means that the ceremony is about to end. I won't do a lengthy speech. Everything is about the same, and I feel that everyone here is already tired of hearing it…"

The audience let out laughs.

Han Xiao smiled as he nodded. "In short, what sort of person I am can be seen from my actions. I believe that society has its own views of me, and I don't need to repeat it, so let's skip that and go to the questions… Anyone?"

Hearing this, many of the reporters raised their hands enthusiastically, hoping for him to point at themselves.

Just as Han Xiao was about to pick someone, one of them stood up on his own and began to speak.

"Your Excellency Black Star, I heard that the Mechanic Emperor Manison also made a great contribution to the Intelligent Plague. Without him, the three Universal Civilizations would not have been able to find the location of the virus core. Thus, it can be said that a third or even half of your Galaxy Medal belongs to Manison… but for this award ceremony, the Mechanic Emperor did not obtain anything, and you seem to have forgotten about it and ignored his merits, accepting the medal with a peace of mind. What do you think of this?"

The originally enthusiastic venue suddenly seemed to have been doused in cold water, instantly quieting down.

Everyone moved their eyes subconsciously to Manison, who had been sitting indifferently at the edge of the venue.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes a little as he sized up the reporter. He saw the cold smile on that person's face, obviously wishing to embarrass himself and the three Universal Civilizations in public.

Chapter 1147: Only Interested in Causing Sensational News

The moment he started to ask his question rashly, the meaningful gazes of Urranrell, Bader, and the Pope immediately landed on him.

The reporter's chest had his nametag, and he was called Porters, belonging to a news group in the Primeval Star River. His position was not low, otherwise he would not be responsible for the interview of the three Universal Civilizations on behalf of his media. Having participated in many press conferences for the three Universal Civilizations, his performance had been normal. To suddenly get into trouble, naturally someone had to put him up to it.

Han Xiao's thoughts spun. At first, he suspected the Mechanic Emperor, but he quickly banished that thought.

The Old Man could not wait to pretend to be an ostrich right now. The more low-key he was, the better. This behavior of hiring people to question for himself was actually in some manner a self-damaging act… Manison was not so humorous and would not do such disturbing things.

Thus, the most likely suspect would be the Super Star Cluster Alliance, who contradicted the three Universal Civilizations most openly. Not only did they wish to sow discord, they also wished to badmouth the three Universal Civilizations in public. It cost little to do so.

All they had to take out was a sum of Enas, which would be astronomical in the eyes of ordinary people, and the reporter would naturally be tempted. In such a grand scene, the negative impact of an untimely question would be further magnified.

The identity of a reporter acted as a shield for him, allowing him to add fuel to the fire. The three Universal Civilizations naturally did not wish to worsen the situation, and thus, they would not capture him or threaten him afterward. As the ruling party, a pawn was just a pawn to them. They had to show some class and go straight for the orchestrator behind the scenes.

The surrounding reporters look at Porters in surprise and agitation.

"Have you lost your mind‽"

"Quick, apologize and sit down!"

"You don't want to be in this business anymore‽"

Those who knew him whispered in low voices, wishing to pull him down, but Porters stood firm, staring straight at Han Xiao with a spirit of getting to the bottom of the matter.

Han Xiao pressed both of his hands on the podium, slowly saying, "Dear reporter, I don't seem to have invited you to ask your question."

"So, are you avoiding the question now?"

Porters turned a deaf ear to them, his gaze sharp and his bearing aggressive.

Oh, there's a hint of a western reporter's flavor in his attitude.

"You guys, only thinking about sensationalizing news every day," Han Xiao said with a smile that was not a smile. "I believe that the galactic society has a unified view of the Mechanic Emperor's behavior, but looking at you, it seems like you wish to fight for him, huh?"

"I'm just asking the questions that the public might be curious about, based on the professional ethics of a reporter." Porters straightened his back, with a conscientious attitude.

"Alright. This question is a little more sensitive. While I did not call upon you, I can answer this one." Han Xiao tapped his fingers on the podium, his tone casual. "Manison did indeed make a contribution. This is an undeniable fact, but your statement is wrong. In fact, Manison discovered the problem of the virus core earlier than I did. This medal should have belonged to him, but he deliberately chose not to report it because of his selfishness. If it was not for me who revealed it, he would not have revealed this key information. In this manner, the three Universal Civilizations would always have been kept in the dark, and the universe would still be shrouded in the shadow of the Intelligent Plague."

"So, you're admitting that the Mechanic Emperor should be sharing the Galaxy Medal with you? You also think that it's unfair he has not been awarded the medal?" Porters pressed on.

"I only admitted that he has credit due in this area, not that he deserves the Galaxy Medal. Don't distort my meaning at your own will. Moreover, Manison's final decision is enough to make everyone here re-evaluate his motives."

"Your Excellency Black Star, please don't digress. We are not talking about the Mechanic Emperor's choice, only his objective achievements." Porters was skilled in such evasive methods.

"No, they are not separable. Part of my credit comes from my plan to stop the Mechanic Emperor. If he did not do anything at that time, my credit would be limited. If you think based on this logic, technically, he might deserve half of the Galaxy Medal. Hmm, that actually makes sense… but seriously, if we were to hand him a medal, then those not in the know would believe that he has done a good thing, and those who have worked hard for the universe would feel that this is unfair. I believe the three Universal Civilizations only made such a decision after great thought."

"But the Mechanic…"

"I've answered your question. You may sit down now. There are still others waiting to ask their questions. Please do not flout the rules time and again, or I'll have to ask you to leave."

Han Xiao indifferently cut off Porters.

The other party's goal was to create trouble, so whatever he said would make the atmosphere uncomfortable. He would only stop at his own explanation, never thinking of making the other party speechless. As long as an earnest attitude was shown, most viewers would naturally listen to it, and continuing to argue would not only be pointless but also damaging to his image.

Seeing the nearby guards already eyeing him, Porters could only sit back down in anger.

Ignoring the contempt, disgust, and complicated gazes of his peers around him, Porters suppressed the fear in his heart and tried his best to make himself look calm. He controlled the trembling in his hands and feet, secretly breathing a sigh of relief.

Hu… I fulfilled the requirements.

Most likely, the President of my broadcasting station is going crazy now. Luckily, it's not my problem anymore. I'll immediately resign once I return. Whether the station gets suppressed or not isn't my problem. Why would I still work when I've gotten my remuneration?

Dreaming of the future, Porters felt that a beautiful life was waving its hands at him.

The memory in his mind was extremely clear. Not too long ago, a few mysterious people suddenly contacted him, offering him a huge sum of money to make him launch a verbal attack during today's occasion.

He knew that the moment he did this, his career would come to an end. Even if the three Universal Civilizations were too lazy to deal with him, the people below would act spontaneously and demand that the media industry ban him.

He was mentally prepared for this. Not only was the amount raised enough to move him, but the other party also had huge backing. The moment they looked for him, he could not reject their offer, so he did not have much choice to begin with.

While his actions would invite investigations and industry bans for him, his employer not only gave him money but also promised to arrange an escape route, allowing him to change his face and move to their territory to live, thus avoiding the grasp of the three Universal Civilizations.

For the rest of his life, he would be a rich man and enjoy his limitless fortune… This was what Porters was looking forward to.

Seeing that there was nothing wrong with Black Star's answer, the atmosphere in the field quickly recovered. The reporters continued to enthusiastically ask questions, pretending that the episode just now did not happen.

From start to finish, Urranrell and the other two's expressions did not change one bit. Manison also remained silent, with no intention to interrupt, as though his soul had already left the venue, thinking about what he should get for dinner.

No one else came to make trouble again. Han Xiao answered a few friendly questions before returning to his seat. The three Universal Civilizations' leaders then spoke for a bit more before the award ceremony ended successfully.

The guests left the area one after another, while the three Universal Civilizations' leaders left the scene under the escort of their guards. Han Xiao also left by the VIP passage after exchanging a few words with the other Beyond Grade As.

The moment he walked out of the venue, he received a call from Sylvia.

"Army Commander, I watched the live broadcast. What should I do with that reporter, Porters?" Sylvia immediately got to the point.

"What do you intend to do?"

"Get rid of him?"

"Let's not. We can only get rid of our anger, and it will even give the Super Star Cluster Alliance an excuse to gain a bargaining chip. The three Universal Civilizations will definitely not allow him to continue living his original life. That's enough."

"So, we just sit still and do nothing?"

"Let me think…" Han Xiao thought for a while before an evil grin stretched across, "Monitor the flow of funds for all his accounts. The Super Star Cluster Alliance will definitely find a way to launder the money and put the reward into his account. The moment he receives a large amount of income, hack his account and donate all his money, including his savings."

"Let him work for nothing? Heh, evil enough. I like this idea."

Sylvia's eyes gleamed, and she immediately cut the call.

Han Xiao left the quantum network, not even putting Porters in his heart. He was not willing to stoop to such a low level to deal with a tool.

He quickly threw this matter to the back of his mind, stretching out his hand to take off the Galaxy Medal and examine it closely.

The item details on his interface showed that this medal would bring to him a Universe Legendary Point, [Galaxy Medal Awardee], as well as a bonus effect of solidifying the relationship between him and the three Universal Civilizations at [Respect]. This was equivalent to 3,000 Contribution Points.

"The number of faction points cannot beat even one Legendary Point."

Han Xiao nodded in satisfaction. He did not have much hope for this kind of medal anyways, so it was a surprise to obtain extra gains.

At this moment, two dynasty non-commissioned officers walked out and stopped in front, as though they were there just for him.

"Your Excellency Black Star, the three heads have invited you to meet with them."

Han Xiao's feet stopped, and he nodded. "Lead the way."

At the same time, in the temporary base of the Flickering World for the Super Star Cluster Alliance, the messengers of each ally met secretly in the round table conference room through remote projection.

A virtual screen was suspended, playing the live broadcast of the award ceremony.

After watching the live broadcast, many of them shook their heads.

"The effect was only so-so, not the level of influence we hoped for."

"An ordinary reporter can only reach this level. I told you not to hold high hopes."

"A little effect would be good. Right now, the prestige of the three Universal Civilizations has been consolidated once again, and hitting them will only bring us a weak effect."

"This is only a trivial matter after all. Strength is still the most important principle."

"That's right, so let's forget about this topic and return to the more important things. Come… what did we discuss previously?"

"We talked about the various support for the organizations. It's time to act collectively, like with those Immortals Organization. This time, we're attacking preemptively. We cannot wait for the three Universal Civilizations to take action before fighting back."

"The stowaways we sent out in the first phase of the exploration can now be officially activated. The three Universal Civilizations control the gateway to the Flickering World, while we're alone. If we wish to obtain a steady stream of supplies and reinforcements, we must count on these buried chess pieces."

"The first batch of targets to occupy have also been selected. Our regular army will not move, and all the agents will first take action. Before the three Universal Civilizations formally intervene, we'll try our best to seize the territory within the free competition zone."

"What did the Beyond Grade A Development union say?"

"They basically choose to maintain neutral, but Black Star claims to have a private grudge with the Modo Civilization, so his attitude is currently unknown."

"Troublesome guy… Hey, messenger of Modo, wait until the conflict officially breaks out. We might not have the energy to take care of you guys, so you will have to come up with your own plans. If you really can't do it, sacrifice yourself to hold Black Star back. The overall situation is the most important."

"Okay…"

"Everyone, the success or failure of this operation will determine the future of our respective civilizations. To gain further opportunities or to be ruled forever… at all costs, we can only succeed!"

Chapter 1148: The Participation Requirements of the Three Universal Civilizations

Han Xiao followed the two dynasty non-commissioned officers through the tightly guarded corridors to a large office, which had been refurbished for the three heads of state. Right now, the door of the innermost reception room was closed.

The Secretary of the Dynasty Ruler put down the work on his hands, approaching them with a respectful tone.

"Your Excellency Black Star, the three Rulers are still in discussion. Please wait for a moment."

"Alright, I'll sit by the side."

Han Xiao casually found a place to sit down, while the Secretary assigned people to bring refreshments for him before sitting opposite Han Xiao.

In order not to let Black Star feel left out, the Secretary turned into an escort and started talking.

Having spent decades in the dynasty, Han Xiao knew quite a few of the high-ranking officials, and this was not his first time talking to the secretary. As they talked, the topic shifted to the little incident that had happened just now.

"Your Excellency Black Star, what do you think of that reporter?" the Secretary asked.

"Just an unlucky sod."

"Indeed." The Secretary laughed. "The moment he was selected, his life was destined to be affected. It's understandable why he would choose to gamble for the greatest benefits in the end."

"Eh, I thought you'd have to maintain political correctness in your position. You should have said that he should have immediately reported the orchestrator."

"Hehe, we pay attention to political correctness, but we also have to be practical. The upper echelons will never like a person who only knows how to blindly shout slogans." The Secretary shook his head. "He's not our citizen, nor is there any patriotic factor about him. The probability of expecting him to actively expose the other party is low. Tell me, what would he get in return?"

"A tiny reward, maybe a medal?" Han Xiao casually joked.

"Haha, you're quite humorous… However, these are extravagant hopes. What he'll get is likely a downgrade of his position. He was originally a big-name reporter belonging to a news group, who was responsible for attending our official events, so it should be considered a top-level position. But if he exposes this matter, there won't be preferential treatment for him… You also understand that the civilization is a huge system, with each department not just working for the civilization but also looking out for their own political achievements. So, why would the news department take such a risk to allow a suspicious person to remain? They will have a good talk with the news channel's upper echelons, then that guy will likely be shifted elsewhere."

"Doesn't that mean that the person would be worth taking care of?"

"Is there a need? It's easier to swap with a new person. Is he working in a non-replaceable role?"

"Oh, that's a little cold blooded. Aren't you afraid of making people disheartened?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Haha, do you think we will surround and protect a small reporter so that others will see our care and increase their confidence in cooperating with us? So, in the future, it's more possible for them to seek us out to expose others?" The Secretary laughed.

"Isn't that a good thing?" Han Xiao was interested.

"Different levels have different logics in dealing with matters. At our level, many times, the policies for dealing with such matters run contrary to ordinary people's thinking logic. It's basically a combination of many factors." The Secretary blinked. "If it's a higher position or character, even an organization with a certain power, we may make concessions as you mentioned.

"But for a small reporter? We will not waste our time on him. Our war with the Super Star Clusters on public opinion has always been going on in the dark, and this is not the first time such matters have happened. If he has no contacts and is totally unable to fight for the protection that we have planned… he's not an important figure, so we shall not focus so much on him."

"I didn't know this in the past, but your words are really bold." Han Xiao sized up the Secretary once more.

"It's just the truth. My authority might be huge, but the resources available to exercise them are also limited. In the end, it boils down to a question of distribution." The Secretary smacked his lips as he said, "It's no good for them to proactively expose it, so it's better to agree to the orchestrator behind the scenes. At least, you can obtain a large sum of money, and the things you do are within your scope of normal duties. You have not crossed the line… After all, questions asked by the journalists are from their own free will. We cannot change that."

"Can you really not?"

"… At least in name. There is no official budget for friendly questioning, so we can only rely on hard authority to make others more self-aware." The Secretary smiled. "But authority is not always useful. There are not many reporters who dare make things difficult for us. Some do it for performance; some are instructed. All sorts of scenarios have been experienced before, but how could there always be the same root issue?"

Han Xiao stroked his chin before suddenly saying, "Why do I feel that your words carry a deeper meaning?"

"Haha, I've been seen through. My idea was actually to test you out and see how you intended to deal with this journalist, Black Star… With your swift and vigorous means, you've probably already deployed your measures." The Secretary laughed.

What vigor and resoluteness, you might as well just say that I'm petty…

Han Xiao secretly scolded but casually revealed his plan.

"It's good that you did not fall for the trick. It seems that my reminder was unnecessary." The Secretary smiled.

"… It's really tiring to talk to you. Don't hide things, just tell me directly." Han Xiao was helpless.

"Hehe, we hope to downplay it and not impose any personal threats on the journalist, so we need your cooperation. If this person's life is threatened, it'll easily turn into a fuss…"

"I think it's useless even if you don't wish to do anything. The people behind might choose to silence him, which will also allow them to smear the blame on you."

The Secretary folded his hands as he replied, "I understand, and there is indeed such a possibility, but the probability is low… First of all, such accusations are not damaging enough for us to make trouble. If someone tries to place the blame on us, there will be flaws, and it would be easy to reverse the case back onto them. Furthermore, how many would care about a journalist's life or death? The moment the news is spread out, those with a discerning eye would immediately see through the issue of the problem. In addition, those who are likely to care about the news are also journalists themselves, and spreading the news will only spoil the image of the media industry… With so many factors, this is why we chose to downplay it."

Hearing this, Han Xiao did not agree nor disagree. The higher one's level, the wider their knowledge. The progress of his own methods over the years came, to a certain extent, from his exchanges with the people of different classes, influenced by their own methods.

After chatting a while longer, Han Xiao suddenly recalled a certain matter and changed topics.

"Urranrell's term should be almost over, right?"

In his previous life, after the end of the Flickering World storyline, the Crimson Dynasty Ruler changed. The day was almost here.

The Secretary paused a bit before subconsciously lowering his voice. "I cannot share the specific details yet."

"Alright then, let's just talk about you. If Urranrell were to retire, your position would also have to change, right? Any news for you?"

"The moment the Ruler retires, my term as Secretary will also come to an end. The change of position has not been decided yet, but I'll definitely be one of the foreign delegates for the government, likely within the same rank as well…"

Just as Han Xiao was about to pursue the topic, the doors to the reception room opened.

The Secretary stopped talking at the right time, gesturing for Han Xiao to enter. Seeing this, Han Xiao walked into the reception room. The first thing he saw was the three leaders behind their desks, with the various Beyond Grade A personal guards beside them.

As the door closed, Han Xiao casually greeted them.

Dark Lord Clotti nodded slightly, with no intention to speak.

It was instead Oulou who swept Han Xiao from head to toe before slowly saying, "You caught quite a few of my friends previously. It's a pity I was not there, or else you would not have succeeded."

"Good day to you too. Pleased to make your acquaintance." While he sensed the hostility in Oulou, Han Xiao remained indifferent, keeping a slight smile without trying to provoke the other party.

"Humph." Oulou snorted and did not continue talking, only raising his head slightly and showing an arrogant posture.

The first impression this guy gave off was really just arrogance.

While Kasuyi had mentioned that Oulou was more moderate, this was in reference to the Dark Lord, who was known for being cold. Han Xiao did not expect Oulou to be enthusiastic toward him, especially given the fact that he had captured a few Federation allies not too long ago.

Wuornos did not even open his eyes to look at Han Xiao, as though he had fallen asleep.

Among the three, Han Xiao was the most curious about Wuornos. In his previous life, both the Dark Lord and Oulou had entered the main battlefield during the World Tree War and had perished. Only Wuornos had not been dispatched. Furthermore, his previous records were also few and between, making him extremely mysterious.

Even in normal times, when it came to Beyond Grade A powerhouses, Wuornos was rarely counted because he basically did not move against anybody, a weirdo just like Sorokin. However, their reputations lay at the two extremes.

At this moment, the Dynasty Ruler Urranrell spoke. "Black Star, how does it feel to have the Galaxy Medal?"

"I'm flattered." Han Xiao was expressionless.

"But you don't seem too satisfied?"

"… I've been seen through. Yes, I'm actually a little worried."

"What are you worried about?"

"If I ever make new contributions to the universe in the future, will I then get a second or maybe a third Galaxy Medal? I feel that I might have to open a warehouse to store this stuff. It might even have no space in the future to store all these medals. What a headache." Han Xiao sighed.

Urranrell was perplexed. Can you please speak coherently?

"Let's skip the polite remarks. You're not just looking for me to encourage me, right? Just tell me if you have something." Han Xiao spread out his hands. After putting up a front for the whole day, he did not wish to be polite anymore.

Bader sighed before speaking. "Then let's get straight to the point. I believe you've learned from your channels that the dispute between us and the Super Star Cluster Alliance is about to begin. For the Black Star Army, as the leader of the private armed forces in the Flickering World, we require you to provide a certain amount of assistance."

"Hmm?" Han Xiao frowned.

The three Universal Civilizations had been trying to get the Beyond Grade A Association to help them deal with the Super Star Clusters, even using the monopoly of Class Knowledges as a bargaining chip, but the union had never agreed. There had not been any unnecessary actions for a period of time, but now it had started once more.

"You should be aware of the results of the Beyond Grade A Union's vote some time ago. I thought we already gave our answer," Han Xiao said.

"That's right. We know that the Beyond Grade A Association plans to abide by its neutral stand, but that is your own agreement, not our request," the Pope drily said.

Urranrell also added, "Black Star, we hope that you'll work with us on this matter."

The Crimson Dynasty originally allocated its territory to the Beyond Grade A allies, hoping that they could contribute at this time. But the development of the union exceeded their expectations, and now, their original allies wished to remain neutral. Of course, they were displeased.

While the territory of the Black Star Army was given as a reward for meritorious service, there was also a motive behind giving it away, and if it could not achieve the effect they wanted, they would not call it quits so easily.

"I thought that we had reached a common consensus on this issue, but it seems that you have misunderstood my position." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

"Don't misunderstand. We understand your intentions, but this is not beyond the scope of our agreement." Bader interjected.

The three Universal Civilizations had created momentum for Black Star because they wished to gain a spokesperson for them within the union. They wished to utilize Han Xiao as a link to influence the entire Development Union. Such a juncture like this would be when the spokesperson came into play—on the Super Star Cluster Alliance's side, they had their Beyond Grade As, so the three Universal Civilizations would not easily allow their allies to go on strike.

"If I do this, I'll deviate from the united front and lose the bigger picture because of small gains." Han Xiao waved his hand.

"Relax, we've taken this into consideration and have chosen an entry point for you…" The Pope leaned forward. "Since you've publicly expressed your personal grievances with the Modo Civilization, just use this as a reason to move a little. You can use these reasonable excuses to get more of the Beyond Grade As to intervene in the storm without damaging your reputation."

"Will it not be damaged just because you say so? Don't start." Han Xiao waved his hands again.

"Then we each take a step back. We will not force you to participate in the event throughout, but if the Super Star Cluster Alliance's Beyond Grade As takes action, I hope that the Development Union will respond. Since you have shouted about regulating all Beyond Grade A conflicts, it should be implemented to the end. This perfectly falls within your jurisdictions."

Han Xiao immediately understood the intentions of the three Universal Civilizations and put on an embarrassed face as he explained, "But in such a situation, those who are willing to help the Super Star Clusters are definitely of their direct line. Since you also have your own direct Beyond Grade As, isn't it appropriate for both direct lines to fight? It will not be suitable for the union to take action as it will make us biased."

Bader deepened his tone in dissatisfaction, "If you put it like this, then what do we need you allies for?"

Han Xiao frowned, and he raised his tone, not ready to be outdone. "If you have the ability, just cancel all the Beyond Grade A ally contracts now."

Bader was rendered speechless.

You're good, I'll shut my mouth now.

Chapter 1149: Eve of the Incident

After rebuking Bader, Han Xiao felt much better.

While he might have become the Special Consultant for the three Universal Civilizations, his previous grudges against the church and the federation had yet to disappear, so being impolite to them felt pretty good.

Seeing this, Urranrell took over and solemnly said, "Black Star, this matter is of utmost importance. I hope that you can assist us in proposing it to the union."

Toward his own ruler, Han Xiao would naturally hold himself back a little. However, he remained firm. "The Development Union should not and cannot favor any party. If we act according to your requirements, when your direct lines step forward, will we need to restrain them as well? Can you accept mediation? If we treat you the same, will you be offended? You understand what I mean. I personally have a reason to deal with the Modo Civilization, so I declared that in advance. This is not against the united front, but it's better for the association itself to remain neutral."

He knew what the three Universal Civilizations were planning. The purpose of the Beyond Grade A Association was to mediate with all Beyond Grade A conflicts. The three Universal Civilizations wished to take advantage of this and turn the association into an indirect third-party ally.

If the Super Star Clusters take out their direct Beyond Grade As, then we will fight you, but if the three Universal Civilizations take out theirs, then we'll pretend we did not see anything.

In this manner, the final result would make people mistake the development union as the dog of the three Universal Civilizations.

Han Xiao naturally would not agree to this. He was the Vice President of the Beyond Grade A Association as well as a common ally of the three Universal Civilizations. His identity now was sensitive, and both sides needed him, so he could not go down the wrong path.

The three Universal Civilizations had an advantage in terms of the number of their Beyond Grade As, so they definitely would not agree to being treated fairly.

Sure enough, after hearing Han Xiao's statement, the leaders rejected the proposal. As a ruler, it was impossible to give an external union a higher law enforcement power than themselves.

The Pope slowly spoke. "Black Star, let us be open. We understand your position very well. The Mechanic Emperor wishes to create opposition, but you are different. You don't wish to separate the Beyond Grade A group from us. It's not as though you are refusing cooperation with us, so we are optimistic that there is actually some room for negotiation. Just say what you want."

"That's right. My aim is to form an cooperative partnership between the Beyond Grade As and the advanced civilizations, not just being your vassals or sheltered under you. As for the premise of equality… you have to at least let go of most of the shackles against the Beyond Grade As, such as the monopoly of Class Knowledge."

"Isn't that what we proposed before? To use the removal of knowledge monopoly as a bargaining chip in exchange for the development union to deal with the Super Star Cluster Alliance, but you refused."

"How should I put it? Using this as a deal is actually a threat or coercion in the eyes of many of the Beyond Grade As. Another purpose of this union is to bring all the Beyond Grade As together and not continue to force them into factional disputes. Thus, most people hope that the three Universal Civilizations will unconditionally let go of many restrictions including the monopoly of knowledge as well as reform the alliance system. Only after this will we then be willing to talk about the new cooperation conditions. This is an issue with the order it is being done…" Han Xiao explained.

The union could technically be likened to a strike, aimed at improving the welfare of the entire class and fighting for better treatment for themselves, so they would be quite united before the benefits were obtained.

"Assuming we do this, what form of new cooperation do you hope to achieve?" The Pope threw the question back.

"To be honest, the opinions within the union have also not been unified as of now, but the majority suggest reducing the nature of allies and strengthening the employment relationship. That is to reduce compulsion and increase our freedom. The cooperative relationship should also be no longer limited to one, and it should be in the form of employer and employee. In addition, we will not be affected by the aftermath between faction battles…"

Han Xiao repeated the expectations of the development union. There were too many twists and turns in this, as the needs of the advanced civilization allies and the free Beyond Grade As were basically different. When different positions fought, it would be difficult to come to a result that everyone was satisfied with.

The three leaders shook their heads. Neither side could make any concessions, so the talks could only come to an end without any common goal reached.

Walking out of the reception room, Han Xiao sighed in resignation.

Following the rise in his position within the universe, the choices he faced every day were becoming increasingly critical. Every decision could have a profound impact on his own development, and if he did not pay attention, it would easily deviate from the tracks he envisioned and become difficult to remedy. Only through experiencing this would one then be able to understand the danger involved.

The moment Han Xiao left, the three leaders shared a glance.

"It seems like there's no need to count on the development union to provide assistance. Black Star was not perfunctory at all. He has a clear conscience when accepting rewards and can reject without feeling guilt at all. Heh, his principles are really strong." Bader sneered.

"Enough. This was not our main objective in building momentum for him as well. This was something we expected. It would be too simple if such a small reward moved a pinnacle Beyond Grade A."

"There's no problem for Black Star to cherish his feathers. We cannot lose sight of our long-term goals just for some short term gains. We still need him to act as a link to guide the development of the union… It's just that their requirements now are still a little whimsical."

"The Beyond Grade As can't be without restrictions. If their shackles are completely removed, it will be a hidden danger in the future."

"We don't have the time to deal with this now. Shelve the negotiations and observe Black Star a little longer. No matter what, having him in the top position is better than the Mechanic Emperor."

…

Under the vigorous propaganda of the three Universal Civilizations, the various Star Fields broadcast the award ceremony, causing extensive discussions among the numerous galactic residents.

Among the hottest topics was Han Xiao himself. Some people thought that the Galaxy Medal he obtained was well-deserved, while others thought that his merits were not great enough when compared with the previous Galaxy Medal winners.

But in any case, the facts could not be changed. If one were to count Han Xiao's deeds of catching EsGod, stopping the disaster, fighting the Mechanic Emperor, and contributing to the stability of the universe, most people would hold a positive attitude.

However, the enthusiasm for the discussion of the award ceremony in galactic society lasted for only a few days before a sudden change attracted the attention of the entire universe.

Just a few days after the end of the award ceremony, the largest armed conflict so far broke out in the free competition zone. Many of the organizations launched attacks on multiple planetary strongholds without warning, as if they had agreed beforehand.

The free competition zone suddenly fell into chaos.

…

Hong long long long!

The earth rumbled continuously, and a series of heavy ground combat vehicles tens of meters high advanced. Wherever they passed, mountains and forests fell, bunkers shattered, and ground defense lines were breached.

Troops of armored soldiers raised their weapons and fired frantically at the intruders. The muzzles ejected intense beams of light. However, a group of vigorous and powerful figures shuttled through the artillery fire, easily decimating the troops. The small team easily shredded the defending front, and the mud thrown up by the vehicles and explosives buried the corpses of the soldiers.

This was a resource-rich planet located in the middle of the free competition zone. It was originally discovered by a vassal Star System level civilization under the three Universal Civilizations, and they established a stronghold here. However, they were ruthlessly attacked today.

Their attacker was a large fleet bearing a common logo of a snowflake shaped emblem with two spears staggered at the bottom. This represented the organization known as 'Northern Battlefront'. Established in the free competition zone, they had no major records, but no one expected them to come and attack a planet occupied by a Star System civilization without warning.

The Northern Battlefront fleet had dispatched tens of thousands of Grade B players as well as a large number of warships and ground combat equipment. It did not take long for the defensive forces of the stronghold to fall into a full retreat as they were unable to withstand the Northern Battlefront's offensive.

This was because the Northern Battlefront was actually a player-formed organization, created by a large number of guilds banding together. They also recruited many solo players with capital, so they had a good foundation to support a certain level of interstellar warfare. After all, they had gone through four versions in Galaxy, so the guild had accumulated quite a lot of money.

There were tens of millions of active players in Galaxy, of which the Black Star Army probably recruited a little more than ten million and was the largest player faction. The rest of the players were scattered among various organizations, with equally large numbers each as the guilds could afford to recruit them.

Within the stronghold was a group of players from the three Universal Civilizations stationed on guard, with probably about one or two hundred of them. However, they were soon overwhelmed by the army and could not withstand the waves of attacks.

A warship of the Northern Battlefront was suspended high in the sky, and within the command room, the leader of the Northern Battlefront looked down on the battlefield with a smile.

"Victory is before us. Quickly deal with the enemies. We still have other strongholds to conquer."

He was the leader of the Northern Battlefront that was jointly elected by the many guilds forming the coalition, and he was responsible for the operation this time. His ID was 'Fire of Northern Sea', and he was the president of a large club in Europe.

"Where shall we hit next?" asked another senior who was part of the guild.

"Whichever is nearest. We'll carve a path for ourselves."

Fire of the Northern Sea waved his hand energetically.

The Northern Battlefront had communicated with the NPC organizations and reached an agreement with the Super Star Cluster Alliance, acting as an agent to help the Super Star Cluster Alliance conquer the various strongholds.

Every time they occupied a stronghold, they would get additional rewards, and they did not even need to struggle in occupying the planets. The Super Star Cluster Alliance was responsible for initiating the war, and the high resource sharing provided to them was equivalent to a steady stream of funds. At the same time, the Super Star Cluster Alliance would provide resource support to them during the campaign, such as material purchase discounts and other benefits.

It was not just the Northern Battlefront; even the Galactic Business Alliance and the 5C Alliance, other player made alliances, had also reached an agreement with the Super Star Cluster Alliance to temporarily fight for them.

The conflict between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance was an open secret, and the Super Star Cluster Alliance would not be afraid of the three Universal Civilizations and the Black Star Army like the smaller factions. The clubs of various countries saw this opportunity and hopped on the bandwagon to participate in this national war.

Them starting a national war was not just for entertainment but more for profit.

By doing so, they could utilize this channel to cozy up to someone powerful such as the Super Star Clusters, recruit more players through the wars and strengthen their organization, and obtain resources. Furthermore, they would fulfil the main storyline of faction war and perform some off-field preparations for the Pro League this season, easing the dominance those in the Black Star Army had.

And now, due to the Super Star Cluster Alliance being the preemptive one, the Northern Battlefront and the other guild alliances took the chance to attack and expand their territory in the free competition zone for the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

Fire of Northern Sea opened the star map, watching the real-time expansion of the Super Star Cluster Alliance's territory in the free competition zone as he excitedly clenched his fists.

"This is an unprecedented event. The Black Star Army has too great an advantage in the Flickering World. Only if the Super Star Cluster Alliance wins will we be able to turn the tides and obtain equivalent resources to them!"

…

This similar war scene appeared on multiple planets in the free competition zones. In addition to the player alliances, other private armed organizations also robbed territory for the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

Around 2,400 planets were invaded on the same day, most of which were resource rich planets, transportation hubs, or other strategic locations. At the fourth exploration phase, the maps were basically complete, and the Super Star Cluster Alliance could accurately select the high value targets.

Facing the sudden problem created by the Super Star Cluster Alliance, everyone was left shocked!

"Galaxy Chronicles—The First World Server War

"On February 25, 732, the three Universal Civilizations held an award ceremony for Black Star, awarding him the Galaxy Medal.

"On February 29, 732, a large-scale armed invasion broke out in the free competition zone of the Flickering World. The Super Star Cluster Alliance instructed multiple armed organizations to expand their territory, which eventually became the fuse for official conflict between them and the three Universal Civilizations. This was the prelude to a national war and went down in history as 'Eve of the Incident'."

Chapter 1150: Anti-Trust Regulations, Main Storyline of Counterfeiting

In the free competition zone, Emerald Star Cluster, Planet Rosende…

This was a resource rich planet located within the inner ring of the Star Cluster. It was occupied early on by a Star Cluster level civilization named 'Thunder Horn'. They had transformed it into a temporary base camp for their exploration army, and the planet was heavily guarded and well stocked with materials and troops.

Right at this moment, the leaders of the Thunder Horn Civilization Exploration army were gathered in the conference room of the headquarters.

"The two stronghold planets in the central region were invaded successively and breached by the different organizations employed by the Super Star Cluster Alliance. What are your thoughts?"

The chief commander pressed his hands on the table, his sharp eyes looking at all the officers present.

Bang!

A high-ranking commander with a bristly beard slammed the table as he angrily shouted, "Is there still a need for discussion? Immediately gather manpower for a crusade! My troops are guarding one of the strongholds, and they have been almost completely wiped out. We must fight back!"

Another tall and thin officer with a calmer temperament stroked the lightning-shaped blue horns on his head. This action was similar to a human stroking his beard. He slowly said, "I feel we should wait and see for now. The Super Star Cluster Alliance's actions have a strategic intention behind. Even if we take our stronghold back, we will be attacked once more. Furthermore, the central region is currently in chaos due to the trouble caused by the Super Star Cluster Alliance, and it's too dangerous to hold onto our land."

Now that the fourth exploration phase had been completed, the four Star Clusters in the free competition zone were divided into regions, with dozens to hundreds of Star Systems for each Star Cluster. According to their locations, they were divided into the outer edge area, inner ring area, central area, and finally the core area for a total of four layers.

At present, the main strategic goal of the Super Star Cluster Alliance was to completely control the core and central areas, having a stable rear base that could allow them to utilize space transmission methods such as stargates to maintain their supply and transportation channels.

While this would cause them to be completely surrounded, there was no other way for the Super Star Cluster Alliance. Since guerrilla tactics were not suitable for them, they could only resort to sieging tactics.

"Then, what are we going to do? Are we going to obediently pass the stronghold to them and let my men die in vain‽" The hot tempered bristly beard lashed out.

"Chief commander?" The calm officer turned his head. "I believe your thoughts align with mine."

The Chief commander looked up when he heard this and replied, "I'm also in favor of waiting. The situation now is not clear."

"They've already started fighting. What's not clear about that?" the hot-tempered officer shouted.

The Chief commander patiently explained, "In this storm, we're not the main characters. The three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance are the true protagonists and chess players. While the fourth exploration phase is called the free competition zone, we're only forces that have come to pan for gold and occupy land, the chess pieces that took the initiative to enter the chessboard. We are far from being able to influence the overall direction, so we must wait for the three Universal Civilizations to respond."

"So, we have to count on the three Universal Civilizations to take action for our forces in trouble, to start a war against the Super Star Cluster Alliance, huh?"

"Of course not, the three Universal Civilizations will not enter the fray so easily. After all, the principle of the free competition zone has not been torn apart yet. The Super Star Cluster Alliance has employed so many people. Other than strengthening itself, it was also to stick to the rules of the game. Everyone would use their agents to compete, and it will reach a more intense level once the two armies start fighting officially. However, this is not the time yet."

The calm officer nodded. "That's right. Chess pieces like us can only wait for the orders of the players. When the three Universal Civilizations show a reaction will be when we choose our sides, then we will no longer be alone and will have a large number of teammates."

The other senior officers also nodded.

While they were unwilling to be pawns, the moment they chose to enter the free competition zone, it was tantamount to them consenting to being in the game. This was the rule formulated by the three Universal Civilizations. Of course, there would also be no shortage of benefits. Only by being a pawn could they obtain the benefits of the Flickering World, and how much they got depended on their ability.

Beep beep beep…

At this moment, a virtual screen popped up at the center of the conference table. On it was an announcement issued by the three Universal Civilizations to the entire universe. The title jumped out in everyone's eyes.

"Supplementary Regulations on Anti-Monopoly within the Flickering World Fourth Exploration Phase."

It's here!

The eyes of the Chief commander flashed, and all of them immediately read the report.

The content of this announcement could be roughly summarized into a few points. Firstly, it defined the Eve of the Incident as the beginning of malicious competition and monopolization, and they believed that the Super Star Cluster Alliance was violating the 'Regulations on Free Exploration'. Secondly, it ordered the Super Star Cluster Alliance to immediately stop the malicious expansion behavior, strongly condemning them on behalf of the civilizations in the universe. Thirdly, if the Super Star Cluster Alliance still did not repent, they would begin sanctions and redistribute the territory occupied by the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

In the appendix of the announcement, there were plans to implement the sanctions and redistribution. The Crimson Dynasty and the other two universal civilizations expressed that they were unwilling to destroy the 'Free Exploration Regulations', so they encouraged the organizations and forces in the free competition zone to launch a siege against the Super Star Cluster Alliance. They would then be given special support based on merit.

At the same time, in their distribution plan, they stated that they would not reclaim the planets that the various forces snatched from the Super Star Cluster Alliance. As a reward for helping them against the Super Star Cluster Alliance, they would reclaim their territory as appropriate after the event… In short, they were dangling a carrot to draw forces to attack the Super Star Cluster Alliance and increase the difficulty of the latter to woo agents over to their side.

One could either choose the three Universal Civilizations or the Super Star Cluster Alliance. There was no third option. If one wished to stay neutral, the end result would be to see their territory gradually being eroded away by the Super Star Cluster Alliance. This was also the scheme of the three Universal Civilizations, as they were confident that no one would silently get robbed.

And in the one in ten million possibility that people really chose to give up their territory than to get involved in the storm, the three Universal Civilizations would just send regular troops into the area, and after going through the Super Star Cluster Alliance, they would no longer reallocate the territory back to the other forces, instead occupying it.

As for the third party Beyond Grade A organizations, they were a special existence within this storm. Only they had the capital to remain neutral, and at the same time, the three Universal Civilizations as well as the Super Star Cluster Alliances would avoid their territory to a certain extent.

This was the influence brought about by the establishment of the Development Union, which was different from the trend in his past life. The butterfly effect had already begun to take effect!

Of course, this was based on the premise that the majority of the Beyond Grade As would keep to watching as much as possible. Their forces could also take the opportunity to expand, but taking advantage of this battle had to be controlled to a degree.

"An insidious strategy." The chief commander coldly snorted before suddenly increasing his volume. "Have the organization leave with the fleet for the central area. The time is right. We now have enough indirect allies."

Everyone stood up, giving a military salute.

"Understood!"

Meanwhile, at the Black Star Army's frontline stronghold in the Emerald Star Cluster, the outbreak caused an uproar among the army players. A large number took to the frontlines to explore, causing the dining hall to be filled with a wave of black as all the players in combat uniforms gathered.

"What's happening? I went for a business trip a few days ago and didn't come online, but how did the world change so drastically? What are these guild alliances doing?"

"The Super Star Cluster Alliance wants to unify the free competition zone, but how did the Northern Battlefront and the Galactic Business Alliance come on board?"

"I read the forums, and they seemed to have gotten the main storyline mission from the Super Star Cluster Alliance."

"But we don't have a related mission. Does that mean that you have to be in the Super Star Cluster Alliance faction in order to obtain the mission?"

"That might not be so. Haven't some people analyzed the current situation? The three Universal Civilizations will definitely not let this slip. Since we're in the Black Star Army, we should naturally stand on the side of the three Universal Civilizations."

Just as everyone was discussing the matter, the announcement of the three Universal Civilizations popped up on the floating screen in the main hall, attracting everyone's attention.

After reading the report, the atmosphere started to heat up once more.

"Haha, see what I said. Such a huge plot cannot just be a unilateral main storyline."

"So, this is a faction war, with the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Clusters on opposite sides?"

"We're going to fight a national war!"

The players were excited.

But after a while, their interface still remained silent, leading to everyone feeling confused.

"This can't be. Didn't they say it was a faction battle? How are we not involved in the main storyline?"

"Could it be that we have to trigger it ourselves? But who do we look for?"

"We're members of the army, so maybe we have to wait for the army to issue an official announcement for the mission?"

Just when everyone was in a state of uncertainty, the Phillip subprogram on everyone's communicator suddenly popped up, issuing a notice.

Black Star Army Expedition Order.

In view of the contradiction between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance, the army has decided to carry out an armed crusade against the Modo Civilization Exploration Force. The reasons are detailed in the appendix 'Kunde Civilization' (Expand/Collapse). Only the Modo Civilization will be targeted, and there is no need to bother about the other Super Star Cluster Alliance Civilizations. If there are any forces that prevent our actions, you are allowed to retaliate. The primary strategic goal is to expel and kill the Modo Civilization and its affiliated organizations. All troops cannot deviate from this strategy.

As soon as the announcement popped out, a mission notice was seen on the interface of all the players present.

Except for the specific requirement, there was no difference from the main storyline missions obtained by the Super Star Cluster Alliance players.

Seeing this, many of them smiled with joy.

"That's right. We really need the army to issue an announcement before we can activate the main storyline mission."

"So, there's a grudge between the Modo Civilization and us?"

"Sigh, one look and you're the sort that did not read the background story of the version update. The Modo Civilization conspired to use the Kunde Race in the Flickering World to annihilate everyone. They're such low people and deserve to be beaten up."

The countless army players could not wait to immediately enter the central area.

However, what they were unaware of was that the task they triggered was actually problematic and was not the main storyline of the battle between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

The ordinary vassals of the three Universal Civilizations or Super Star Cluster Alliance mercenaries would not specify which civilization to fight; the players would improve their Mission Rating so long as they helped their forces expand.

The missions for the army players, while in the same model, was simply to attack the Modo Civilization.

Because of the united front, the Black Star Army and the other Beyond Grade As could not respond to the call of the Crimson Dynasty and did not have the initiative to get involved in the storm. Thus, the army players would not have the main storyline of the fighting between the two factions!

"It's all thanks to my wit…"

Han Xiao secretly breathed a sigh of relief when he saw the excited reactions of the players on the forums.

As early as when the development union required all its members to be neutral, Han Xiao had guessed that the Black Star Army would not be able to join the main storyline of the battle between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance. As the vice president, if he wished to maintain his status and power, he had to be subject to the collective resolution of the united front.

He had guessed the follow-up impact at that time and thus deliberately left the Modo Civilization as a goal so that the three Universal Civilizations and development union would feel that this was a private vendetta.

In this manner, he could justifiably imitate a war mission and make the army players mistakenly treat it as the main storyline. While the mission was simpler than the actual main storyline, the players could only accept it.

If there was not even a counterfeit main storyline, then the large number of players would be disappointed and might even switch factions to participate in the national war. There was no doubt about it. After this mission release, the negative impact would be minimized. While the specific missions were different, at least they would be able to enter the national war, which was enough for most players.

At the same time, this could show a contrast with the other Beyond Grade A organizations. Most of them would not be able to participate in the main storyline, but the Black Star Army had a fake main storyline. This would attract some players from the other factions to switch over to his side.

On the other hand, the players in the national wars during his previous life had a lot of room for free play. While they got to fight side by side, it also meant they just waged their own wars without caring for each other. The main point of him creating the main storyline was to integrate all his players to go against the Modo Civilization, having a greater chance to complete the mission [Kunde Race Leader's Last Wish]!

In this manner, the hidden danger was basically solved.

"United front, united front…" Han Xiao muttered helplessly.

Right now, the united front had become a new shackle to him. While it could be maintained at present, as this clause affected the interests of more members, problems would inevitably rise. It was estimated that the three Universal Civilizations also had plans to drag down the unity of the Beyond Grade A group.

To be honest, as far as he was concerned, he felt that the chance of reaching an agreement between both the development union and the three Universal Civilizations was low. There was a strong conflict of interest between the two sides' demands.

As far as the union was concerned, because of their different needs, the collective resolutions drawn currently were naturally not the best plan. It could only be said that it was a plan that no one strongly opposed.

The development union wanted the three Universal Civilizations to unconditionally lift the monopoly of knowledge, before talking about other cooperation. In the eyes of the Beyond Grade As, this was a reasonable request because their current source of Ultimate Knowledge was obtained through meritorious service. They had paid enough for many years and collected all the Ultimate Knowledges, but they were not allowed to pass it on to others.

Only by breaking the monopoly of the three Universal Civilizations could the shackles of their factions be lifted. In this manner, the union itself would be responsible for the spread of knowledge, so current and future Beyond Grade As would no longer need to work for the three Universal Civilizations to obtain Ultimate Knowledge. After all, most people were originally not citizens of the three Universal Civilizations and had no responsibility toward them. In this manner, those who wished to join the three Universal Civilizations would only be looking for a strong backer and not for an ulterior motive.

However, Han Xiao knew that the chances of the three Universal Civilizations allowing this was slim.

Unconditional? Even he himself thought that this was bullsh*t!

But as the Vice President, he had an obligation to convey the collective resolutions, and at the same time, he could not represent so many people to make claims, so he could only convey the meaning of the association truthfully.

Based on Han Xiao's own ideas, it was not a bad option to agree to the deal proposed by the three Universal Civilizations, which was to deal with the Super Star Cluster Alliance in exchange for them lifting the monopoly on knowledge. However, many of them disagreed. Firstly, they did not wish to undermine their original intention, and secondly, they did not wish to take the risk to get involved in this turmoil. Everyone had a different viewpoint and position… If the two sides remained in this deadlock, Han Xiao concluded that the final result would be that the Beyond Grade A Association would not be able to bear it and start imparting knowledge privately, which would give the three Universal Civilizations an excuse to attack them.

"This is difficult… but it's nothing to me." Han Xiao shook his head.

First of all, he had already obtained his Ultimate Knowledges. In fact, he did not care about the problem of the monopoly of knowledge.

Secondly, he knew where the turning point of this matter would be, so he did not care about the problems exposed at this moment.

"Wait till the Calamity of the Supers or the World Tree appears, then I'll be able to break the existing pattern. Now is not the time… Speaking of which, I'm not sure if the Holy Accord has succeeded yet."

Han Xiao smirked.

Temporarily dropping this thought, he picked up his communicator to give someone a call.

In the turmoil caused by the Super Star Cluster Alliance, the Beyond Grade As would mostly not be involved, but there would be a small number of people involved in their own private affairs. One of them would definitely be Sorokin.

Their interests were in line this time, and perhaps they could work together quietly this time to turn the Modo Civilization into pigskins.

Furthermore, Han Xiao already had a bold guess about Sorokin's identity.

"Now's a good time to verify it…"

Chapter 1151: Little Kid Soro, You've Revealed Yourself!

In the Limitless Financial Group's Flickering World branch, a huge virtual star map was suspended in the center of the top-level office, and the picture showed the current pattern of the free competition zone. The Super Star Cluster Alliance was occupying a large majority of the core and central areas of the four Star Clusters. Their territory was represented by the red dye spreading and encroaching upon the blue area representing the other forces.

Sorokin stood with his hand propping up his head, staring at the star map as his eyes flickered.

"After this Crimson Tide, the advanced civilization conflict will affect the structure of the entire universe… There will be business opportunities everywhere!"

After solving the problem of Traveler, the Limitless Financial Group turned back to hug the thighs of the federation and the church once more. As such, they definitely had to contribute toward this turmoil, and at the same time, this was a reasonable opportunity for him to make a fortune in war. As the head of the financial group, Sorokin would definitely not miss it.

"The middleman during the war can promote the business of selling materials, arms, and other resources. Those forces standing on the side of the three Universal Civilizations will definitely need to replenish their materials. This is the number one business opportunity… but it's only a small profit. The true profits are outside of the chessboard, and I also need admission tickets. I should be eligible though…"

Sorokin was muttering to himself, feeling a little excited.

If he could obtain the real benefits of this incident, the size of the Limitless Financial Group could move up again, and a skyrocketing share price would not be a dream.

Beep beep!

Just as he was fantasizing, his personal communicator rang. It was a call from Black Star.

Seeing the caller, Sorokin's expression changed.

He subconsciously trembled a little upon seeing Han Xiao's name now.

But he quickly adjusted his mood, putting on his signature smile as he answered the call.

"Your Excellency Black Star, my dear partner, why have you contacted me today?"

"I have a cooperation deal." Han Xiao did not beat around the bush. "The conflict between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Clusters has finally broken out, and it's my chance to settle accounts with the Modo Civilization. Everyone knows that I'll deal with Modo Civilization, so we should have the same interests here, right?"

Sorokin's eyes gleamed as he smiled. "That's right. Ignoring my relationship with the federation and the church, Traveler sold me out, so he and the Modo Civilization have a debt to settle with me."

He still thought that the Modo Civilization was the backer of Traveler. He completely believed the lie Han Xiao weaved at the beginning and had decided to settle his accounts with Modo Civilization.

"Since we have the same goal this time, there's a basis for cooperation. You're a commercial organization and are not suitable to intervening in armed conflict. Thus, I need you to provide funds and materials on a large scale, okay?"

"The Black Star Army's influence in the Flickering World is much larger than mine, and you still need me to supply war funds?" Sorokin raised his brow.

"The more, the merrier. I'll never find them enough." Han Xiao did not feel embarrassed at all.

While he was not lacking in funds, it was definitely more comfortable to spend the money of others than his own.

Sorokin gritted his teeth in secret, cursing his shamelessly while his smile remained unchanged. "Yep, I'm happy to fund your war activities against the Modo Civilization."

"I'll ask the clerk to send a list of supplies over later. Just follow it."

"…Okay." Sorokin gritted his teeth.

"There's another thing. With your foresight, you must have seen the new business opportunities."

Sorokin hesitated a little, having a bad premonition. "You mean…"

"Stop pretending. The conflict between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance reaches everywhere. Although the free competition zone is the target of competition, the three Universal Civilizations will not just gaze there and will inevitably open up a second front to turn the tides. They will target the foundations of the Super Star Clusters in the explored universe through putting political, economic, and other sanctions to pressure them… and here are the huge business opportunities."

The Flickering World was the center of the storm, and the main stage of the armed conflict. However, there would be another battlefield outside this chessboard, which was the three Universal Civilizations exerting pressure on the Super Star Clusters themselves, making them too tired to cope, which indirectly served as a way for the Super Star Cluster to give up their advantages in the free competition zone as soon as possible.

This business opportunity lay in the economic sanctions. Targeted by the three Universal Civilizations, the business community of the Super Star Clusters would experience turbulence, and a large number of companies would be unluckily hit. This was a good opportunity for other universal financial groups to enter the market, biting off a piece of meat from the Super Star Clusters.

The Limitless Financial Group was close to the three Universal Civilizations, and being a top financial group would naturally give them the qualifications to enter the market and feast on it. Han Xiao was eyeing this opportunity, preparing to take a share.

At the same time, this plan would also better allow him to complete the mission of the Kunde Race.

The remaining mission requirement was for him to cause huge losses to the Modo Civilization. Killing the opponent's army was one way, and destroying the financial stability of the Modo Civilization was another direction.

Moreover, the scene of the death of the Kunde Race leader was still vivid to him. From an emotional point of view, Han Xiao also wished to beat Modo as badly as possible.

Sorokin was a little unwilling. "I haven't decided to intervene yet. Besides, you're already a guest of the three Universal Civilizations and can enter the venue without me. Why use my channels?"

"Your channels are more suitable." Han Xiao smiled without any shame.

While the Germinal Financial Group under his banner could independently enter the market, compared with the Limitless Financial Group, his business scope was still a lot smaller. It would not be as easy as utilizing the Limitless Financial Group's channels. In this way, not only could he borrow someone's strength to develop, he would also not feel the pinch.

Of course, for Sorokin, this was akin to grabbing his business. He felt as though he had swallowed a fly, and he felt an urge to command his factory to begin manufacturing punching bags with Black Star's face on them so that he could vent his frustrations.

"That's not too good…"

Sorokin was unwilling and wanted to avoid the request.

However, Han Xiao's tone suddenly changed, becoming more subtle.

"Speaking of which, I recently found a historical figure that interested me when I was looking up information."

Sorokin was taken aback for a moment, wondering why Han Xiao changed the topic all of a sudden.

He suppressed his impatience and pretended to be curious. "Who?"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, staring interestedly at Sorokin as he spoke.

"Rovell Sissock, one of the Primordial Ones with the name of Soul Emperor. Have you heard of him before?"

"… I have, but why has he aroused your interest?"

"Oh, I was collecting Primal Esper Ability Entities a while ago, and this one called the Soul Flame caught my attention. When I checked its information, I found out that its last host was someone called the Soul Emperor. It didn't matter much to me, but not long after, I happened to run into the current host of the Soul Flame, and he told me some astonishing news. It turns out that the Primordial Soul Emperor did not die in a war as the data showed. His soul managed to escape, and he hid himself. Due to his special ability, he might just have survived to the present day… and I also discovered that his ability is very similar to yours. Don't you think it's magical?"

"Haha, it's just a coincidence… but a Primordial One that's survived to this day? It's really a bit powerful."

"I agree. I feel that it's a coincidence… Yes, let's get back on topic. We're working together to intervene in this matter, and it's actually a win-win situation. Isn't it good to get a larger share together?"

"Oh, that makes sense. Alright, you've convinced me. We'll put it as such. When the time comes, I'll open up the channels to help the Germinal Financial Group enter the venue."

"Haha, I wish us a happy cooperation, and I won't continue to disturb you."

"Alright, to a happy cooperation."

The moment the call ended, the smile on Sorokin's face vanished.

Ka-cha!

An electric spark flashed as the communicator was crushed into a piece of scrap iron.

"This guy has discovered my secret!"

Sorokin looked suspicious.

'Soul Emperor' Rovell Sissock was indeed his earliest identity!

Although he did not reveal anything when he spoke just now, a storm was actually brewing in his heart.

Were it not for his psychological qualities, Sorokin would not have been so calm after someone had called out his previous identity, and his expression would have revealed the answer.

Sorokin did not believe that Black Star was absolutely certain of being able to see through his identity. It had to be because of some certain intelligence he had that allowed him to make an association, so he asked to test him out.

With so much time in between, he had already gone through many identities. The other party could not possibly have real evidence on him.

Just purely from an identity viewpoint, it did not matter even if he knew that Sorokin was the Soul Emperor. He had no grudge nor grievance with the Soul Emperor identity. Even if there were any enemies, they had long since disappeared in the long river of history.

What Sorokin was afraid of was the chain reaction caused by the exposure of his identity. If the three Universal Civilizations and Beyond Grade As knew that he was actually a Primordial One who had survived to this day, they would definitely be jealous. Then, how could he maintain his weak image, continuing to be a pig to eat a tiger?

Furthermore, he was quite sure that he was the only Primordial One who had survived so far. The three Universal Civilizations would definitely move when they heard the news. Just thinking about it made him shiver.

Now that the bargaining chips were in Han Xiao's hands, Sorokin could only accept Han Xiao's proposal, much to his chagrin.

"While Black Star does not have any proof on his hands, if I allow him to continue his investigation, he'll definitely find out all the identities I've used before…"

Sorokin's expression changed slightly.

The identity of Soul Emperor being blown was okay, since it was a positive one, but the other identities he had used were not so clean.

It was to the point that when the Beyond Grade As had received a cleansing, his shadow was behind it!

While any traces were practically cleaned up over the years, if someone managed to uncover it, the consequences would be unimaginable!

Right now, he only wished to let Black Star think that the Soul Emperor identity was enough to blackmail him, so he would not pursue it any further.

"Even if I change my identity again, there'll always be a risk for exposure. Only by getting rid of Black Star can I get it over and done with…"

Sorokin's expression was uncertain.

Chapter 1152: The Worrying Cancer of the Universe

When the anti-monopoly regulations of the three Universal Civilizations were released, the effect was akin to war mobilization. The four Star Clusters making up the free competition zone began to surge as all the watching forces made their choices.

Only a small number of forces were unwilling to get involved, and they thus reluctantly gave up on their investment that had lasted for several years, withdrawing from the competition. Most of the forces were unwilling to get out, and they deployed forces to stand on the three Universal Civilizations' factions, engaging the agents of the Super Star Cluster Alliance in frontal battles within the inner and central ring Star Clusters.

Just like how the civilizations predicted earlier, when the fourth exploration phase was close to being completely over, the trend of free development would gradually reverse to frequent armed looting. With the outbreak of large-scale conflicts, the flames of war spread rapidly. Under the attention of the entire universe, the free competition zone entered a state of war.

The armed forces of the majority of organizations launched a blockade, immediately curbing the expansion trend for the Super Star Cluster Alliance. The four Star Clusters opened up countless battle fronts, in which the stronghold planets on the edge of each faction's territory continued to repeat the process of losing and recovering, appearing on the map as though sharp teeth were constantly chomping up and down.

The Emerald Star Cluster was divided into fourteen battle zones, most of which were located in the inner and central ring regions. The bridgehead of the Super Star Cluster Alliances scattered in the outer edge area was under the most intense siege, with their strongholds quickly falling.

However, the majority of people present just wished to seize more territory. Thus, the intensity of the war was still under control, where everyone tacitly banned the use of Planetary Obliteration weapons, focusing mainly on their fleets and surface combat. After all, if they blew the planet up, there would be no territory left to grab. Thus, the surface combat weapons and the role of Supers were very important.

The large-scale war also represented the rapid depletion of battleships, ammunition, weapons, and equipment. Demand determined the market and gave a large number of opportunities to the financial groups to make money during wartime.

The financial groups in the Flickering World sold various war resources. This included the Black Star Army's Germinal Financial Group whose orders were skyrocketing. The logistics department's assembly line was in full operation, shipping boxes of arms to the free competition zone.

On the other side, at Han Xiao's order, the armed forces of the army assembled at the army's frontline exploration stronghold, attacking the Ferdinand Star System, where the Modo Civilization was located.

At present, the regular forces of the Super Star Cluster Alliance had yet to be activated, and their agent forces were used as the outer defense lines. The Black Star Army's forces advanced straight, deep into the defense line, exchanging fire with the agents belonging to the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

…

In the inner ring sector of the Emerald Star Cluster, a stronghold on the edge of the Super Star Cluster Alliance was attacked by a large armed organization under the Super Star Cluster Alliance, and their main force was temporarily stationed there.

And today, this planet was raided by the advanced forces of Black Star.

With the stronghold as the center, a hemispherical sky-blue energy shield was inverted on the surface, covering tens of millions of kilometers. Above the shield was an intense interstellar war. The defense fleet was struggling to resist the attack of the Black Star Army's fleet, slowly being smashed to pieces.

Small spaceships acted like hummingbirds, wandering throughout the crisscrossing light cannons in the battlefield, up and down, left and right, using thrilling maneuvers to avoid the artillery fire while shooting their assault capsules from time to time, smashing through the enemy battleships. The capsules would penetrate deep into the ship's armor to help the players land on the enemy ship.

The blue tail flames of the rear thrusters from the heavy assault battleship formation left traces of light on the dark battlefield, shining as though they were a swarm of meteors. Supported by the powerful dark matter engine, the assault ship array chopped through the formation of the enemy, tearing the defense fleet into pieces. Bit by bit, they shattered the enemy's coordinated defense.

With the Army Commander being one of the best Mechanics in the universe, the ship manufacturing technology of the logistics department was naturally outstanding. The performance and firepower advantage of their battleships were similarly dominant. The dense energy beam easily penetrated the defensive lines of the stronghold defenders and hit the protective shield like a torrential downpour, creating a series of cobweb-like glowing cracks.

In the headquarters of the shaking ground base, the atmosphere was extremely tense, and the base commander stared at the durability of the shield anxiously.

"The reinforcements aren't here yet?"

"Commander, the other allies are unwilling to fight against the Black Star Army, and they refuse to come to our rescue. Only the nearest Modo Civilization has sent troops, and they are coming through the Hyperdrive Base Station at the moment."

"Damn it, these b*stards… Notify each captain that they cannot allow the Black Star Army to break into our base! Once they send in their immortals en masse, we're finished!" the base commander screamed.

The nickname for the players, the Cancer of the Universe, had spread throughout the galaxy, and they were unanimously known as the King of Ground Warfare. If a battle was maintained within a fleet, they could hold out for a period of time. However, the moment the Immortals broke through the ground defense line, there would only be one outcome: a one-sided defeat.

Faced with the Cancer of the Universe—who were not afraid of death, could resurrect, and disregarded their lives—there was no soldier that would not feel jealous. When confronted with such an opponent, no matter how many casualties the enemy created, it was useless. The ground army would have no morale to go to war.

There was no need to even mention the tens of millions of Immortals that the Black Star Army sat on. Now that they were rushing toward the battle zone controlled by the Modo Civilization, it was basically a walking meat grinder.

Even the agent forces of the Super Star Cluster Alliance hurriedly stayed away from the direction the Black Star Army was taking out of fear, not daring to obstruct them. Their goal was clear; they were there just for Modo, and no one wanted to waste their troops for nothing.

"Commander, the durability of the base's protective shield has fallen below twenty percent. Three of our energy furnaces have overheated and are expected to break in eleven minutes and twenty-seven seconds. Please give instructions!" the operation team leader said in a flustered tone.

The base commander gritted his teeth while looking at the retreating fleet. "Prepare the reserve fleet to take off at any time to seize air supremacy. Preheat all anti-aircraft turrets and activate all missile wells. The moment the shield is broken, fire immediately. All Machinery divisions, armored divisions, and Supers, get ready for ground combat…"

A series of orders were issued, and the soldiers and vehicles quickly got in position, looking up at the battlefield in outer space. From time to time, soldiers could be heard gulping nervously in the communication channel.

In this tense atmosphere, every second seemed like a year. Under the horrified gazes of the base soldiers, the blue shield covering their heads exploded into light motes.

The next moment, a series of whistling sounded ensued.

Pew! Pew! Pew!

Airdrop capsules with shields passed through the net of firepower, dropping down one by one onto various locations within the base, emitting white smoke.

The moment the hatch slid open, teams of heavily-armed Grade B players stepped onto the ground, blatantly charging toward the ground troops.

The quickly approaching Immortals looked akin to the Devil himself in the eyes of the base soldiers. They mustered up their courage and rushed up with an angry roar.

Boom!

Two torrents on the ground clashed!

The Grade B realm was already considered the backbone of the universe, and the moment they came into contact, the more than a hundred thousand players smashed the armored divisions onto the ground, frontally crushing them. The vehicles piled up or exploded, the light of the flames flickering off the players' mechanical suits.

The player waves swallowed the area one after another, flooding the battlefield composed of steel and flesh, causing huge casualties.

It was not that there were no players besieged to death, but the troops of the base saw that every player who they tried their best to kill was resurrected on the battlefield the next moment. Their work was an act of futility.

Despair took hold of every soldier's heart, and the seeds of fear blossomed, forming their deepest nightmare.

Very quickly, the first soldier whose mentality collapsed fled in a panic. This was akin to a signal that caused more to desert their troops and run.

"They're all devils!"

"This is a losing battle. Just run!"

"I don't want to die!"

Desperate shouts rang out from the communication channel, and the base's defenses quickly collapsed.

The base command originally wished to go into battle to inspire morale but was shot with a super long-ranged concentrated energy projectile by a Cannon Master and was immediately turned to ash.

At this moment, the cosmos not far from the planet flashed, and the support fleet of the Modo Civilization appeared at the warp point. Seeing the state of the battle, they knew that it was too far gone.

"We've arrived too late. They've already been attacked by the Cancer of the Universe. There's no saving them."

The captain ordered the fleet to turn around immediately.

…

Bang!

The conference table was pounded hard.

"Tell me, how do we deal with the Black Star Army?" Roddick, the Commander of the Modo Civilization Expedition Fleet, was furious. His roar echoed throughout the conference room.

Before the war, the Black Star Army could not attack the Modo Civilization alone due to the help of the Super Star Cluster Alliance. But now that the latter was too occupied with its own war, this was the best time to start.

This was supposed to be the surrogate war phase, where the Super Star Clusters would only watch the situation, but because of the Black Star Army, the Modo Civilization had to move out in advance, losing their qualification to wait and watch. They had fallen into a disadvantage.

"Most of our allies are unwilling to fight head-on with the Black Star Army. We can only resist it personally, not allowing him to enter our territory."

"The other Super Star Clusters will not sit back and watch our line of defense being breached. They will provide support."

"Even so, their support will be limited. The goal of the Black Star Army is clear—us, and us alone. Everyone is worried that intervening too much will cause the Black Star Army to drag them down as well."

Everyone discussed their thoughts in low volumes, and the atmosphere in the room was gloomy.

If it was any other armed organization, the problem was not that serious. After all, the Modo Civilization was still a Super Star Cluster Civilization and had sufficient armed forces.

However, with the current limitation to the war intensity, Supers were very important. The Immortals of the Black Star Army were too devious. Even if they could stop the Immortals for a while, they would not be able to withstand the casualties.

"We can only let the Immortals deal with other Immortals. We have also recruited many Immortal organizations. As long as they are given enough money, they can be dispatched to resist the Black Star Army," Lagos proposed.

"We can only do this for now."

It was a loss for them to take out their normal Supers, whom they had painstakingly cultivated, to fight against the players. Only Immortals could fight against Immortals.

Roddick was gloomy. "Unfortunately, we'll need to force the Black Star Army to withdraw if we want to get out of this situation."

"What should we do, reconcile with Black Star?"

"That's impossible." Roddick decisively shook his head. "Only by getting rid of Black Star himself will the army fall apart… Unfortunately, it's not possible for us."

"Well then, if we change the direction, it's okay to cause Black Star some trouble so that he has no time to take care of us."

"You have a plan?"

"Not at the moment," Lagos shook his head thoughtfully. "But I may have a way to deal with Black Star…"

Chapter 1153: Arrangements

Roddick's eyes flashed, and he asked, "What's your idea?"

"What do you think Black Star's weakness is?" Lagos beat around the bush.

Hearing this, everyone fell into deep thought.

"Black Star has amazing strength. His fleshy body is tough, his foundation is huge, and his influence is at the peak…" Roddick's expression was unsightly. "I can't think of any weakness."

"I'll rephrase, what does Black Star care about?"

"His troops? But we can't shake his foundation at all… His mother planet? It's heavily protected. There's no way to strike, and this sort of small problem is not enough to make Black Star feel overwhelmed… His officers? As far as I know, all important members of the Black Star Army are equipped with the transmission device similar to a Multi-Dimensional Sky Opening Transportation Device, which cannot be blocked. It's impossible to threaten Black Star with this…"

The more Roddick spoke, the more he despaired. In his opinion, unless the upper echelons intended to encircle and suppress Black Star without considering the casualties, there was nothing that they could do to the opponent.

Lagos shook his head.

"Black Star is indeed powerful, but we're overthinking it. Get rid of your inner doubts and re-examine him. There are still some ways to achieve our goal, which could be divided into direct and indirect routes."

Hope welled up back in Roddick. Over the past few years within the free competition zone, Black Star had become a tumor to him. "Hurry and explain."

"The direct route is simple. Start with Black Star himself. While you cannot destroy his body, his soul is definitely not as tough as his Indestructible Body."

After hearing this, Roddick was immediately discouraged. "So what? Even if Black Star's soul is relatively weak, it's not something we can target. You should at least be at the level of a pinnacle Beyond Grade A to affect him."

"No, no, no, look at this file."

Lagos swiped his finger on the virtual screen, releasing a confidential file.

Glancing over, Roddick muttered to himself, "Marwell Project File, Number 023, Project name: [Soul Swap Twins]… What's this?"

"This is a confidential file sent to me by the superiors not long ago. I don't know much about this Marwell Project, but according to the description, this plan is one of the civilization's secrets to cultivate special Espers.

Everyone nodded, not finding it surprising.

Because they coveted the position of hegemons that were held by the three Universal Civilizations, the Super Star Cluster Alliance had always known to hide its trump cards, and they had formulated many secret special talent training plans. After the Tragedy of the Pinnacles, there were even more plans. Some of the Beyond Grade As of their direct line that were hidden in the secondary dimensions were the products of their training plans.

This matter was considered a semi-open secret among the advanced civilizations, and the three Universal Civilizations also knew something about it, but they were unaware of the details behind each plan.

"You're saying these two can deal with Black Star?" Roddick expressed his doubt. "Impossible. These twins are not even at the Beyond Grade A level. Can they even hurt him?"

"You also subconsciously fell into a misunderstanding. It's not just another Beyond Grade A that can hurt one! While the twins are weak, they are the only qualified ones to be able to utilize a Universal Treasure that is classified as a Space Wonder. It possesses a miraculous effect toward the Soul and has never appeared before. It might work on Black Star."

Roddick hesitated a while before gritting his teeth. "Since there's no other way, apply to the upper echelons for them to dispatch the twins to help… What's the indirect route?"

"For the indirect route, we start from the people around Black Star. Throughout his life so far, the people he has acknowledged are few. Among them, his relationship with the Dragon Emperor is more subtle. If something goes wrong with the Dragon Emperor, he might temporarily throw everything aside and restrain the Black Star Army."

Roddick was taken aback. "Why use the Dragon Emperor as a target?"

"An officer like Hila will definitely be heavily protected. Compared to her, the chances of targeting the Dragon Emperor are higher."

"Didn't you say that he will have equipped the people he values with the teleporters. The Dragon Emperor can't be defenseless, so how do we deal with her?"

"What I'm talking about is not a siege. She's a Beyond Grade A and cannot be easily attacked…" Lagos took a deep breath. "But imagine, the Dragon Emperor's temper suddenly changes, and she begins to commit heinous crimes. It's impossible for Black Star to turn a blind eye toward her actions."

"You mean…"

"I have two plans. One is to let the Soul Swap Twins go to Dragon Emperor and distort her thoughts, so the success rate is more straightforward. The second is to find a way to get the Dragon Emperor trapped into a vortex of anger, causing her to perform heinous crimes such as randomly killing innocents and breaking the peace treaty. Black Star will have no choice but to divert his attention."

"The first one can be thrown aside. How do we go about the second plan?"

"It can be blaming her or causing her to go crazy. According to the data, she has a very obvious weakness…" Lagos' eyes flickered. "As for specifics, some consideration is needed."

Hearing this, Roddick's eyes lit up.

It seems like this is pretty reliable!

…

Among the battle zones of the four Star Clusters, the Ferdinand Star System of the Emerald Star Cluster was the most eye-catching. The reason was the Black Star Army being so powerful that it tore through the outer line of defense formed by the agent forces, pointing directly to Modo Civilization, which was located in the central area.

While the Black Star Army only stated that it would target the Modo Civilization, this would inevitably affect the whole scenario. The current behavior of the army had a profound impact on the overall battle situation of the Emerald Star Cluster, and the outer defense circle that was constructed by the Super Star Cluster Alliance now showed a gap.

Using the attacking direction of the Black Star Army as a breakthrough point, a large number of organizations in the faction of the three Universal Civilizations chose to follow them, trying to enter the Modo Civilization territory through this gap, which was in the hinterlands of the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance could only plug up the gap with their reinforcements. Even if the agents' forces were not willing, they had to come to curb the advancement of the three Universal Civilizations' forces headed by the Black Star Army.

The Modo Civilization also had to supplement a part of their armies to cooperate with the Northern Battlefront to block the Black Star Army, barely restraining them around the fifth to seventh Star Zones on the frontline.

This front has also turned into a war vortex of the Emerald Star Cluster, attracting a large number of armed fleets to gather and turn it into a meat grinder. The Ferdinand Star System had become the most intense area of this current battle.

The war in the Flickering World was in full swing, and the three Universal Civilizations were not idle either. They promulgated measures to impose multi-domain sanctions on all the Super Star Cluster Civilizations, eroding the national power of each Super Star Cluster on the political and economic level, so they could not concentrate on this war.

Thus, there were also a large number of business personnel from the Germinal Financial Group that had joined the fleet returning to the explored universe and travelling to the various Star Fields.

…

In the spaceship, the current vice president of the Germinal Financial Group, Iapetus, looked out of the porthole, the brilliant tail flame reflected in his eyes as he muttered to himself, "In the blink of an eye, over twenty years have passed…"

Touching his little moustache, a complicated look flashed past his eyes.

The image of him being taken away by Black Star was still vivid. In a flash, Iapetus had turned from a youngster with a slight talent in business to a strong, experienced businessman. He had even risen to the position of vice president.

At first, he was reluctant, but he felt more at ease as time passed. In order to get promoted, he had worked hard to showcase his value. Right now, he was already accustomed to working for the army, helping them to seek more benefits.

Every time he thought back to his past, Iapetus felt as though it was all a dream.

Originally, he was just the head of a small financial group. He had never expected to become an important civilian officer under the Black Star Army, boarding the top stage of the universe.

By obtaining the opportunity created by turbulent times, they would shake the economic stability of an advanced civilization, not only earning huge profits but also affecting the state of the universe. This was one of the top achievements of the galactic merchants!

Those who could do this were definitely hegemons in the universe.

Without Black Star as the guide, he might only have made his name in the small pond of a Star System. It would be difficult to imagine doing things he had done in his current life.

If asked whether he felt gratitude to Black Star, there was indeed some, but Iapetus sighed more at how much his destiny had changed after meeting up with Black Star.

At this moment, the secretary walked in, holding a digital document in his hands.

"Vice President, the Limitless Financial Group has drawn up a cooperation agreement and needs your signature."

"Oh, bring it over."

Collecting his thoughts, Iapetus glanced through the document once before signing his name.

He was clear that this was a trip with a mission.

Cooperating with the Limitless Financial Group to take a share of the economic sanctions was only a superficial reason. He had two underlying missions to perform.

The first was to focus on combating the Modo Civilization in the economic field, and the other was to help the intelligence personnel monitor the material and military movements of the Super Star Clusters.

The lifeline of the Super Star Cluster Alliance in maintaining this war lay in their logistics and transportation. The moment their backend assistance stopped, the troops in the free competition zone would just become a lone army looking to be defeated. Thus, the Army Commander privately gave him a task to allow him to pass through the Super Star Cluster and detect the transportation lines of these civilizations.

As long as they could control or cut off the transportation lines, the troops in the free competition zone would just be a group of turtles within an urn.

After more than twenty years of contact, Iapetus was aware that Han Xiao was farsighted. He knew well that his Army Commander was already making arrangements and that he was just one of the chess pieces that needed to be placed in a suitable position.

…

Meanwhile, in an exploration base of the Black Star Army, a group of players gathered in a private room, making a hubbub of noise.

"It's been almost twenty minutes. Why were we called over?"

"You guys were also notified by Phillip?"

"That's right. I don't know why we're here."

Everyone there had just arrived at the exploration base, ready to join the next fleet to attack the Modo Civilization, but they had suddenly received a notice from Phillip, asking them to come to this room to standby.

This situation was generally a sign of a mission trigger. Only a few would refuse, so there were about two thousand people within the room. They were basically part of the group that had joined the Black Star Army since its inception, and some were even members of the Chinese clubs.

Suddenly, a strange noise sounded in the room.

Buzz!

A virtual projection appeared, which immediately attracted everyone's attention. Many of them gasped.

"Black Star!"

The projection that appeared was Han Xiao.

Looking around at the curious faces, Han Xiao nodded in greeting.

"Everyone, it was I who asked you to come here. You are all veterans who have been fighting with the army for many years, which makes you trustworthy. I have picked the best out of all of you, and there's a secret mission I hope to entrust to you."

Upon hearing this, everyone present widened their eyes.

We're players specially selected by the Army Commander?

Ah, a hidden mission!

"What would you need us to do?" some of the bolder players shouted.

Han Xiao smiled.

"I require you all… to act as spies!"

He then released the 'Secret Mission' he had prepared earlier to the players present. All those on scene lost focus in their eyes as they turned their attention to the interface.

Since many of the foreign clubs had planted their spies there, Han Xiao was prepared to give them a taste of their own medicine. He was going to send some players to pretend to join those guild alliances to inquire about news. He had also conveniently planted a few spies in the Modo Civilization to investigate the transportation lines as well.

For this reason, he would conceal the files of these players in the army, 'washing out' their identities and creating a scenario not unlike that of Infernal Affairs[1]. This was nothing difficult for a Beyond Grade A.

He did not wish to discover the Modo transportation line to completely ruin the hope of the Modo Civilization but to better encircle and fight their reinforcements. He realized that the Modo Civilization would not give up on their desire in the Flickering World that easily. As long as they could survive, the Modo Civilization would insist on sending in troops and continuously throwing soldiers into this meat grinder.

Not only would it allow him to complete his own mission, it would also keep the Black Star Army in a state of intervention. After all, once Modo was gone, the Black Star Army would no longer have an excuse to intervene in the war.

This was just one corner of the strategy. Han Xiao was secretly laying out many traps, preparing to weave a large web to cover the Modo Civilization, turning it into a prey in the web with nowhere to escape.

For this reason, he even secretly contacted a person he had not talked to in a long time, a dangerous antisocialist and a powerful demagogue, a person who was perfectly useful for such situations in his mind…

Rossellin!

It was not difficult for him to imagine what sort of changes would take place within the Modo Civilization…

(1) Infernal Affairs, or Tlač, is a 2002 Hong Kong crime thriller film.Back

Chapter 1154: Dilemma of the Silver Revolutionary

On a colonial planet of a certain Star System level civilization, within a rented temporary stronghold, the senior officers of the Silver Revolutionary Army gathered together, most of them with a melancholic look.

The current leader, Edmond, frowned. "While the competition in the Flickering World has caused turbulence in the universe, the efficiency of our publicity program is far from expected. It could even be said that progress is stagnant."

The Silver Revolutionary Army had predicted this conflict in the Flickering World, so they wanted to take advantage of the turbulent times as an opportunity to grow their team. But when the conflict broke out, the spread of their ideals did not go as easily as they thought.

One of the men wearing glasses pushed his glasses up as he spoke. "Based on our survey, the popularity of the three Universal Civilizations in the universe is 1,174.1% higher compared to the same period as predicted by our mathematical mode. In other words, the three Universal Civilizations have obtained more trust from the people in this period. The turmoil of the Flickering World should have allowed the galactic residents to see their domineering attitude, but it did not drastically deteriorate the image of the three Universal Civilizations, unlike what we predicted."

"How could this be…"

"The root cause of this deviation lies in the sudden Intelligent Plague incident not too long ago… This disaster scared countless galactic residents, and the three Universal Civilizations responded in a timely manner. It only took about half a year to resolve it, and this extreme universal crisis allowed the galactic residents to see the power of the three Universal Civilizations, which is what they wanted.

"Black Star also played an important role in this, and it can be said that if not for his achievements, along with the Mechanic Emperor's ambitions attracting hatred, the three Universal Civilizations would have lost a large wave of popularity in this Flickering World incident. Right now, their foundations are still stable."

Hearing this, the senior officers of the Silver Revolutionary Army could not help but reveal bitter expressions.

The conflict of the Flickering World should have been a once in a lifetime opportunity for them to develop, but now, it seemed that this opportunity would no longer meet their expectations, as the effect was ninety percent lower than expected.

Without this, everyone felt that their future was quite gloomy, and they lamented in secret, complaining about how the Intelligent Plague had destroyed their plans.

But everyone was unaware that this Intelligent Plague should have been the important event in their rise. Due to the butterfly effect Han Xiao caused, this had become an obstacle to their development.

Edmond turned his head to look at the dignified woman who was leaning on the sofa not too far away and asked, "Mentor, how do you see it?"

Everyone gazed at her. While they were all in the upper echelons, they subconsciously understood that Rossellin was their true spiritual pillar.

Rossellin swilled her wine glass as she indifferently replied, "Since development is now blocked, take your time. The hearts and wills of people are ephemeral like smoke, and the current support may change in the future. Be more patient."

"This…" One of them opened his mouth in hesitation. "You don't have a way to solve this problem?"

Hearing this, Rossellin laughed. "Haha, do you think I'm omnipotent? I can only follow the general trend to plan out details. I can't change anything with my own strength."

As she spoke, Rossellin stood up, walking to the front as she smiled. "Since there are difficulties with our development now, I plan to take out some time to work on something else. Black Star sent me a request a while ago."

Everyone got a shock.

"You still maintain contact with Black Star?" Edmond was surprised.

"Why not?" Rossellin casually shrugged. "After all, I was an officer under him for a period of time. He didn't stop me from leaving, so I technically owe him a favor."

Edmond's expression turned serious as he solemnly replied, "Right now, we're plotting against the three Universal Civilizations. Who's Black Star? An important ally of the three Universal Civilizations! How can you still maintain contact with him!"

"To be precise, it was Black Star who contacted me." Rossellin did not think much of it. "Besides, I think he's well aware of what we're trying to do. He probably thinks of us as a joke."

Edmond's expression was grave as he paced around the room. He finally said hesitantly, "What does Black Star want you to do?"

"He wants me to go to the Modo Civilization and intensity their social contradictions." Rossellin clicked her tongue. "He really trusts in my abilities…"

One of the Silver Revolutionary Army members was shocked. "How can this be? It's one thing not to expose us, but he even asks for your help to fan the hatred in another civilization. Isn't he someone who cares for the masses?"

Rossellin laughed derisively. "How could a man who broke into the decades-long established foundation be as kind-hearted as the news says? It's just that he knows how to maintain his image and give the dirty work to others. Now, it's my turn to work as well…"

With that, she did not wait for the rest to reply, pushing open the door and leaving the room.

Black Star's request for her was to try and provoke the internal conflicts within the Modo Civilization, and she was given free rein. Rossellin already had a vague idea of how she should act. In her opinion, Modo Civilization was made up of three main races, and thus, it was very suitable for implanting radical split thoughts.

Speaking of which, she herself originally wanted to revolutionize the lives of the three Universal Civilizations' citizens but ended up turning around to revolutionize the lives of people in the Super Star Clusters, who were supposed to be her supporters.

Rossellin did not mind it, however. Unlike most of the upper echelons in the Silver Revolutionary Army, she did not believe that she needed to do something big. Be it against the three Universal Civilizations or the Super Star Clusters, as long as she could create upheaval in society, she did not care who the opponent was.

…

Within a certain asteroid belt in the explored universe was the secret base of the Assassin's Society.

Ding ding dang dang!

Hundreds of assassin apprentices in training suits were practicing in the open-air training ground. Only the sound of weapons colliding could be heard.

In the stands of the training ground, several instructors stood with their arms folded, supervising the practice of the apprentices while Lothaire stood at the very front, staring with indifferent eyes.

It had been almost twenty years since Han Xiao ordered him to secretly form the Assassin's Society. Over the years, he had left a frightening record of assassinations on the black market and secretly recruited many assassins, constantly training new people. Now, the organization had reached a certain scale.

Beep beep.

His communicator rang.

Lothaire glanced at it before walking off.

"Stop the training, assemble the staff, and prepare the spaceships. We're heading off."

Several of the officers showed curious expressions.

"Where are we going?"

"New mission. We're going to Modo."

Lothaire concisely spoke as his figure disappeared down the passage.

He had no interest in authority and always kept in his mind that the organization he established was a sharp blade that Black Star hid in the dark, stabbing the target Black Star pointed to.

…

In the Primeval Star River, within the Modo Civilization's secret base…

Ta, ta, ta!

Heavy footsteps sounded in the corridor outside as a person slowly approached a door.

With a creaking sound, the door was opened, and dazzling light shone in.

A group of soldiers stood at the door, with only their silhouette seen against the light. The commander said in an emotionless tone, "Soul Swap Twins, there's a mission."

There was no response at first, only deathly silence.

But this silence did not last long. A rustling sound came from a corner where the light could not reach, and a humanoid creature enveloped in shadowy fog walked out of the darkness. There was a baby-sized figure lying on his shoulders, wrapped in the same shadowy fog.

Both of them only revealed a pair of blood red eyes, and no one could see what sort of species they were. Obviously, some kind of abnormality had happened to them, and the only telling factor was their size.

These two were the Soul Swap Twins. The person with a normal growth was the elder brother, while the infant was the younger one.

"Modo allowed us to go out again?" The younger one lying on the shoulders spoke with a hoarse voice, not unlike that of an old man.

Seeing the two, the officer immediately replied, "Same old rules. Immediately get on board with us. You can only get in touch with the Soul Swapper once you get to the mission location."

"Who are we dealing with this time?" the elder brother asked with some resentment.

"Black Star!"

Hearing this name, both twins shared a look, inexplicable fluctuations in their eyes.

There was no tension but rather a faint excitement and greed, as though they had discovered a treasure.

At this moment, the officer took out a magical orb, saying, "The target has an ability to make predictions. This magic orb is inscribed with a magic circuit that will cover your aura, so when it's worn on the body, it can effectively interfere and mislead any prophetic abilities."

After the magic orb was given, the group of soldiers stepped forward, leaving the room with the Soul Swap Twins. Each soldier had a tense expression, their footsteps subconsciously speeding up, obviously wishing for the twins to be boarded as quickly as possible.

Even if they did not have the Space Wonder called the Soul Swapper, the twins were still quite dangerous, spending most of their time in prison.

While their realms were not high, long term contact with them would cause people to have more hallucinations, lowering their Sanity values.

…

At the same time, Aesop raised his head to look out of Floating Dragon Island in suspicion.

Aesop closed his eyes, directly activating his abilities. His thoughts seemed to pass through the dimensions until he locked onto the territory of the Modo Civilization.

"The feeling comes from Modo Civilization. What sort of abnormalities? It seems like they've used a masking device. The perception is vague, and the specific possibility of a future cannot be seen either…"

Aesop frowned uneasily.

Chapter 1155: Chess Player

In the Army Commander's Black Star Palace office, the bright and shining star map sand table was suspended a meter above the ground, like a flat picture scroll, and the blue light reflected on Han Xiao's face.

The star map sand table was a miniature map of the explored universe, of which two areas were illuminated. One of them was the free competition zone of the Flickering World, while the other was the Modo Civilization's territory within the Primeval Star River.

In these two areas, there were many scattered light spots. Above each spot was a head or influence emblem, which represented the identity of the light spot. These included people such as Lothaire and Rossellin.

Han Xiao slowly paced around the sand table, moving the light spots representing Lothaire and Rossellin to the Modo Civilization area as he whispered to himself, "Rossellin and Lothaire are in place. Iapetus is almost there with the Germinal Financial Group as well…"

This scene was akin to a chess player, with the star map as a chessboard and the forces deployed as chess pieces, constructing a game of encirclement and suppression against the Modo Civilization.

Because of the development union as well as the constraints of the image created by the three Universal Civilizations, he could not move personally. Thus, in the free competition zone, if he wanted to mess around, he needed someone to do the dirty work for him.

This time, Han Xiao formulated a strike plan based on the military and economic fields. The frontal battlefield was simple—just fight and consume the forces and resources of the Modo Civilization.

As for the economic field, that was the highlight, taking advantage of the opportunity of war and sanctions that would shake the domestic market of the Modo Civilization. With the large number of financial groups and organizations that would close as a result, the Germinal Financial Group under his command would cooperate with the Limitless Financial Group and other business giants to enter and hunt down these assets, sucking the lifeblood of the Modo Civilization.

The partners Han Xiao found for the Germinal Financial Group were not just limited to the Limitless Financial Group. Since the Black Star Army represented a huge community of interests, Han Xiao had a lot of connections with the heads of various financial groups. He contacted a bunch of people, putting forth his cooperation requests through relying on his twin heavyweight identities of the Black Star Army and the three Universal Civilizations' ambassador. Faced with such an opportunity, there were few financial groups that would refuse such a deal.

With his current influence and status, even if he merely remained in Black Star Palace, he could still leverage resources of a terrifying scale.

As for what would happen as a result of this chain reaction, the Modo Civilization might not regress but would definitely be hurt through this attack.

In contrast, all the partners of the Germinal Financial Group would be able to make a fortune out of it.

"This feels more and more as though I'm the leader behind the scenes in the triads." Han Xiao snickered before sighing. "I'm only missing one last link, which is a supervisor for the Shattered Star Ring, who is needed to locate their supply lines as well…"

The Shattered Star Ring bordered the Flickering World, so the Super Star Cluster Alliance would definitely use this to their advantage to send reinforcements and supplies to the Flickering World. However, the Shattered Star Ring was his backyard, and the army would definitely know of any movements made by the Super Star Cluster Alliance there. It would definitely be possible to trace their transportation lines.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance was definitely aware of this point, so they would use various means to cover up the fleet, fighting a battle of wits. For them, maintaining the concealment of their supply lines was vital to winning the war.

"Sylvia and Herlous are both in the Flickering World, and the highest-ranking officer left in the Shattered Star Ring is Lagi. I worry about his way of doing things…" Han Xiao shivered involuntarily and decided to change to another person. "Hila and Sylvia cannot return for the time being… Oh, Nero has already grown up. It's time to make him take more responsibilities."

The Shattered Star Ring was still the base camp of the Black Star Army, and the task of monitoring the Super Star Clusters should not be too difficult. It was a good time to let Nero handle this and temper the kid.

Right now, Nero was at his peak. He had the ability but lacked the experience. Han Xiao had always hoped to train Nero into a unique talent. Aside from the close relationship, Nero himself was also a protagonist-level character, with amazing potential and worthy of training as a core member.

If he could train out a better worker than Sylvia, that would be for the best. Not only would he be more worry-free, but Nero was also a man and would not care about his hairline. Added with his various fatigue resistances, he was strong and could literally be worked to death.

"That's right. Aesop is also good at finding people. I can invite him as a consultant and let Nero temporarily act as his assistant…"

Han Xiao stroked his chin as this idea took hold.

An elder in the family was akin to having a treasure. Getting Aesop to come forward would not only increase the chances of finding the Super Star Cluster Alliance transportation line but also allow Aesop to pass on his precious life experience to Nero, killing two birds with one stone.

He just did not know if Aesop would willingly step up and help. That old fellow should be desperate for something to do, after being trapped in Floating Dragon for over a decade.

Beep beep!

Just as he was thinking about it, his communicator rang. Glancing at it, the corners of his mouth curled up.

Speak of the Aesop. That old man probably foresaw that I was going to call him and thus decided to be preemptive.

As he thought that, Han Xiao answered the call.

"Old man, you saw that I was going to find you?"

"I've come for something else." Aesop did not beat around the bush, immediately speaking. "I foresaw that danger's coming from Modo Civilization. They've made some movements lately targeted toward you. You have to be careful, as they used a shielding device and I cannot get a clear prediction."

"Oh, I understand." Han Xiao nodded, not feeling surprised at all.

With him already targeting the other party, the Modo Civilization would definitely do something to try and restore the situation. Even without Aesop's reminder, he knew that the Modo Civilization would inevitably counterattack. It was not surprising for them to use a shielding device, as he still had someone with the title of [Oracle] protecting him.

"You'd better be more cautious. While I might not have gotten a clear prediction, I have a bad feeling about this," Aesop stressed.

"Alright, I'll keep my eyes peeled."

Han Xiao began to recall the various trump cards that the Modo Civilization had in his previous life, beginning to deduce how they would carry out their counterattack against him.

"Just take it seriously. You said you were looking for me as well?" Aesop changed the topic.

Hearing this, Han Xiao told Aesop his plans.

"To invite me as a consultant… I have no objections, but you've got to ask Ames for this. If she's not afraid that I'll take the chance to run off, I'm alright with that."

Aesop thought about it and did not reject it in the end.

He had been 'trapped' in Floating Dragon for so long and had already given Ames to Black Star as though he was sending off his daughter to be married. He had nothing else to worry about now, so his adventurous spirit had begun to resurface once more.

"I'll find time to speak to her." Han Xiao laughed.

While his relationship with Ames was close, he still needed to observe his manners and pay a visit if he wished to borrow one of her people.

After chatting a while more, Han Xiao turned off the communicator, sizing up the star map as he nodded in satisfaction.

In this manner, the layout was basically complete. He did not need to interfere anymore; he just needed to wait for his pieces to act and let things develop as planned.

Han Xiao opened the interface.

More than half of Version 4.0 has passed. According to my current experience accumulation efficiency, I should have enough to reach level 340 before the end of the version, undergoing my next sublimation.

He had originally almost saved up enough experience, but because of his battle against the Mechanic Emperor, he had been forced to change his experience into Awakening Points in one go, adding nearly ten thousand Intellect points. After so much time had passed, his experience was slowly accumulating once more.

The God's Trait Transformation points obtained through producing four new Universal Treasures had already been used by him. Now his God's Trait Transformation—Machinery had reached level nine, bringing to him a considerable bonus. As long as one more God's Trait Transformation—Machinery point was obtained, there would be a qualitative change as with every five stacks.

According to Han Xiao's estimation, when he reached level340 and transformed his God's Trait Transformation—Machinery to level ten or more, alongside the new talents from the Kunde Race Mission and some new Mechanic Universal Treasures, he would be able to suppress the Mechanic Emperor.

At that time, even if the Mechanic Emperor did not come to provoke him, he would go and fight with him, rewriting the 'tie' battle record that they had!

…

As the days passed, the battle in the free competition zone intensified. Under this chain reaction, turmoil broiled in the universe, raising surging winds and storms.

The three Universal Civilizations began imposing extremely strong sanctions on the Super Star Clusters. The latter was still resisting all pressure, and various negative reactions had already started appearing in each civilization.

Among them, the Modo Civilization suffered the most. Not only did they suffer heavy losses due to the Black Star Army in the free competition zone, but the country also gradually turned chaotic. Assassinations got more frequent, with the victims all being successful people from all walks of life, causing panic among the populace. It also seemed that someone was deliberately inciting negativity among them, causing the social conflicts to further amplify.

At the same time, their economy was also impacted. A large number of their companies went bankrupt, and many people became unemployed. Even if the Super Star Cluster Civilizations had many huge businesses, when having their revenue robbed by several financial group giants, it would be impossible for them not to suffer losses.

If it was in peacetime, with just the power of the Black Star Army, it would be impossible for the Modo Civilization to even be swayed. However, the three Universal Civilizations were the main force behind the sanctions this time, which burnt out the Modo Civilization. This environment provided Han Xiao with an excellent opportunity to mess them up.

In just three months, the Super Star Cluster Alliance's plan was in full swing, but with their investment regardless of cost, the overall war in the free competition zone had achieved some advantages… except for the zone where the Modo Civilization was located.

Meanwhile, a fleet with no emblems arrived at the Inter-Star Field Stargate linking to the Shattered Star Ring. It was the secret force dedicated to transporting the Soul Swap Twins.

Chapter 1156: Nation Saving Plan

The conflict of the Flickering World was seen as a resistance by the Super Star Cluster Alliance toward the three Universal Civilizations' hegemony. The Galactic Society eventually gave this resistance a formal name—The Flickering War.

For this Flickering War, the Super Star Cluster Alliance had prepared decades in advance. From the first to third exploration phases, they had continuously sent stowaways into the Star Field, establishing secret Stargates. While the three Universal Civilizations were preoccupied with the Intelligent Plague, the Super Star Cluster Alliance had started to prepare war resources, avoiding eyes and ears to establish hidden warehouses in the barren universes at different locations. They even managed to build secret military communication networks.

And today, all of their hidden hands had been connected. The Super Star Cluster Civilizations had built a secret transportation network to deliver lifeblood to the Flickering World, and the secret force that transported the Soul Swap Twins also utilized this secret stargate to arrive at the Shattered Star Ring, leaving no record in the public stargates.

In the temporary detention room of the spaceship, Lagos, the warlord of the Modo Civilization Expedition Fleet, was communicating with the twins to explain the mission.

"… Your mission objective this time is Aesop Hurricane, the adoptive father of the Dragon Emperor and the current Special Consultant for the Black Star Army."

"Didn't the superiors call us over to deal with Black Star? Why is it another target now?" the elder brother of the twins said.

"This is part of the plan to deal with Black Star. Aesop is a key figure, and his position is important to the Dragon Emperor. With the relationship between Black Star and Dragon Emperor, we can use this strategy to shift Black Star's attention away from us," Lagos solemnly said.

In the past few months, he as well as all the other upper echelons of the exploration army had repeatedly analyzed the pros and cons, finally choosing this method to save their nation.

This battle plan had received approval from the various members of the Military Strategy Department. According to Modo's current situation, if they wanted Black Star to stop, they could only do so by throwing him into another vortex.

The Modo Civilization was also aware of the name of Aesop. This long-lived man had a strong power of Prophecy and was thus difficult to deal with. But in contrast to going head on with a Beyond Grade A, it was easier to attack Aesop.

It was precisely because of Aesop's predictive abilities that he had to be specifically targeted. In the past few months, Aesop had paired up with Nero to search the Shattered Star Ring. They had discovered the location of multiple transportation lines dedicated to the Super Star Cluster Alliance, which caused a substantial number of problems for them. If it were not for the fact that the Black Star Army only targeted the Modo Civilization, the overall damage to them would be even larger.

While Nero's luck also played a huge part, in the eyes of the Super Star Clusters, the main point was still Aesop's Prophecy that did the work. Thus, even if they could not deal with Black Star, they had to get rid of the problem that was Aesop.

However, the Soul Swap Twins were terribly disappointed.

"I thought that I would be able to directly attack Black Star. I rejoiced for nothing."

Lagos frowned. "If you went directly against Black Star and failed, you would die immediately. Isn't targeting Aesop the safer option?"

Hearing this, the Soul Swap Twins displayed sarcastic smiles.

The way they spent their lives was as good as not living. So, why would they care about it?

Black Star was a pinnacle Beyond Grade A, and he would definitely not be easy to deal with, but they did not care about the danger. They only looked at his huge assets and lofty status.

If they could utilize the Soul Swapper to occupy Black Star's body, all of that would belong to them. Not only would they gain their freedom, but they would also become a top powerhouse in the universe, taking away the foundation of power and strength that Black Star had developed for decades.

Compared to their lives, the twins wanted to gamble on this, but there was no need to express their hearts at this time.

"Tell us the process," the younger brother of the twins said hoarsely.

"Aesop is currently a Special Consultant for the Black Star Army," Lagos explained. "He is highly guarded, and he has his ability to find any hostile targets, so we will use some forged transportation lines as bait to lure the snake out of its hole. Then, we'll find a way to allow you to make contact with Aesop. You can then use the Soul Swapper to temporarily distort his thinking and manipulate him to intervene in the conflict of a certain civilization, before asking him to commit suicide. This will anger the Dragon Emperor into pinning the blame on the civilization… We will help to secretly propagate this. All you need to do is to be responsible for your own mission."

Be it for official or private reasons, Aesop had to die, and his death would be blamed on a Star System level civilization that was protected by a peace treaty. This was for the Dragon Emperor to form some hatred toward the civilization, forcing her to lose control and cause a slaughter due to her anger. Even if the Dragon Emperor did not give in to her grief, she would inevitably have a conflict with the civilization due to her temperament.

No matter what, Black Star would turn back to help, and to protect the Dragon Emperor, he might even have to resort to using force. As a result, the Black Star Army would gain another opponent and would have a high probability of withdrawing its armies.

"Understood." The Soul Swap Twins were noncommittal.

It was not the first time they had done such a thing.

Lagos instructed them some more before cutting the communication. The guards then closed the door again to prevent them from moving around.

The Soul Swap Twins glanced at each other, understanding each other's meaning without needing to speak.

This was a chance for them to become free men. The moment they obtained the Soul Swapper, they could escape after finishing their mission. They were not reconciled to spending their lives as tools.

…

In the office, Han Xiao read the report of the Shattered Star Ring, from time to time looking up at the remote projections of Nero and Aesop in front of him.

"Discovered thirty-eight Super Star Cluster Alliance transportation fleets; completely destroyed two lines of the Modo Civilization and seven secret resource bases, seizing daily supplies, weapons and ammunition. Another eleven suspected transportation routes of the other Super Star Cluster Alliances during the monitoring…" After browsing the report, Han Xiao smiled and praised them. "Well done."

"It's all because of your tutelage." Nero scratched his head as he laughed dumbly.

"You're now the chief in charge of the Shattered Star Ring. Don't laugh so stupidly. You have to be more serious, understand?" Han Xiao rapped on the table.

Nero immediately straightened his expression.

He was already an adult, but in front of Han Xiao, he behaved in a very relaxed manner, naturally revealing his childish side.

At this moment, Aesop smiled as he said, "I like this kid. He has a lot of potential. Given enough time, he will become quite a unique character. His luck is pretty good."

Han Xiao nodded and asked, "Any forecasts so far from your Prophecy?"

Aesop shook his head. "It's still the same foggy sense of danger. Three months have already passed, but they have not seemed to move."

Han Xiao turned back to Nero. "Take note to increase the collecting of intelligence. At the first sign of trouble, report to me."

During this period of time, he had analyzed the possible plans of the Modo Civilization and felt that the probability of them attacking him was quite low. It was more likely that they would choose to start with the people around him, so he had strengthened the protection around his mother planet as well as various officers and increased Phillip's monitoring of the entire army.

Because most of the information was actually reported up by level and might not be able to reach him, he lowered the standard of importance for Phillip to directly report to him. While this might cause his workload to increase, it was a trivial matter for such a period.

"By the way, what did you say to Ames?" Aesop asked. "I'm running everywhere with the Black Star Army right now, but she does not seem to be afraid that I'll suddenly leave."

"Oh, I told her that I'm watching you for her. If you run away, then I'll bring you back." Han Xiao laughed.

"Tsk, I knew it." Aesop's eyes narrowed. "Is she that unconfident of me? The stuff I've seen, how could she know more than me? I've probably eaten more salt than the amount of rice she has eaten."

"Then you must feel thirsty a lot," Han Xiao joked. "From your tone, it seems like you were really intending to slip away."

"I've been under house arrest in Floating Dragon for decades. I can't possibly stay there until the end of my life." Aesop folded his arms in front of him. "To be honest, with you taking care of Ames, I feel reassured. There's no need for me to remain here. I took those years of staying as a rest, and now I'm ready to continue my travels."

Han Xiao did not find it weird at all. For a long-lived species such as Aesop, a decade or two was just like a year or two for a normal person. This old man's desire for adventure was carved deep into his bones, and he could not settle down in one place forever.

"Then, why don't you just tell Ames directly? If you are honest and truthful, she definitely won't stop you."

"No, no, then she won't send people after me. That would be so meaningless."

Aesop shook his head, revealing a gleeful tone akin to someone goading another party to catch him.

Han Xiao was speechless.

I suddenly have the desire to beat this old man up…

"Aren't you afraid that I have preparations made to prevent you from slipping away?"

"Haha, even if I tell you, you won't stop me." Aesop smiled. "I want to maintain a tacit understanding with her, so I'll need you to help convey my meaning."

Han Xiao understood. This meant that Aesop was planning to leave without saying goodbye, and he planned to use Han Xiao as a microphone. This was also a way to get back at him. Previously, it was Han Xiao who had caught Aesop, making the latter lose face.

Giving himself a reminder before successfully slipping away would settle their debts.

"Then, when are you preparing to leave?"

"I'll help you with this last task, and once the Flickering War is over, I'll leave."

"Hey, when the time comes, I'll see if you can escape from my palm."

Both of them shared a laugh.

By the side, Nero suddenly felt as though he had become a lightbulb.

Han Xiao gave him a few more instructions before hanging up. Thinking about it, he then called Ames.

Only two rings had passed before the call connected.

"Oh, busy man, you have the time to chat with me now?"

Ames' laughter was like a clear spring bubbling through the communicator.

"What are you up to?" Han Xiao smiled.

"Practicing the Knowledge you got for me."

Han Xiao had managed to exchange a Knowledge of the Esper Class, passing it to Ames. She had been studying it diligently. Because ordinary people did not have an interface, they could not do it overnight but had to slowly pore over the research.

The two of them chatted a little before focusing on the trending topic.

"Black Star, how long do you think the Flickering War will last?" Ames was curious.

Han Xiao contemplated. "At least three to five years, a decade or two at max."

The Super Star Cluster Alliance would not give up so easily. The previous Flickering War lasted for quite a long time. The players were only contracted as agents around the end of Version 4.0, and in the later stages, most of it was reduced to cutscenes as the players went offline.

This time, because of the sudden emergence of the Intelligent Plague, the Super Star Cluster Alliance was more prepared and could resist for a longer period of time. However, with his own intervention, the course of the battle would be shortened. The two factors both affected each other, changing the plot of his previous life. Thus, Han Xiao also found it hard to say how long the alliance could support itself this time.

But the final result should be the same as in his previous life, where it would end with the failure of the Super Star Cluster Alliance. This battle was for them to gain a glimmer of hope, a gamble with a low success rate.

"So long…" Ames sighed. "I originally wanted to invite you to travel to the world of the secondary dimensions, but it seems like you don't have the time in the next few years."

"Again?"

"You're not willing?" Ames tilted her head, her hair spilling over her shoulders like a waterfall.

"Cough cough, I'm actually not that busy. You also know that us Beyond Grade As cannot personally enter the Flickering War. After destroying the Modo Civilization, I'll be free, and I can accompany you to visit the secondary dimensions…"

… as well as allow Aesop to slip away. Han Xiao finished in his mind.

"Then we have a date." Ames' eyes curled up as she smiled.

Chapter 1157: Soul Swapper

Somewhere within the Shattered Star Ring, three small battleships with the Black Star Army emblem were cruising in the starry space. All three battleships were blitz-class shuttles, exceptional in speed.

The responsibility of this force was to track down any suspicious transport fleets.

In the command room of the lead spaceship, the captain carefully stared at the star map in front of him, which marked the patrol route of the squad. Once a suspicious unit was found or a new mission assigned, it would be displayed.

"I heard that a couple of days ago, there seemed to be traces of a suspicious transport fleet in the neighboring Star Zone. However, the clues were intermittent, and we seem to have lost it. Do you think they will come over to our sector?" A nearby officer made some idle talk.

"It would be great. If we can track down the suspicious fleet, it will be our credit. We have been patrolling here for a few months and have not even performed a proper mission. If we're not lucky, we probably won't get any merit," another person said with some envy.

Because the patrol mission was dull and boring, the captain did not stop his subordinates from chatting as he thought the same. While he was only a bottom-rung member in the army, he had the desire to progress. As long as he accumulated enough merits, he could acquire the army's elite training qualifications and invest in himself, which would be beneficial to his promotion.

Beep beep!

At this moment, a red dot of light rippled on the star map, and a notification was heard. This was a field inspection mission, which meant that their space buoy had intercepted a suspicious unit.

"Mission!"

The captain's eyes brightened as he thought that an opportunity had come for him. He immediately ordered the fleet to change directions, heading toward the marked coordinates.

The spaceships immediately turned around, and their engines released a roar as they shot toward the depths of the starry sky.

After flying for a period of time, the team arrived at the target location. Opening the detection device, thirty or forty spatial folds appeared on the radar's view.

These were the traces left by hyperdrive transitions. Each trace represented a spaceship. At this moment, the traces had yet to disappear and extended out, pointing out the course of these dozens of spaceships in disguise.

"A total of forty-one hyperdrive jump tracks have been spotted. Follow the traces and catch up!" The captain did not hesitate.

The squad was now energized, and they followed the trail of the hyperdrive engines, tracking them for around two hours before a barren asteroid leapt into view.

The trail ended here, which meant that the target exited the hyperdrive mode at this point.

The vice-captain glanced at the radar before speaking. "Report, the target has disappeared. They might be on the planet to collect resources or hiding in ambush behind the asteroid. Awaiting instructions."

The captain deliberated for two seconds before saying, "No. 2, perform a scan on the planet surface. No. 3, round to the back of the planet. No.1, maintain position. Keep the engines ready, prepared to move at any moment."

"Roger that."

The three spaceships immediately separated, and it did not take long for the results to arrive.

A docked fleet was found on the planet's surface. Their emblem represented a local commercial organization, and they were currently collecting the underground gas resources. The scale of this fleet was exactly the same as the number of transition traces, which was the target of this team.

"Send out a wide area communication, asking to check the identification codes," the captain ordered.

The transportation fleet of the Super Star Cluster Alliance utilized various methods to hide as they travelled, and one of the most common ones was to pretend to be the troops of other organizations. If the tracking team of the area happened to come across any of such fleets, they would generally ask to check the identity of the other party, guilty until proven innocent.

However, the authority to check the identities of any transit fleet was actually only given to the Civilization Security Team. The Black Star Army, as a private armed organization, did not have the right.

But in this world where authority was decided by one's fist, the Black Star Army's motive of tracing the transportation fleets of Modo Civilization resulted in many of the civilizations allowing it, unwilling to cause trouble. Most of the civilizations of the Shattered Star Ring did not have any issues, closing one eye to this.

Occasionally, the tracking team would uncover a genuine transport party, and the enemy would strike at them first, but this was an unavoidable risk. Thus, the tracking team generally did not fight, only maintaining communication with the intelligence department. This way, even if the tracking team was killed and disconnected, it could still send back messages and allow the department to know the identity of the target enemy.

At this time, the tracking team sent a communication request to the transport fleet, but the other party did not respond.

The captain immediately turned vigilant. "Something isn't right. Immediately prepare to report…"

Before he could finish speaking, his brain spun, and his vision turned chaotic. This state only lasted for a second before he regained clarity.

But the scene in front of him froze his whole body, and fear erupted from his heart.

He saw that his surroundings had turned into a prison, and his body was firmly fixed in a confinement chamber, unable to move.

He was lost for words.

I was in the command room a second ago. How did I end up here‽

Before he could make sense of his situation, his brain spun yet again. His surroundings changed, and he was now situated in a transparent glass room, with a swarm of black beetles next to him.

Looking through the transparent walls, he was terrified to see giants walking outside the room without even looking at them. He could not even see how tall these giants really were.

Everything seemed to have been magnified countless times over in his vision.

"What the hell…" the captain murmured subconsciously, but rather than hearing his voice, he only heard a slight hissing sound.

He paused before lowering his head to look at himself. A chill ran down his spine, and he dared not believe his eyes.

His body had actually turned into that of a black beetle, just like the bugs around him!

In that instant, he seemed to have understood.

It's not that the world has gotten bigger… I've shrunk!

At this moment, a deep-orange jet of flames blazed in the sky, filling the entire glass capsule and turning his thoughts into a blazing white cloud.

Boom!

With just a breath, all the black beetles were burnt to ash.

An operator in a white lab coat removed the flamethrower used for the experiment. Taking a look at the residue within the glass capsule, he gave an 'OK' signal.

The team leader nodded before saying, "Reporting to the commander. The targets have been eliminated."

"Hmm."

In the flagship, the commander nodded as he looked out of the porthole at the scene outside.

Two of the spaceships, No. 2 and 3, had already been reduced to fireworks. Only the commanding spaceship managed to escape and leave the scene.

In this escaped spaceship, all of the members were shells, replaced by a different soul!

"The plan was a success."

The commander lightly nodded before looking to the side. There was a smoky crystal-colored mirror floating in the air, about fifty centimeters in diameter and only three centimeters thick.

The Soul Swap Twins stood in front of this mirror, their palms submerged inside the surface of the mirror up till their wrists, as though it was being swallowed.

This mirror was the marvelous Universal Treasure named the Soul Swapper!

"It's done. Stop right now!" the commander bellowed.

Hearing this, the Soul Swap Twins slowly withdrew their palms. The soldiers around them immediately moved forward, taking away the Soul Swapper and placing it in an extremely sophisticated safe, away from the Soul Swap Twins.

Seeing this, the twins glanced around the surrounding mechanical turrets protruding from the walls and ground that were aimed toward them before laughing nonchalantly.

These turrets were safety devices to prevent them from moving. They were remotely and intelligently controlled, since the soul swapper only worked on the souls of living creatures. It was useless against machinery.

The commander then retracted his gaze, looking in the direction that the shuttle was fleeing, and whispered, "The Death Warriors prepared in advance have already penetrated the enemy. With our bait, it should be enough to catch the person…"

…

"A squad in the Thousand Lights Star System was ambushed on their way to track a suspicious fleet. Two of their spaceships were destroyed, and only one of them got out alive…"

At the Black Star Army headquarters in the Shattered Star Ring, Nero whispered after reading the report. He looked up at the several officers in the room, asking, "Everyone, what are your thoughts?"

Mia was decisive. "The situation is obvious. The transport fleet attacked them, so it is likely from the Super Star Cluster Alliance. We should immediately mobilize troops around the incident site to track the target."

"I feel that this is a little strange. The Super Star Cluster Alliance normally do not make any head-on attacks because their identity will be exposed once they fight. Most of the time, they try to get rid of the tail instead. The reason for their attack is only if the chasing troops were not discovered early, allowing them to accidentally catch up… but once they attack, they will not leave any of them alive. The previous cases were all like this," Tomar muttered.

He had already been studying magic under Lagi for decades. While his teacher was a salted fish, he still could not resist Tomar's gifts for magic, so he had slowly worked his way up into one of the officers of the Black Star Army. His relationship with Nero was good, and he was currently in Nero's team.

"Maybe the surviving spaceship escaped in time. However, the Star Clusters must also have known that the information was leaked, so did they decide not to waste their energy in pursuit?" Mia guessed.

"That would make sense." Tomar did not doubt much as well.

"Let's ask the survivors for any details first."

Nero thought about it before ordering his assistant to contact the captain of the surviving spaceship. After a moment, the communication came through, and the captain of the tracking team appeared on the screen.

"Recount your experiences. I want to know the details."

The eyes of the captain on the screen flashed. He nodded, revealing an expression of lingering fear and anger as he recounted his experience.

The soul in this body had already been replaced by a Death Warrior prepared by the Modo Civilization. The effect of the Soul Swapper was not simply just transferring the souls of the two bodies but also allowing the invading soul to inherit most of the target's memories. This was because the brain of the body was still present, just like a library.

However, this memory would not naturally merge with the new soul. It needed to be sorted and read slowly, and there would naturally be parts missing. Generally speaking, the older memories would be more easily forgotten, while the most recent memories would remain complete.

There usually existed some sort of exclusivity to prevent different souls and physical bodies from merging. Methods like reincarnating in a new shell and seizing souls could also be done by some Espers or Psychics, such as Feidin or Chen Xing, but with lower success rates.

The Soul Swapper would greatly increase the success rate of the transfer of souls, bringing it close to a hundred percent under normal circumstances. However, this was affected by the strength of the target and the strength of the user. At the same time, using the Soul Swapper to complete the soul transfer would greatly reduce the chances of rejection of the body and soul.

The soul transfer was only one of the functions of the Soul Swapper. This mysterious thing had many other functions.

After listening to the report, Nero gave a few words of encouragement and prepared to end the conversation.

At this moment, the 'survivor' suddenly put on an angered and sad expression as he shouted, "We're now the nearest unit to the enemy. I hope to be able to continue this mission, continue pursuing the troops to avenge my friends!"

"Sure."

This request was reasonable, and Nero had no reason to refuse.

Hanging up the communication, Tomar spoke out again.

"Nero, now that the target knows that he has been exposed, he'll definitely change his plan. Instead of going to the transportation line, he will escape separately. I suggest using the second plan."

This sort of scenario was not the first. The moment their transport forces were exposed, they would be treated as abandoned children. Even if they continued to track them, they would not be able to discover the secret stronghold of the Super Star Cluster Alliance.

"That's right." Nero turned over to look at Aesop. He said in embarrassment, "This… Your Excellency Aesop, we'll have to trouble you once again."

"No problem." Aesop waved his hands, as though it was nothing.

The so-called second plan was to borrow Aesop's ability to let him go to the location of the incident, using the relevant clues as a medium to make on-the-spot predictions, seeing the multiple possibilities and grasping more clues.

In order to obtain a clearer prediction, more information was needed. This method was effective, so over the past few months, Aesop had not just stayed in the headquarters but also conducted many field visits under heavy protection. This method had allowed the Black Star Army to discover many targets.

Nero nodded and loudly declared, "Let's not delay further. Prepare the spaceship immediately and take His Excellency Aesop to the location."

…

In a certain Star Field, on a certain planet, at a certain base, Manison stood in front of a virtual screen with his hands behind his back, staring at the contents of the screen.

This was the secret information from the Primeval Star River base camp, coming from the spy he had planted in the Modo Civilization many years ago.

Only a brief message was written.

The Soul Swap Twins were transferred from the base, and the Soul Swapper was taken from the warehouse by the army. The destination was unknown.

"Soul Swapper… If I my guess is correct, the Modo Civilization must intend to use this Universal Treasure to deal with him. Maybe I can…" Manison muttered to himself, an inexplicable light in his eyes.

Chapter 1158: Parasitism and Sudden Change

A few days later, in the Thousand Lights Star System of the Shattered Star Ring, a Black Star Army armed fleet flew out of the stargate. There were thousands of battleships of various models. In the middle of it was a very large, conspicuous flagship.

Inside the command room, the Calamity Grade officer nodded at Aesop and said, "Your Excellency Aesop, we're here."

"Quickly get to work then." Aesop nodded calmly with hands behind his back.

Usually, Nero would arrange at least two Calamity Grade Supers as Aesop's bodyguards, at least a thousand battleships, and Black Star's mechanical army and Lord's Avatar. When in danger, Black Star would be able to arrive at any moment. He was very well protected.

"The tracking team nearby have all been called here to search the area. They have yet to find anything for the time being. Let's go take a look at where it happened."

"Sure." Aesop had no objection.

The fleet advanced quickly through Star Zones, soon arriving at the planet where the battle happened.

The ground location where this Super Star Cluster Alliance transportation fleet once stopped was already occupied by the army warriors who arrived a few days ago and guarded as the crime scene.

A small ship carried Aesop and was launched out from the bottom of the flagship, crossing the cordon that the army had deployed at the exterior atmosphere of this planet.

When the hatch opened, Aesop stepped onto the ground in a light protection suit, surrounded by a group of bodyguards.

There were dim depressions on the ground in front of them, clearly the marks left by a battleship stopping and taking off. Aesop quickly walked to it, squatted down, and closely observed these marks while occasionally touching them with his hands. After he walked around the entire crime scene, he finally stopped and closed his eyes as if he was meditating.

This process lasted for about two minutes before Aesop opened his eyes and clapped.

"I saw some transportation spaceships sailing through the universe. The organization symbol on them has already changed to something else. This Super Star Cluster Alliance fleet should've changed into different disguises and gone in separate directions. I'll draw out these organization symbols for you later, so you can search the fleets of these organizations in the nearby area."

"That's great. That's extremely helpful. The great prophet Aesop never disappoints. Your efficiency is amazing, and receiving your help is our great honor," the fleet commander said, clearly having learned how to bootlick from Hadavy.

"Just a small matter." Aesop waved. "However, this is not enough. If you guys can seize one of their battleships or capture their men, I will be able to obtain more accurate leads and search for their original destination."

"Don't worry. With the intelligence you've provided, catching them is just a matter of time. Unfortunately, we'll have to trouble you to stay in this area a short while longer. We'll need you when we seize the enemy ship."

"Hmm, that's no big deal. I happen to want to take a walk outside too."

Aesop did not mind and wrote down what he had seen in the prophecy, all the organization symbols of the enemy's disguises. The fleet commander immediately gave the order and sent this information to all the tracking teams.

The group of them returned to the fleet and was about to depart for the army base of this area and standby when the fleet commander suddenly received a message. He looked down at the communicator, and his eyes gleamed.

"Your Excellency Aesop, you're such a lucky star! I've only just sent out the crucial information you provided, and there's a tracking team that's already found the target. They happened to be resting at a city planet and discovered the suspicious transport spaceship that matched your prophecy. Plus, that ship is alone."

"That's surprisingly quick." Aesop smiled. "Looks like we're still in luck. This team that discovered the enemy did a good job."

"Let me take a look… Oh, the one we've discovered is the only surviving spaceship from before. I remember they were searching everywhere for these guys. Now they've finally got their revenge." The fleet commander smiled. "I told them to standby and keep an eye on the enemy spaceship, to wait for us to arrive and not scare them away."

The fleet departed immediately and hurried all along the way, reaching the destination very soon.

A light purple and bright silver planet hovered in space outside the porthole. The surface of it was filled with colorful galactic cities.

This was a rather prosperous colonial planet. It belonged to the ruler of the Thousand Lights Star System, the Light Rune Civilization.

The Black Star Army would not do whatever they wished without restraint when they were in city planets that belonged to a civilization like this one. The main reason was that there was no need to. Most of the civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring had a good relationship with the Black Star Army, so the army would not offend them for no reason.

"The tracking team is still surveilling the enemy spaceship. They're not moving. What do you think?" the fleet commander said.

"Did they see any of their crew?" Aesop asked.

"The tracking team has already requested to look at the surveillance footage from the officials and shared it with us. According to the surveillance, that suspicious spaceship sent a total of forty-three crew members out. They seemed to be purchasing daily supplies and all returned to the ship not long ago… We've come just in time. Any later and they might have departed."

"Okay! We must seize this transport ship," Aesop said slowly. "Inform the officials to work with us, evacuate the locals, and lock down their departure path so that they can't take off."

The Black Star Army members had a lot of privileges in the Shattered Star Ring. Even if it was just a middle to low-level army member, as long as their identity checked out, they would be able to request official support from the various civilizations if they were on their planet. This was all thanks to the connections Han Xiao had built. It was part of the faction privileges.

The fleet arrived around the dock very quickly and formed an encirclement, while some Supers entered the dock with assistance from the officials, closing in on the target hangar.

Aesop and the fleet commander waited in the flagship in the outer atmosphere and monitored the operation remotely.

On the screen, the Super team charged into the hangar. Very soon, sounds of intense crossfire erupted from within, and flashes of energy cannon attacks flickered inside the hangar, leaving burn marks on the silver alloy walls.

The sound of the battle lasted for about a few minutes. The report from the operatives at the frontline came.

"Report, we only have three team members suffering from light injury, no casualties. The enemy ship contained a total of 271 crew members, who resisted, hiding in the battleship. We killed 209 targets, and the rest saw that there was no way out and ended their own lives. We were not able to capture anyone alive."

"Shame, I was hoping to interrogate them." The fleet commander shook his head. "Never mind, these low-level crew members probably don't know much either. Seizing their transport ship is enough. Your Excellency Aesop, please."

Aesop nodded. He landed on the dock with his guards and came to the hangar where the battle happened.

He looked at the seized transport ship. Its exterior appearance was almost undamaged. There were only some burn marks on its exterior armor.

He stepped forward, pressed his hand on the bottom of the spaceship's armor, closed his eyes, and activated his ability.

…

At the same time, in a rented temporary stronghold in a galactic city not far from this airport, the Soul Swap Twins were using the Soul Swapper hovering in front of them. Dozens of Modo Supers surrounded and aimed their weapons at them. There were also quite a number of portable cannons around.

There was more than one Modo Civilization spaceship that had arrived on this planet, but they had secretly turned the tracking team into their people, so they had all kinds of ways to remain undiscovered.

The commander walked back and forth on the side nervously.

"Have you locked onto the target?"

The elder brother of the Soul Swap Twins' hand was devoured by the mirror of the Soul Swapper. He casually stirred it and said, "Yes."

"Can you sway him out?"

"Tsk, us brothers are just Grade C Supers. Aesop is a Grade B. The success rate of us swapping his soul out of his body isn't one hundred percent."

"To be safe, use the second plan," the commander said.

"Okay."

The Soul Swap Twins focused their energy into the Soul Swapper. Black ripples appeared on its mirror sides as it was activated.

At the same time, Aesop, who was far away at the port, suddenly opened his eyes, and his pupils shrunk abruptly to the size of a needle.

He felt like countless voices had suddenly rushed into his brain and fused into a deafening noise that echoed in his mind. His head was hurting immensely.

He wanted to raise his hand to hold his forehead, but he could not move his body at all.

The aide-de-camp beside him saw that he was acting unnaturally and asked, "What's wrong?"

Aesop's expression changed several times. It became stiff for a moment but then returned to normal.

He coughed, lowered his voice, and said, "Nothing, I've already completed the prophecy."

"What clues did you get?"

Aesop's eyes gleamed, and he said, "I've discovered the real destination of this Super Star Cluster Alliance. It's a secret resources stronghold in a desolate universe belt. The coordinates are…"

He gave the coordinates, and the aide-de-camp hastily wrote it down.

"Hmm, this is enough information. Let's return to the spaceship."

Then, Aesop turned around and left without waiting for his aide-de-camp to reply. The bodyguards beside quickly followed.

…

On the other side, inside the temporary stronghold where the Soul Swap Twins were at, the commander asked, "Was it successful?"

"Hmm." The younger brother of the Soul Swap Twins replied with a husky voice, "We have swapped the many soldiers' souls over. They've successfully become parasites in Aesop's soul."

The main function of the Soul Swapper was to swap souls, but there was no such rule as one for one. Stuffing many souls into one body or just swapping the soul out of the body and turning the body into an empty shell, there were many possibilities.

Unlike with Feidin and Chen Xing, it was a type of puppet manipulation using parasites. The souls of many soldiers and Aesop were fused together temporarily like puppet strings injected into Aesop's soul. Aesop's mind had become fuzzy, and he could no longer think normally. He felt that all his actions came from his heart and did not realize what was wrong with him at all… Putting it simply, it was similar to how someone might go crazy when drunk.

"Aesop's bodyguards won't realize, right?" someone asked.

The commander shook his head and said, "Don't worry, the Soul Swapper's powers are extremely stealthy. No one will be able to notice it other than Beyond Grade As who excel in the mind or soul related abilities, not even Calamity Grades… Of course, peak Beyond Grade As might notice something wrong too, but Black Star's main body isn't here, and he won't monitor such a small matter with Lord's Descent. So, there's nothing to be afraid of."

After the commander said that, he clearly looked more relaxed. He turned to the Soul Swap Twins and said, "Your mission is complete. What comes next won't involve you. Put down the Soul Swapper."

The Soul Swap Twins exchanged looks and laughed creepily at the same time.

"Hehe, sure."

As soon as they said that, a change occurred!

A black shockwave expanded. Other than the commander, all the soldiers' eyes rolled and fell to the ground, not moving.

The Soul Swapper had silently swapped everyone's soul out!

At the same time, the infant-sized younger brother opened his mouth and sucked one soul after another from the Soul Swapper, swallowing them.

The commander instantly reacted to it. He was shocked and furious.

He did not expect the Soul Swap Twins to dare to do this even when they were targeted by so many weapons. Had they really given up living‽

However, at this time, a powerful energy erupted from the Soul Swap Twins.

Feeling this energy level, the commander's expression changed drastically.

"Grade B‽ We ran a check on you right before we departed. Aren't you guys Grade C‽"

The older brother of the Soul Swap Twins laughed out loud. "Hehehe, people grow!"

The two of them had always been acting weak, making the Modo Civilization think they were Grade C Supers. The method they used was not just simply hiding their real strength but a hidden ability they had never told anyone about—their energy could move freely between the two of them without any restrictions. This was related to the mutation these two brothers went through.

If they focused most of their energy on one of them, he would temporarily become a Grade B. If they spread it evenly, they would be able to fool the Super Grade Detection Devices of the Modo Civilization. The two of them had been planning their escape for many years, deliberately controlling their growth speed to stay at this level, all for an opportunity like today.

The Soul Swap Twins laughed creepily and said with a confident tone, "Think about it, we're now Grade B Supers. These cannons won't be able to kill us instantly. The Black Star Army's men have yet to go far. If a battle breaks out here, it will definitely attract their attention. So, think thoroughly about whether you want to attack us because your plan is at risk of being exposed!"

The commander was startled. He quickly yelled at his comrade who was controlling the cannons, "Wait, don't fire."

"That's right. Play nice, and your plan will be able to continue."

The Soul Swap Twins snickered. They chose to do this now exactly because of this reason.

The commander suppressed his rage and questioned, "What do you want?"

"Simple, Modo have been using us as tools for many years. We've contributed enough, and now is the time we take back our freedom… Hehe, I know what you're thinking. Don't worry, we just want to escape. We didn't sabotage the plan with Aesop. Take this as the last mission we'll ever execute for Modo. We don't owe you anything anymore.

"As for this treasure, it naturally belongs to us, so we'll be taking it away. Anyway, no one but us can use it."

The Soul Swap Twins sneered. The shadow shrouding their body devoured the Soul Swapper and absorbed it into them.

Then, the two of them stepped back to the wall, activated their ability, turned into two piles of ink-like shadows, and disappeared.

The commander was furious beyond imagination, but he still did not dare do anything.

He was not only worried about alarming the Black Star Army, which was not far away, but also because he was not confident enough to stop the Grade B Soul Swap Twins. He had no choice but to watch the two of them leave with the Soul Swapper.

It was dead silent in the room. The only sound was his heavy gasps for air.

"Quickly report this to the upper echelons. We've lost control of the Soul Swap Twins. They've escaped!"

Chapter 1159: Destiny's Child's Prophecy

"The Soul Swap Twins escaped‽"

Lagos was shocked to receive the notice from the army emissary and looked worried. However, he was not worried about this but its influence on their plan against Black Star.

"Are you able to capture the Soul Swap Twins?"

The military emissary shook his head and said, "The Shattered Star Ring isn't our territory. The Black Star Army and the local civilizations' surveillance network is all over it. We can't carry out a large operation. The target can use the Soul Swapper and swap bodies. It's too difficult to find them, so we most likely won't be able to capture them."

"The plan…"

"Don't worry. The plan continues." The military emissary smiled.

Seeing this, Lagos looked confused.

Why don't the upper echelons look worried at all about losing a special Universal Treasure?

"You don't seem worried…"

The military emissary shook his hand. "Don't worry, there's no need to send people after them. They'll return on their own."

"You're saying…" Lagos had a rough guess.

The military emissary changed into a serious expression and said, "This information isn't really that confidential. The upper echelons have told me to tell you not to worry about the Soul Swap Twins and continue carrying out the plan as usual. The person in charge of the Marwell project got a Beyond Grade A Mage to secretly plant a mental trap in them long ago and built a hidden sub-personality that's completely loyal to the Modo Civilization. Once triggered, the sub-personality will take over, and they will obediently return themselves."

"I see…" Lagos nodded subconsciously. He then frowned and wondered, "But if that's the case, why not take over the Soul Swap Twins' consciousness completely? Why take the risk?"

The military emissary did not mind and continued explaining. "Controlling the Soul Swap Twins is very easy. No matter how special they are, they're just low level Supers. Do you really think that there have never been such experiments even though the Marwell project has been going on for so many years? We've basically tried everything you can think of.

"However, the results proved that the Soul Swap Twins can only use the Soul Swapper when they have complete self-control and clear consciousnesses. Other than that, any attempt to control the Soul Swapper through controlling the Soul Swap Twins won't work. Even after just the simplest brainwash, the Soul Swapper won't recognize the two of them as qualified users. Therefore, we can only do it this way."

"Why is that the case?" Lagos wondered.

"Hell if I know. It's as if the Soul Swapper has chosen the Soul Swap Twins. It's probably related to the mysteries of the soul. It's all very non-scientific really. And that's the reason we consider the Soul Swapper a Space Wonder. If we could figure out how it works, there would be no Soul Swap Twins…" The military emissary snorted. "Though strange, the two of them are very weak and are no threat. They're only feared because they can use the power of the Soul Swapper. It's like a child holding a gun."

"Understood." Lagos nodded.

"Hmm, good that you know. Anyway, you don't have to be concerned about the Soul Swap Twins. Just be worried about Black Star."

Then, the military emissary cut off the communication, and the screen turned black.

Lagos turned off the virtual screen, exhaled, and smiled with relief.

Although there was a tiny hiccup, to him, the plan targeted at Black Star being carried out smoothly was the most important.

At a certain desolate universe belt in the Shattered Star Ring, a secret resources stronghold of the Modo Civilization was being attacked by the Black Star Army's armed fleet.

The images of this battle were transmitted into the main control room in the Thousand Lights Star System's base. Aesop and a group of officers were remotely monitoring the battle.

Not long after, the battle ended. The Black Star Army fleet had annihilated all enemies and was picking up the loot.

"Great! We've destroyed another secret stronghold of the Modo Civilization!" Nero was watching the battle with a smile. "This is all thanks to His Excellency Aesop's accurate prophecy, which helped us find the enemy base."

With their boss leading the praise, the officers present all expressed how impressed and appreciative they were of Aesop.

"No big deal." Aesop was not in the best mood and just waved slightly.

"Haha, a great job is a great job. Don't have to be so humble. I'll have some people take you back so that you can have a proper rest," Nero said with a smile.

"No need, I'm planning on taking a walk outside. I won't be going back to the headquarters for the time being." Aesop shook his head.

Nero was surprised. "How long do you plan to stay outside then?"

"About a month."

"So long‽" Nero hesitated a moment. "I suggest you come back as early as possible. There might be new missions…"

"What's with all the bullsh*t? I don't even have the right to take a walk outside anymore? Am I just a tool now?"

"Er, that's not what I meant."

Aesop narrowed his eyes and coldly said, "Also, take these troops and bodyguards away. I don't like to be disturbed when taking a walk."

"This…" Nero looked troubled. "I can't just remove them for no reason. What if an accident happens?"

Bang!

Aesop slammed the table and yelled, "What, you think I need your protection? Or are these people here to surveil me‽ I'm telling you right now, remove these people, or I'll go back to Floating Dragon immediately! Is it your place to control me? Do you have any idea what my relationship with Black Star is?"

Nero's expression froze, and he was rather unhappy inside.

This old man is usually easy to talk to. What's wrong with him today? Did he swallow a bomb, or is it that time of the month?

However, unhappiness aside, Nero did not dare talk back to Aesop. After all, Aesop was there to help and represented Floating Dragon. Plus, Aesop was his senior and the Dragon Emperor's foster father, as well as his godfather's good friend.

Aesop did not want to return to the headquarters, and it was not like he could force him or kidnap him. Otherwise, even if his godfather might not blame him, Aunt Ames would not be happy about it for sure.

Nero barely forced out a smile and said, "Since you like to be alone, I won't have the guards follow you."

"That's better."

Aesop turned, glanced at the officers around, and said casually, "You all heard that?"

While the two of them argued, the people in the room all stopped what they were doing and stood in place, frozen. Hearing what Aesop said, they could only nod.

"Good, that's all. I'll go back to my room," Aesop said monotonously. He turned around and left with hands behind his back.

Watching Aesop disappear from their sights, dissatisfaction showed on many people's faces.

"Who does this old man think he is? So arrogant," a Calamity Grade bodyguard said with a frown. "As if I'd be willing to protect him if not for the army's order."

"Exactly, this old man is in over his head." Another person was rather unhappy too.

"Alright, alright, that's enough. He's my senior no matter what. Maybe he's just not in a good mood today. Let's not force him if he's not willing to do so." Nero frowned slightly. He said a few words and hung up the communication.

To be frank, he had been a little tempted to report this to Han Xiao. However, Aesop had just made a big contribution, so if he reported him just because his attitude toward him was a little off, it would be too petty of him, like a kid crying to his father when just slightly unhappy. His godfather hoped he could be independent, and him doing that might disappoint his godfather.

"I'm not angry… I'm not angry…"

Inside the headquarters office, Nero softly murmured to himself. Then, he started to really feel his emotions gradually calming down, as if he was meditating. He had a subtle feeling that he seemed to have learned some kind of special trick to keep himself calm.

"Godfather! Godfather!"

More than a half month later, Han Xiao, who was in the Flickering World's Black Star Palace, received a communication request from Nero. He was startled by Nero's loud voice right after he picked it up.

"Calm down, what's wrong?" Han Xiao moved the communicator a little further away and picked his ear with his pinky finger.

"Aesop is missing!" Nero's tone was anxious.

Han Xiao's movements paused for a second. He frowned and said, "What do you mean by missing?"

"It means he's missing! We have no idea where he's gone, and we can't find him."

"Didn't you send people to follow him? How did he go missing?" Han Xiao asked.

"I…" Nero explained what had happened with a regretful tone. Aesop had shown displeasure toward the bodyguards, so the bodyguards did not follow Aesop closely around so that Aesop would not be disturbed. However, when they were resting on a city planet, the bodyguards discovered that Aesop had gone missing.

"Also, they've discovered a video message Aesop left inside his room."

"What did that old man say?"

"He said it was a message for you, telling you to remember your promise from not long ago." Nero played the video of Aesop saying that.

Having figured out the whole picture, Han Xiao caressed his chin and wondered.

About a month ago when he chatted with Aesop, Aesop had mentioned that he planned to leave the Shattered Star Ring and continue travelling, and he had come to an unspoken agreement with Han Xiao. This was the first possible reason for Aesop going missing that popped up in Han Xiao's mind.

However, with some thought, Han Xiao felt something was not right.

That's weird. The old man clearly said he'd only leave after the Super Star Cluster Alliance issues are over and he's done helping me with it. By leaving now, it means he didn't keep the promise. Was he just unable to endure it any longer?

Han Xiao was wondering but it did not show on his face. He nodded at Nero and said, "Got it, I'll deal with this matter. You can put it aside."

"I… sigh, alright then." Nero wanted to explain himself but gave up after pausing. He sighed and hung up the communication.

Han Xiao stood up from his chair, softly tapped the table twice, and suddenly pulled Phillip out.

"Master, hum… What is it?"

"Bring up the records of Aesop's whereabouts in the last month."

Although Han Xiao felt that Aesop might have run away deliberately, it was better to check through with caution in times like this.

Very soon, Phillip found the records. Han Xiao closed his eyes and browsed them quickly in his mind.

"Hmm, doesn't seem like anything is wrong. He even successfully destroyed a secret stronghold of the Modo Civilization more than ten days ago. Everything seems normal," Han Xiao murmured.

No part of these records seemed abnormal, but he still had a strange intuition that something was off.

The intuitions of Beyond Grade As were always rather accurate. Considering what Aesop had said some time ago about facing some kind of danger in the future, he had a bad feeling about this.

"I have to find him and make sure things are fine."

Initially, his agreement with Aesop was that he would only symbolically chase after Aesop if he ran away but actually let him go. If he really captured Aesop, Ames would definitely be more cautious and monitor Aesop even more closely, and Aesop would probably not have the chance to escape again.

However, out of caution, Han Xiao decided to catch Aesop for real this time. Anyway, the old man did not keep his side of the bargain, so he would still have the moral high ground even if his intuition was wrong.

Having made his decision, Han Xiao gave an order to Nero and told him to command the Shattered Star Ring troops to use all the resources to search for Aesop.

Then, Han Xiao walked out of the room and entered a secret lab.

Inside the lab was a translucent hibernation cabin where Rody was locked inside. Around it were Information Form restrainers. It was the Destiny's Child sub-body that had yet to fully transform.

Aesop's foresight is strong. If he really has made up his mind to escape, unless Nero or Feidin go after him personally, it really won't be an easy task to capture him with just my subordinates. However, now I have a reliable foresight talent in my hands…

Han Xiao chuckled.

In the past, he was only a fake 'Foreseer', so he could only rely on superstition and luck to capture Aesop. However, this time was different. He had a real foresight master in his hands.

Foreseers could see the multiple possibilities of the future. When their abilities clashed, it was basically something like 'I foresaw that you foresaw what I foresaw'; whoever could see further would win.

Although Rody was only half transformed and could not control his ability fully and the focus of the prophecy was basically random, with the uniqueness of Destiny's Child, he should be able to have a few rounds with Aesop.

Han Xiao operated on the hibernation cabin for a while, and Rody awakened shortly after. He opened his eyes slowly with confusion and was dazed for quite some time before gaining focus. Seeing Han Xiao outside the cabin, he shrunk his head and said softly, "Your Excellency Black Star?"

"You're awake." Han Xiao opened the cabin door and said with a smile, "I need your help for something. I have to borrow your foresight ability."

"Huh? But I can't control this ability yet." Rody panicked a little.

"Just do your best… Do you remember that old man who can see you too? The tall, skinny one, the one who spoke for you."

"Yes." Rody nodded. He had a strong impression of anyone who could see him.

"That guy is playing hide and seek with me. I need to find him now. Keep saying his name in your head, then touch me and try to trigger a prophecy that's related to him."

"W-what if the prophecy isn't related to him?" Rody asked softly.

Han Xiao smiled but said with an indisputable tone, "Then try until it is!"

Rody shivered.

He could not control his ability yet. He had to come into contact with the person and would certainly faint afterward. After which, he would wake up feeling extremely weak, and that did not feel good at all.

At this moment, Han Xiao's smile looked like a devil in his eyes.

"Ready?"

"Y-yes."

Rody knew he was in no position to object. He swallowed his saliva and started to rapidly repeat Aesop's name in his mind, hoping he would overperform and succeed in one try.

He extended his shivering hand and touched Han Xiao's arm.

The moment they touched, Rody started to tremble all over his body like he was being electrocuted.

"Ah!"

A few seconds later, his eyes rolled up, and he fell onto the ground. He had fainted.

Han Xiao was not surprised. He took out an emerald green potion from his pocket and injected it into Rody.

He could observe Rody now, which meant he could touch him. Rody fainted because he was just an ordinary man, and he could not afford the energy consumption of his ability, so giving him some potions would speed up his awakening… This was the result Han Xiao had obtained after more than a dozen tests.

As expected, not long after, Rody's eyelids shook, and he slowly opened his eyes. His blurry vision started to clear up as he saw Han Xiao's large body squatting in front of him, staring at him with burning emotions in his eyes.

"Tell me, what did you see?"

Rody shrunk his neck with fear, recalling the images he saw in his dreams. He looked at Han Xiao's expression and said cautiously, "I-I saw that you and a black-dressed woman were dragged into a war. Countless battleships exploded in your hands, and a corpse lay under your feet…"

"A corpse?" Han Xiao was stunned. The storyline of the previous life flowed up his mind, and he said subconsciously, "Aesop's?"

"Yes, his."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

In his previous life, Aesop's death was what caused the Dragon Emperor to lose control and start a slaughter, which went against the peace contract between Universal Civilizations and led to her being hunted.

Is this the world correcting the timeline, or is it because of some reason I'm unaware of? Han Xiao crossed his arms, scratched his chin, and pondered. Interesting. It feels like someone is plotting something in the dark…

Chapter 1160: Dragon Emperor's Inverted Scale

On the Modo Civilization's mother planet, the Modo Three Kings were having a meeting with the military upper echelons.

"Message from the frontline. Aesop has started moving. The plan is going smoothly."

"Our first choice is to have Aesop leave the Shattered Star Ring and take part in the conflict between the civilizations of another Star Field. This way, when Aesop dies, Black Star would have no choice but to go to another Star Field to deal with this, leaving his headquarters…"

"Aesop's foresight ability is great, but he might not be able to escape alone given the long years Black Star has been operating his forces in the Shattered Star Ring. Therefore, we'll have to help him."

"Hmm. If he really can't make it out, we'll have to choose a local civilization of the Shattered Star Ring to frame."

The upper echelons discussed their options.

At this time, the Modo Three Kings received a secret message and suddenly said, "Meeting temporarily dismissed. Take a half hour break."

The people were surprised but had no objection and all left the conference room.

After everyone left, the Modo Three Kings were the only ones left in the room. This time, a virtual communication screen appeared on the table, and a soft laugh sounded.

"Hehe, I'm honored to meet the three of you for the first time."

"Mechanic Emperor!"

The Modo Three Kings looked solemn.

Just now, the Mechanic Emperor had contacted the Modo Civilization and specifically asked to discuss a partnership with the Three Kings. Hence, the secretary had come to relay the message, and the Three Kings had decided that they would listen to what the Mechanic Emperor had to say.

The entire universe knew what an extremely awkward situation the Mechanic Emperor was in. Many Super Star Cluster civilizations saw the opportunity to woo him and wanted to work with him secretly, but Manison never gave a clear answer, nor did he reject them totally. Therefore, the leaders of the Super Star Cluster civilizations monitored Manison's current attitude closely.

"Your Excellencies, I know you're busy, so I'll cut to the chase… I've considered the proposal you made before, and now I'm planning to initiate a partnership with the Modo Civilization," Manison said calmly.

"What kind of partnership?"

"Us secretly working together against the Black Star Army. What do you guys think?"

The Three Kings exchanged looks but did not agree to it immediately. Instead, they asked back, "There are so many Super Star Cluster civilizations wanting to work with you. Why choose Modo?"

"Hehe, it's simple. I have no interest in stepping into the conflict you guys have with the three Universal Civilizations. Black Star is my only target, and you guys happen to be the most suitable partner for that. He's our common enemy, so I have a sensible reason to step in and interfere."

"We'll need more details."

"The shared battlefront requires the Beyond Grade A members to remain neutral, so taking part in the war is looked down upon. However, despite being the vice president, Black Star used personal beef as an excuse to start a war with the Modo Civilization. Therefore, as the president myself, I can do the same thing, using my beef with Black Star as the excuse to work with you guys against the Black Star Army. That way, even if it's found out, there's nothing anyone can say."

Manison's tone was casual but clearly showed his determination.

The Modo Three Kings pondered for a moment before nodding in agreement to what he was saying.

Although they hoped the Mechanic Emperor would join the Super Star Cluster Alliance faction to fight the three Universal Civilizations, they were well aware the chances of that were very slim. Nonetheless, it was acceptable for Modo Civilization now that the Mechanic Emperor had decided to target only Black Star. Black Star was the one who had caused them to be in such a horrible situation, so getting rid of him surely was a good thing.

"So, you plan to send troops to help us fight the Black Star Army?"

"Not really." Manison shook his head slightly. "My forces in the Flickering World are not as strong as Black Star's, and fighting the Black Star Army directly goes against the purpose of the development union…"

"How do you plan to cause damage to Black Star without sending troops?"

"There are plenty of ways. Damaging his reputation for one," Manison slowly said. "The three Universal Civilizations used me as the negative example to build his reputation, which has already affected my position in the Machinery Faith and damaged my interests. I have to think of ways to damage Black Star's reputation, and that is why I've decided to work with you guys.

"What I can do is secretly provide help. For example, have the forces I secretly planted in the Flickering World and Shattered Star Ring do something. After all, your troops are being closely monitored, and my men can move freely in the dark."

Hearing this, the Modo Three Kings frowned.

If the Mechanic Emperor was not planning to participate directly in the battle, his impact would be very limited.

However, thinking about it, there was no way they could make the Mechanic Emperor sacrifice his own troops for their Super Star Cluster civilization. After all, they had never had much of a relationship prior to this, and the Mechanic Emperor was not in the best situation himself.

Furthermore, the Mechanic Emperor was right; the Super Star Cluster's troops were being way too closely monitored. On the other hand, the Mechanic Emperor had planted a ton of subsidiary forces in many Star Fields that formed intelligence and resource networks, which might come in handy.

"…Okay, we'd be happy to work with you. We'll discuss the details later."

"Sure, I'm looking forward to it." Manison smiled faintly and cut off the communication.

The Modo Three Kings finally relaxed and looked at each other. They all saw the same thought in each other's eyes.

If they got Manison's help to transport Aesop out of the Shattered Star Ring, the success rate would be much higher than if they did it themselves.

Although the three of them had yet to decide whether or not to let the Mechanic Emperor take part in this operation, another layer of insurance would never be a bad thing. If they had no way of sending Aesop out of the Shattered Star Ring, it would not be too late to ask the Mechanic Emperor to help.

Furthermore, if Aesop died in the Mechanic Emperor's hands, they would achieve their goal all the same, with greater results than they could have hoped for!

However, while the three of them were having these thoughts, they had no idea that Manison's motive of proposing this partnership was anything but pure. Although he did want to cause problems for Black Star, it was not his main goal.

His sources showed that the Modo Civilization had moved the Soul Swapper out, so it was definitely going to be used on someone, most likely Black Star. Therefore, Manison wanted to use Black Star as an excuse to work with Modo, attempt to take part in the related operation to obtain more information, and find the whereabouts of the Soul Swapper.

Robbing the Soul Swapper was his true goal!

After all, he would not incur any losses even if he failed, so it was worth a try.

…

In the cabin, two bodies shrouded in darkness laid on the ground, one large and one small. They were completely stationery like vegetables. It was the Soul Swap Twins.

Two normal-sized Spacehumans stood on the side, one male and one female. They were stretching their bodies, and the dark Soul Swapper hovered beside them.

"This body is a Pugilist with a strong physique. It feels quite good. It's been long since I've felt this healthy." The male rubbed his neck with a comfortable expression.

"Stop dawdling," the female scolded. "This is just a temporary shell. Quickly pick up our original bodies."

The man and woman were the Soul Swap Twins who had changed their bodies. The elder brother was Jill Emmerson, and the younger brother was Warren Emmerson.

The Soul Swapper worked on them too. They could swap their own souls into someone else's body.

After swapping bodies, their Esper Ability would not be swapped too, and they would only be as strong as the new body. For example, if they swapped into a Grade D Super, they would also become Grade D. However, their souls would be unaffected and remain at Grade B, so their ability to use the Soul Swapper would not be affected either.

Their right to use the Soul Swapper came from their soul and had nothing to do with their bodies, so they would be able to use it even if they were in the body of a dog.

This ability was one of the reasons the two of them were confident in escaping successfully—they could keep switching bodies and be very difficult to find.

"Elder bro, although we're free now, we haven't got rid of that…" Warren pointed at his own head.

"Hmm, that mind trap is a problem. Luckily, the Modo Civilization probably thinks we can't even detect it."

Jill curled his lips with disdain.

The mind trap the direct Beyond Grade A Mage of the Modo Civilization planted into their souls would not disappear when they changed bodies.

Accordingly, given their Grade B strength, not to mention defusing this mind trap, they would not even be able to notice it at all. They should have been in the dark all along… However, the Soul Swapper had the function to check the state of a soul.

All Space Wonder level treasures had a certain 'absolute' aspect. Not to mention a mind trap set by an ordinary Beyond Grade A, even if it was set by a peak Beyond Grade A, as long as it was targeted at the soul, the Soul Swapper would discover it. This was similar to the Spacetime Amber's 'absolute' aspect; as long as its fundamental mechanism was not figured out, even ten peak Beyond Grade As attacking it together would not damage it in the slightest.

It would be a wild dream for the two of them to defuse a mind trap set up by a Beyond Grade A, but including a Space Wonder in that equation would make things different. Even though the two of them could not use the Soul Swapper to its fullest potential, they still had an emergency method to deal with this problem.

The Soul Swapper did not have the ability to 'purify souls', but the two of them planned to gather mind energy far beyond their own power by absorbing a large number of souls and slowly chipping away at the trap in their minds.

This plan would require a lot of souls, which meant they had to kill a lot of people. But clearly, they had no choice, nor did they care.

"Elder bro, what's our plan?"

"Let's go to some place where no one recognizes us, take over a body with high potential, and slowly grow stronger. When we're at Calamity Grade or even Beyond Grade A, we will be able to go anywhere we want in this universe!"

Jill knew that 'keeping a low profile and cultivating' was the right path. Flames of ambition sparkled in his eyes.

In his heart, becoming the only ones who could use the Soul Swapper was both lucky and tragic.

The lucky part, of course, was that the Soul Swapper only recognized the two of them as users, as if they were chosen.

The tragic part was that, because of that, they were imprisoned by the Modo Civilization for many years, they became the subjects of countless inhumane experiments, and their personalities became twisted.

However, the tragic dark days were in the past now. The future was full of hope, and the Soul Swapper had brought them infinite possibilities…

From now on, they were free!

…

In Floating Dragon Island, water vapor filled the magnificent palace. Deep inside the layers of fog, there was the sound of water flowing.

Hu!

The thick fog was suddenly disturbed, and a tall silhouette suddenly appeared beside the wardrobe shelf in the palace. The King mechanical suit automatically fell off and disappeared, leaving Han Xiao standing there.

The sound of water in the room paused for a split second, and a force field shockwave fused with water vapor suddenly rocketed toward him. Han Xiao stood still and let it land on his chest, creating a loud noise, but his body did not move at all.

"You startled me. Next time, tell me before you teleport here." Ames' voice came from the fog.

Han Xiao's vision penetrated the fog and saw a magnificent black, crystal bathtub in the middle of the room. Ames tied up her hair with a piece of white cloth and faced away from him, sitting in the tub. He could only see her snowy neck and moist shoulders that were tender like the skin of a child.

"Bathing?" Han Xiao snapped his fingers. "Quickly finish up. There's something I have to tell you."

"What is it?" Ames turned her head slightly, showing her elegant side face with water droplets hanging from her long earlids that blinked softly.

"It's about Aesop. He's missing."

"… Give me a minute."

Ames did not mind Han Xiao watching and stood up directly. She heated up her body temperature, and the water vapor quickly evaporated from her skin.

She walked out of the bathtub, casually pulled the black dress over to her with a force field, and donned it with a spin. She then took off the white cloth in her hair and let it fall.

Beyond Grade As' bodies would never get dirty; bathing was mainly for the purpose of enjoyment. All they had to do was adjust their temperature to that of an ordinary person, and they would be able to enjoy the feeling of taking a warm and comfortable bath. This way, they did not have to look for lava.

"Let's go. We'll speak outside."

The two of them walked out of the palace and came to the garden. Ames sat down on the chair and stared at Han Xiao with a weird expression.

"I allowed Aesop to go and help you, but you let him escape. That's a little irresponsible of you… Did you deliberately let him go? You're so bad."

"Ahem, you're overthinking it." Han Xiao coughed unnaturally and said without changing his expression, "Didn't I come to notify you instantly?"

Ames held her chin and joked, "Looks like even the universally famous Black Star still loses to a great prophet."

"He's a friend after all. It's not like I can really imprison him or something." Han Xiao smiled casually before putting on a serious expression. "Enough with the jokes. My intuition tells me that there's something wrong. Aesop might not have left on his own will."

"Oh?" Ames frowned, and the smile disappeared on her face. Shocked, she said, "Did someone kidnap him?"

"I don't think so. I arranged more than enough guards for him. If they'd kidnapped him physically, I'd definitely have found out."

"Does that mean someone controlled his mind?"

"That's the problem. I've had Aesop's guards carry around all kinds of psychological guarding devices, mind wave detection devices, and energy radars on them. If someone used soul magic, a psychic Esper Ability, or anything of the sort on him, it would have triggered an alarm, even if it was from a Beyond Grade A. However, none of these devices responded… Therefore, I suspect that Aesop might be controlled by an unknown method."

Although the soul and mind were not areas Mechanics excelled in, it did not mean he had absolutely no knowledge of them. He was just not as good as those who were experts on the subject.

"What method?" Ames asked.

"I don't know either. We'll only find out after we find Aesop and check him." Han Xiao shook his head.

In fact, if this conspiracy theory was right, he was very curious about how Aesop fell for it. It was completely undetectable, so he had no idea what method was used.

"I'll find him with you." Ames narrowed her eyes, and dangerous emotions flickered in her eyes. "Who dares to target my people? Do they think I'm dead‽"

"Don't get so riled up. This is just my guess. We'll have to investigate further." Han Xiao comforted Ames.

He had come to give Ames a heads up so that she would be mentally prepared, preventing the situation of her emotions going wild like it did in the previous life.

Han Xiao knew Ames' personality quite well. Sure, she looked like she did not care about anything usually, but her family and friends such as Aesop, Jenny, Hila, and Aurora were her inverted scales. Once threatened, she would turn into a raging dragon, leaving all rules and laws behind, and retaliate, no matter who the enemy was, not giving the consequences any thought at all.

This time, Han Xiao told Phillip to send a message. A few seconds later, the King mechanical suit appeared beside him again. The helmet opened, and inside was Feidin.

"Army Commander, I'm here."

Han Xiao nodded and explained to Ames, "Aesop's prophecy ability is very suitable for hiding. It won't be easy catching him using regular methods, so we'll need some luck."

He was not just going to bring Feidin along for this but also Rody. Teleporting the three of them there using the King mechanical suit would save a lot of time, and he could use the Black Star Army's troops right there in the Shattered Star Ring.

"All of Floating Dragon's resources are available for you to use. You don't have to care about anything else. I just want Aesop." Ames gave the right to command to Han Xiao without any hesitation and then stood up with a poker face. "We'll leave now!"

Chapter 1161: Finding a Needle in a Haystack Is Where We Excel

The universe was extremely enormous. Even if one had extraordinary individual strength, without a force large enough, one would not be able to achieve much in the galactic society.

The Black Star Army was among the top armed forces in the Galaxy. They had manpower, resources, money, ships, and everything. As soon as Han Xiao's highest order was given out, the Black Star Army's men in the Shattered Star Ring started executing the order immediately. They searched through one Star System after another and locked down all kinds of transportation hubs to find Aesop's whereabouts. The Floating Dragon Island's troops were also mostly dispatched.

Clearly, such a big movement could not stay hidden. It quickly attracted the attention of the entire galactic society. With just a little research, they knew that Dragon Emperor's elder had gone missing. To search for just one person, the movements of the Black Star Army indirectly affected dozens of Star Systems.

Such a deep search impacted the operation of some public facilities, which some galactic residents had slight problems with. However, given that it was from the Black Star Army and even the local civilizations did not do anything about it, of course, the ordinary residents did not dare do anything too.

Other than dispatching troops everywhere, the Black Star Army also issued a bounty for Aesop through the local media channels, making use of the power of the people.

A large monetary reward would be given to anyone who could provide any real leads to Aesop, such as witness reports, transit records, and many more. If anyone could capture Aesop alive and give him to the army, the reward would be an outrageous 135 million Enas. Ordinary galactic residents would not be able to even spend all this money in their lifetime. It was also humongous for some medium to small armed organizations.

As the saying went, with a high enough reward, people would step up sooner or later. Some medium to small organizations joined the search team, and a ton of free mercenaries started looking too. Even some galactic pirates and scavengers were searching secretly, hoping to acquire the reward and clean their ledgers. The local galactic residents of the Shattered Star Ring also kept an eye out.

For the time being, Aesop had become the focus of countless organizations in the Shattered Star Ring.

In the past, Han Xiao was on his own and hardly had any forces; being able to capture Aesop was mainly thanks to Feidin's luck. Decades later, his army had grown into a giant. There was no need to play hide and seek with Aesop like he used to; he just had to make use of his resources, and it would become extremely difficult for Aesop to go anywhere.

Even though Aesop's foresight ability was very powerful, all he could do was move with extreme caution and stealth in this kind of situation, not daring to appear in front of ordinary people.

Of course, these were just the basics. Han Xiao's core method of finding him was Rody's prophecy, alongside Ames, Feidin, Nero, and Harrison's luck, on top of his own Virtual Technology continuously calculating the possible coordinates Aesop might head to so that he could narrow down the search area.

…

Dark red sandstorm shrouded the sky like a red piece of cloth placed over the entire planet.

Through the low visibility sandstorm, a man in a heavy protective suit was walking alone on the red desert. The raging storm drummed his body like hammers.

This man walked a few hours like this when, suddenly, a meteor-like spark of light penetrated the sandstorm and plummeted toward this man. He stopped and looked up, an approaching small spaceship reflected on the ally mask of his protective suit.

Hu!

The spaceship slowly landed before this person and released an air force field with a fifty-meter diameter, blocking the sandstorm and creating a clean area.

The hatch opened. This person stepped onto the spaceship without hesitation, dusted off the sand all over his body, and took off the heavy protective helmet. An old face appeared. It was Aesop.

"You're the ones here to fetch me?" Aesop patted the helmet.

"Yes, we'll be responsible for getting you out of the Shattered Star Ring." The captain approached him. "Don't worry, we're professionals, certainly reliable."

Aesop nodded with approval and said, "The single person space cabin that sent me here has yet to be destroyed. Go destroy it on while you're at it. If it lands in Black Star's hands, it'll be a prophecy medium. Don't leave any clues like that."

Due to the Black Star Army's lockdown over the Shattered Star Ring, he could hardly go anywhere. He was barely able to find a space cabin and landed on this desolate planet and waited for quite a long time before this spaceship arrived to pick him up.

"No problem." The captain nodded.

The spaceship took off, came to a desolate desert area not far away, and discovered the metal space cabin that was half buried in the sand.

Bang!

Two explosive light beams shot out of the spaceship and destroyed the spaceship. The flame only lasted for an instant before being extinguished by the raging wind, leaving only metal fragments shattered around that were gradually buried by the sand.

After completing this task, the spaceship turned around, rose up, and took off into space.

At the same time, Manison, who was in the Primeval Star River, received the message. He opened the surveillance footage, and it showed Aesop in this spaceship.

"They finally picked him up…"

Manison looked at the screen.

For confidentiality purposes, this spaceship that had gone to receive Aesop had hidden its organization symbol. It actually belonged to an organization called 'Milder Armed Transport', one of the secret organizations Manison had planted in the Shattered Star Ring.

Not long ago, the Modo Civilization had officially pulled him into the plan, shared some information with him, and asked him to help.

Modo Civilization only did so because of the lack of a better choice. The lockdown of the Black Star Army was too tight, so they could not make any moves in the Shattered Star Ring and could not secretly transport Aesop out at all. They were almost discovered multiple times. Hence, they decided to borrow the Mechanic Emperor's men and have him take over the 'delivery'.

"Modo must have used the Soul Swapper on Aesop and made him escape deliberately."

Of course, in the information the Modo Civilization provided, the existence of the Soul Swapper was not mentioned. They only said that they controlled Aesop using some kind of mind control method and did not explain further. However, they did not know that Manison had known about the Soul Swapper since long ago, so he understood what was used on Aesop instantly.

Manison had no plan of stopping Modo's mission. He even planned to cooperate with it fully.

Although Aesop was one of the Ancient Ones, he had quit the organization long ago. The Ancient Ones were mainly Eternals. Beyond Grade As were a part of it, but not all members were Beyond Grade As. There were quite a number of unique members with special abilities but weak combat capabilities just like Aesop.

Although Manison did know Aesop, they were not friends, so he did not mind Aesop dying.

On this matter, his interests aligned with Modo. There was a chance using Aesop's death to plot against Black Star would force him to disobey the Peace Treaty of the advanced civilizations. This way, Black Star's reputation would be severely damaged, and the great image the three Universal Civilizations had been building for him would collapse. That was exactly what Manison hoped to see, so he was willing to cooperate.

However, all of this was just the cherry on top. Manison's main goal was still the Soul Swapper.

"Aesop is now in my hands. He's definitely come into contact with the Soul Swapper at a relatively close range. Through searching his past whereabouts, the rough search area can be determined. Through cross-referencing the records, the Modo Civilization's secret fleet that transported the Soul Swapper can be found. The person who's now controlling Aesop's body should be one of the Modo Civilization's men. Maybe I can hypnotize him and question him."

He did not know that the Soul Swap Twins had already escaped. He thought that the Soul Swapper was now being transported back by the Modo Civilization, so his search direction was already inaccurate.

…

Not long after the spaceship transporting Aesop left, another fleet visited this dark red desolate island. The Black Star symbol was engraved on their exterior armor.

Inside the command room of the main ship, Han Xiao, Ames, Feidin, and the rest gathered. This was a fleet commanded by Han Xiao personally.

"Hmm, this is the planet, exactly the same as it is in the prophecy. It's also one of the locations that overlapped between the areas chosen by Feidin, Harrison, and Nero."

Han Xiao looked down at the planet's surface.

Rody's prophecy did not work all the time, but any information that he gave was crucial, and Feidin and the others had the help of the Advanced Luck Glow. Under Han Xiao's instructions, they randomly selected some coordinates in the various search areas, and Han Xiao focused the investigation on the places where their choices overlapped.

Although they had yet to get any leads, Han Xiao was still confident in this method.

What he did not know was that he had only just missed Aesop multiple times. This method was indeed very effective. In a way, luck was truly invincible.

"Scan this planet. Report any abnormalities to me."

As Han Xiao gave the order, spaceships departed from the fleet one after another and circled the planet using all kinds of detection devices to scan the planet without missing a spot.

Normal readings showed on the screen before Han Xiao. There did not seem to be any abnormalities. However, after quite some time, some exciting news finally came from one of the spaceships.

"Sir, we have discovered an extremely weak radiation signal in the desert. The sources of it are scattered and buried a few meters under the ground. Do we dig?"

"Dig!"

The image on the screen quickly changed into the view from this battleship. The suction device at the bottom of the ship sucked out plates of burnt black metal fragments that looked like parts of a destroyed machine.

"Report, radiation source found. Analyzing… analysis complete. This should be the wreckage of a type of space cabin that was destroyed by an explosive energy cannon. Affected by the energy, a certain amount of radiation was left in the wreckage that's gradually weakening. The radiation will completely disappear in a few days."

"Looks like we're not too late." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

If they had arrived a few days later and the radiation had disappeared, they would not have been able to find this wreckage.

With this, not only could it act as a medium for Rody's prophecy, it could also be used with [Bold Explorer]. One could see the future, and one could see the past.

Very soon, this pile of space cabin fragments was transported to Han Xiao.

Han Xiao picked one fragment up, looked at the burn marks on it, and said, "It doesn't look like an attack, more like a deliberate attempt to destroy evidence, probably not wanting to leave any clues to us… Unfortunately for them, we're lucky."

Han Xiao grabbed the fragment in his hand and activated [Bold Explorer].

Ripples appeared in his vision, and his vision instantly changed.

He saw a space cabin falling down from the sky and landing on the surface of this planet. The hatch opened. A man wearing a heavy protection suit walked out from it and slowly walked away.

Although he could not see this person's appearance, he felt it was most likely Aesop.

Like time had been shortened, not long after, a spaceship appeared above the space cabin, launched two explosive light beams, and shattered it into pieces. The images stopped abruptly here, and Han Xiao's sights returned to normal.

This footage was short but quite informative.

"This is indeed a space cabin left by Aesop. A spaceship appeared after to destroy the clue, which means it was here to fetch him…"

Han Xiao recalled the appearance of the spaceship in the footage. It was not a common model but a high-speed spaceship known for its hyperdrive speed. It was expensive to build, and not just anyone could afford it.

"Phillip!"

"I'm here, hum… Please give the order, master."

"Search all the people and organizations in the Shattered Star Ring who possess the Featherlight Grade spaceship. Don't leave anyone out, and focus on any organization that has a stronghold near this area."

"Ah?" Phillip batted his large eyes and made a pitiful expression. "That's a lot of data, hum… It'll occupy a lot of computing power, hum…"

Han Xiao gave him a stare and said, "Then hurry up!"

Phillip reluctantly took out a progress bar from his pants, placed it upright beside him, and created a large box filled with paper. He then jumped in and started searching. The progress bar started moving at the same time.

After quite some time, the progress bar finally finished. Phillip's head extended out from the box. He spewed the pieces of paper out from his mouth with an illuminated piece of paper in his hand. He then filled his mouth with air and angrily said, "Humph! Found it, hum! Take it, take it!"

"A lot of tricks you have."

Han Xiao rolled his eyes, switched into quantum network vision, and retrieved the search results.

A large amount of data instantly flew into his head like a tsunami, blocked by the dam built by Han Xiao's brain capacity and computing power that did not even shake in the slightest. He quickly started browsing through it.

"A total of thirty-seven million and thirty-one matches… Hmm, let me take a look."

Han Xiao quickly filtered in his brain, browsing through all of the records in less than two seconds and memorizing all of it. Only Virtual Mechanics would be able to use this 'dumb method' to lock onto suspicious targets… When he had the ability to filter the entire haystack, finding a needle would not be that difficult anymore.

Most of it was data with no value, but one organization that was emphasized had attracted Han Xiao's attention.

"Milder Armed Transport… I seem to have an impression of this name."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. He searched through the mind palace inside his brain, and the memories came up.

… I got it! This organization is one of the Mechanic Emperor's subsidiary organizations that was exposed in my previous life.

Han Xiao's expression became solemn.

Although he had no final confirmation, his intuition told him that this was most likely the organization that transported Aesop away.

Doesn't this mean that old b*stard Manison is involved in this too?

Han Xiao was not planning to question the Mechanic Emperor. It would be a waste of time anyway as he definitely would not admit it.

All kinds of thoughts flashed past his mind. Han Xiao turned to the others and said with a low voice, "Have people monitor the Milder Armed Transport closely… No, monitor all the organizations I'm going to name. I want to know their recent movements, but don't startle them. Monitor them extra closely, and don't make any moves without my order!"

Han Xiao had always known some of the organizations that the Mechanic Emperor had secretly planted in the Shattered Star Ring. Originally, he did not want to let the Mechanic Emperor know this, but now that he seemed involved in this matter, Han Xiao decided to take measures and monitor all of the subsidiary organizations that the Mechanic Emperor had in the Shattered Star Ring!

Chapter 1162: Unlucky Modo

Ten days later, somewhere in the Shattered Star Ring, a spaceship flew, dragging a long trail of flames. Within the cockpit, Aesop was looking at the Shattered Star Ring star map with countless red marks that represented dangerous areas with a grave expression.

The captain stood to the side, hesitated for a moment, and said, "There aren't many routes left for us. We're about to hit a dead end. If this carries on, we probably won't have a way to get you out of the Shattered Star Ring. Do you have any plans?"

Aesop pressed his hands on the table so heavily veins appeared on the backs of his hands. He growled, "Aren't you guys professionals? Why is this happening‽"

Confused as well, the captain smiled bitterly and said, "We don't know either. We haven't left any clues behind, and we've been moving very stealthily, but the Black Star Army has been able to put up accurate encirclements around as if they are aware of where we are. We have no idea how or where they obtained such accurate information… Could this be the ability of foresight? Aren't you a prophet? Why didn't you notice it?"

Aesop clenched his teeth and had nothing to say.

He did indeed use his ability along the way, and it certainly helped them to dodge some of the troops. However, no matter how many times they got rid of the Black Star Army, the Black Star Army would be able to catch up again soon after. Even though the Mechanic Emperor's subsidiary organizations kept changing their carriers, it had absolutely no effect.

Furthermore, it was not Aesop who was controlling his body now, just the collective consciousness of a group of Modo soldiers. They were unable to use the foresight ability to the fullest. The secret stronghold location that was deliberately given to the Black Star Army was not acquired by prophecy; they knew where it was to begin with and leaked it on purpose so that the others would not suspect him.

Originally, Aesop's target was to head to the edge of the Shattered Star Ring. However, under the pursuit of the Black Star Army, he had no choice but to keep hiding and was forced to change the route. He was still going in circles in the Star Field, and the situation was getting worse by the minute.

"If there really isn't a way out…" Aesop looked at the star map, pointed at a planet nearby, and clenched his teeth. "Then cancel the plan of leaving the Shattered Star Ring. Take me to this planet."

The captain looked in the direction Aesop was pointing. His expression changed slightly, and he said, "Planet Mountain Ash? That place has always been chaotic. Are you sure?"

"Yes." Aesop nodded without hesitation.

This was a colonial planet currently belonging to a local Star System civilization. However, due to its history, this planet had very aggressive and sharp societal conflicts.

Originally, Planet Mountain Ash had a native intelligent species of its own that developed into a surface civilization that had been prospering. However, when they ventured into the universe, they were discovered by the local Star System civilization. Due to the treaty that forbade them from interfering with a lower civilization, the local Star System civilization only observed them at the start and did not interfere much. It was similar to the relationship the Godoran Civilization had with Planet Aquamarine back then.

However, Planet Mountain Ash was located at the borders of two Star Systems. The local Star System civilization had frequent physical conflicts with its neighbor, and both of them wanted to expand their borders. Therefore, they both hoped to make Planet Mountain Ash theirs. An unspoken rule of the Peace Treaty was that only Star System civilizations had real assurances. Despite surface civilizations being included in this treaty on paper, there would always be advanced civilizations that did not obey it secretly.

Of course, they still had to look like they were obeying the treaty on the surface. Hence, the local Star System civilization could not possibly directly attack the surface civilization, so they resorted to two methods. The first was to contact Planet Mountain Ash in the name of technology exchange, deliberately leaking some technology and then framing the Planet Mountain Ash civilization for stealing it. The second method was to secretly incite the split of the surface civilizations, then providing 'war support' to some of the governments in crucial times, leaving the army on Planet Mountain Ash using the excuse of settling rebellions.

The enormous difference in their strengths meant that there was no way a surface civilization could fight with a Star System civilization. Using these two methods, the local civilization gained control of Planet Mountain Ash without much suspense.

The ongoing societal conflict came from the retaliation of the Planet Mountain Ash civilization. There were frequent riots and demonstrations of all sorts. Hence, the local Star System civilization implemented policies to stabilize their ruling, occasionally sending official troops in to suppress these civilian activities on Planet Mountain Ash. This was why the environment of the planet had been chaotic.

In the universe, planets like Planet Mountain Ash were not a rarity. Laws created the seemingly peaceful galactic society, but under the surface, the rule of the jungle still applied. It was just not that bloody and naked anymore, rarely causing the extinction of an entire race.

Aesop needed a planet exactly like this. If he could die in the hands of the Star System civilization's troops, the Dragon Emperor would be furious at the local Star System civilization, and the plan would be considered a success!

"Alright, since you've made up your mind, I'll find a way to secretly send you in."

The captain did not try to dissuade Aesop any longer.

He was a base member of the Mechanic Emperor's subsidiary organization who was unaware of the whole picture. He was only responsible for completing the transport mission that was given to him. Whatever his employer said, he would follow, and he knew nothing else. In fact, he did not even know that his top boss was the Mechanic Emperor.

"Remember, it has to be stealthy," Aesop said and enlarged the image of Planet Mountain Ash on the star map. A complex emotion flashed passed his eyes.

Looks like this is where I die…

His mind was shaken for a split second before becoming firm again.

As the collective consciousness formed from multiple soldiers' souls, he did not fear death and was absolutely loyal to Modo.

Sacrifice himself in exchange for a chance for the Modo Civilization to take a breath, this was his mission!

However, while he was in an emotional state, no one on this ship knew that there were dozens of advanced spaceships secretly following them from not far behind.

It was the fleet led by Han Xiao!

The fleet was equipped with state of the art stealth devices of the logistics department. They had already been following the spaceship Aesop was on for close to half a day, but they had never been discovered.

…

Inside the main ship command room, Ames looked at the spaceship in front and wondered, "Where do you think he's going?"

Han Xiao glanced at the star map with his arms crossed and said, "Probably Planet Mountain Ash."

"Why would he go there?"

"How would I know?" Han Xiao shrugged.

Through monitoring all the secret organizations that the Mechanic Emperor had planted in the Shattered Star Ring, the search of the Black Star Army became much smoother. He was able to fully lock onto Aesop's whereabouts a day ago and followed behind it secretly. He did not immediately act because he wanted to see what backup plans the Mechanic Emperor had.

Speaking of which, if the Modo Civilization insisted on using their own forces to transport Aesop, Han Xiao really might not have been able to catch him this easily. He still did not know that the mastermind behind this was the Modo Civilization.

However, the Modo Civilization thought that the Mechanic Emperor's troops were more hidden, so they chose to borrow his forces, which achieved the complete opposite effect. To Han Xiao, most of the subsidiary organizations that the Mechanic Emperor had in the Shattered Star Ring had no secrets. It was like he had 'maphacks'.

"Do we go catch him now?" Ames turned to look at Han Xiao.

"We don't have to go through so much trouble. Just make him come to us."

Han Xiao smiled, snapped his fingers, and sent an invisible set of data.

…

Boom!

Aesop was studying the star map when he suddenly felt the spaceship tremble. It seemed like it had suddenly shut down its engine and stopped moving.

He looked up at the captain with a shocked and nervous expression.

"What's going on? Did the spaceship malfunction?"

"I-I don't know."

The captain was confused. He then displayed his superior home appliances repairing ability and slammed the control table a few times, but it did not respond at all as if the artificial intelligence of the spaceship had died.

Whoosh!

The hatch suddenly automatically opened.

Everyone was startled. The spaceship was in the middle of cosmic space. If the hatch opened, everyone inside would be sucked out.

However, that did not happen. The outside of the hatch was quiet. The people inside looked out the porthole with confusion, only to still see the dark cosmic space outside.

"What's going on‽"

Aesop and the rest came to the hatch and looked out. The moment they saw what was outside, Aesop's entire body froze, and terror filled his face.

Outside was an enormous metal interior of a ship. Black Star and Dragon Emperor were standing outside the hatch with a group of their subordinates, staring at him with a faint smile.

Aesop's eyes opened wide. His mind went into chaos.

Where is this? Why am I here‽

Did I open the door the wrong way, which caused me to see illusions‽

Han Xiao smirked and said, "You really can run, huh? But not even saying anything before you leave? That's cold, old man."

This was his doing. He easily hacked into the spaceship and took over control without anyone noticing, then made it turn around and fly into the main ship.

He left misguiding imagery on the portholes, so the people inside had no idea what happened.

Ames took a few steps up, narrowed her eyes, and said with a displeased tone, "Humph, you made us look for you for so many days! Don't you have anything you want to say to me?"

Seeing this, Aesop lost all hope.

It's over! The plan's failed!

Damn it, I was so close!

Now it's all gone down the drain!

He was filled with frustration.

No, there's still a chance! Black Star and Dragon Emperor both think I'm Aesop himself. I can still continue to disguise myself as him!

Aesop had yet to totally give up. He wanted to keep trying. He suppressed the tsunami of shock in his heart and forced out a smile, faking an embarrassed expression. "Well, you found me… Black Star, didn't we agree you'd let me go? Why have you gone back on your words?"

Han Xiao did not reply to him but instead turned to Ames and said with a smug tone, "See, I was right."

Hearing this, Ames sized Aesop up and nodded heavily with approval. "You're right, his smile isn't despicable enough. He must be a fake!"

Aesop was completely stunned.

His brain went blank.

What, they can actually see through my identity from such a small detail‽

Damn! What kind of laughable reason is that! Like hell I'll believe it!

Aesop's smile became more and more stiff. He had a bad feeling but still persisted and said, "What are you guys joking about? Alright, I admit I was wrong for sneaking away. I'll accept any kind of…"

Before he finished, Han Xiao suddenly shouted, "Still faking it‽"

Aesop was shocked. He was filled with despair.

At this moment, he knew that he had long been exposed. Black Star was only toying with him!

The next moment, he clenched his teeth, suddenly pulled out a weapon, and aimed it at his own head. He pulled the trigger without any hesitation.

The plan had failed, and he had no way of escaping, so he immediately chose to end his own life. This way, he could prevent Black Star from finding out who was behind all this, while at the same time, he would get rid of the prophet Aesop, making his last contribution to Modo!

Boom!

However, he was just about to raise the firearm when a light beam flashed past his eyes. Nero, who was prepared for this, instantly blasted the firearm out of Aesop's hand.

Then, the army soldiers swarmed over and pressed Aesop to the ground, making him unable to move.

Seeing this, Ames breathed a sigh of relief, deactivated the force field in her hand, and looked at Aesop, who was still struggling, with complicated emotions in her eyes. She then turned to Han Xiao and nodded as a sign of appreciation.

"Thanks. Things would've become troublesome without your help."

"It's no biggie. Aesop is my friend too."

Han Xiao waved his hand.

Ames smiled and softly punched Han Xiao's chest but did not say anything.

She knew that without Han Xiao's help, there was no way she could have found Aesop this easily. In the end, something irreversible might have happened, and Aesop was her irreplicable family. She could not imagine what she would do if that happened.

Words were not enough to express her appreciation. She looked at Han Xiao; he gave her a feeling of assurance and reliability.

This time, the captain who was shivering on the side carefully said, "Erm… Your Excellency Black Star, you've found your man. Can we go now?"

Han Xiao glanced at him, snorted, and said, "Leave? Stay here and don't resist. I'll let you guys go when you've told me everything you know."

Although these people were the Mechanic Emperor's subordinates, they probably did not know anything. Han Xiao did not plan to do anything to them. This would be entered into the Mechanic Emperor's ledger, and it was far from over.

Then, Han Xiao came to Aesop, squatted, and looked curious.

"Alright, now let me see what's going on with you, old man…"

Han Xiao ordered the soldier beside the press down hard on Aesop. Nanoparticles slipped out of his sleeve and formed a thin, black needle.

He held it in his hands, aimed at Aesop's butt, and pressed it in like a nurse injecting a needle into a patient.

"Huh!"

A very strange yell sounded.

Han Xiao plugged out the black needle and looked at the combat information on the interface. He quickly browsed through Aesop's status, and his expression became confused.

"Soul Swapper? What is that?"

Chapter 1163: Clues

[Soul Parasite]: This character is infected by an exterior soul parasite, and his mind is being controlled by it. Source: Soul Swapper. Duration: Unknown.

Aesop's current status appeared on his status bar.

Han Xiao noticed the words 'Soul Swapper' instantly. Clearly, this was the thing that secretly bypassed his detection devices and got to Aesop. He wondered what device this was.

He searched through his memories and was certain he had never heard of this name in his previous life.

"Soul Swapper, I wonder what its specific functions are. It sounds like a machine…"

While he was softly murmuring, Aesop suddenly froze, covered in sweat. His eyes widened with overwhelming shock.

What did I just hear? Did the exact words 'Soul Swapper' come out of Black Star's mouth‽

How does he know about the Soul Swapper? Where did this information get leaked‽

Of course, the Modo soldiers' souls inside Aesop's body did not know Han Xiao got this information from the interface, so the first thought that came to mind was that this information got leaked somewhere. His mind went blank with despair.

Han Xiao noticed his abnormal reaction and thought, He's responding strongly to it, which means this Soul Swapper must be something very important.

Since he now knew the symptoms, the matter was no longer that complicated. It was clearly more suitable for someone with expertise in the soul area to handle it.

Han Xiao stood up and called Feidin over, pointing at Aesop.

"The old man got infected by a soul parasite. Take a look."

"Sure." Feidin nodded. A ripple psychic energy was released from between his eyes and entered Aesop's mind.

The others waited on the side. About twenty seconds later, Feidin retrieved his psychic energy and looked hesitant.

"What is it? Is something wrong?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

Feidin frowned slightly. "There is indeed another cluster of collective souls inside his mind. Not really strong, Grade B at most, so I can deal with it. The problem is, this cluster of parasite souls has already perfectly fused with Aesop's own soul with close to no rejection. I have hardly ever seen anything like this…"

"So, you're saying there are risks?" Ames asked.

"There are indeed. They've fused too deeply, so the difficulty of removing the parasite is as high as doing an extremely precise operation on his soul. There's no room for errors. Once something goes wrong, Aesop's own soul will be damaged too…"

"You don't have to force it if you're not confident. I can ask Kasuyi to help. He'll definitely give me face."

Han Xiao was not surprised. He was in a similar situation back when he fought seven-eyes, so he was somewhat experienced. Aesop's situation was much less severe than his.

Feidin shook his head. "It's not that I'm not confident. I can eliminate the parasites, but I can't do it without wiping out their souls. This is why I'm confirming, do you want to do some interrogation first before curing Aesop?"

The soul swap of the Soul Swapper had close to no side effects, which most Supers were unable to do. To most Supers, the soul was a mysterious territory that could not be messed with.

Feidin, for example, could not even divide his own wife out of his soul and could only make love mentally every day. So, of course, he could not get rid of the parasite while still ensuring it stayed alive.

"I see, then don't cure him just yet." Han Xiao responded without hesitation.

The parasite was currently his biggest source of intelligence, so he had to interrogate him no matter what. Curing Aesop could be done after that.

As for the fact that Aesop's body would still be the one getting tortured during the interrogation… Ha, there was Aurora's life energy potion anyway. As long as there was no risk of Aesop dying, there was no problem.

The conversation between them was open, so the Modo soldiers inside Aesop's body heard it too and were in incomparable despair.

He wanted to keep all the intelligence he knew hidden, but he was well aware that there was nothing he could hide in the face of a Calamity Grade who specialized in souls.

Without the Soul Swapper, the body became a prison, and he was locked inside Aesop's body, unable to do anything but accept his fate.

"Leave the interrogation to me." Feidin waved and told the army soldiers to lead Aesop to the interrogation room.

Feidin was a kind person who did not like interrogations, but in the face of such a despicable enemy, he did not mind using more extreme methods.

The soldiers around cleaned up the scene and took the captives away. This time, Ames came to Han Xiao and softly said, "We've got who we came for. What are you planning to do now?"

"Ask the parasite who sent him, then come up with a plan depending on that. No matter what, this isn't over," Han Xiao replied casually.

All he knew now was that the Mechanic Emperor was part of this. He did not know if there were any other organizations behind it. Although they were not able to reach their goal, he was not going to let this go so easily.

He even planned to use this as the clue to search for information about the Soul Swapper, to see if he could obtain it and study it.

"Okay. If you're going to retaliate, count me in." Ames's tone was indisputable and firm.

"… I'm guessing they came for me. You don't have to drag yourself into this trouble. I'm here." Han Xiao shook his head.

He knew the risks involved, and he did not wish to involve Ames.

He also did not want Ames to step into his conflict with the Mechanic Emperor. Battles between peak Beyond Grade As were still too dangerous for her.

"What do you mean? I'm not one who's afraid of trouble. If they dare to target my men, I'll have to show them I'm not easy to mess with!" Ames frowned before smiling once more. "Also, you helped me, so I have to help you too. That's what an ally should do. Even if you reject me, I won't give up."

As she said that, a notification popped up on the interface.

You have triggered mission [Ames' Rage]!

Mission Introduction: Due to her family being hurt, Ames is enraged. She hopes to take revenge on the mastermind of it with you.

Mission Requirements: Take revenge on the mastermind together with Ames.

Reward: 250,000,000 EXP, +40 Ames Favorability, +10 Aesop Favorability, +30,000 Floating Dragon Island Contribution Points, 2 Random Rewards, 1 Character Summon Card.

Bonus rewards will be given depending on the Mission Rating.

Han Xiao scanned through the mission. This kind of mission was becoming less and less significant to him nowadays, but it still counted. Anyway, it would not be too much trouble, so he accepted it.

Mainly because he saw how firm Ames' eyes looked—she was clearly not going to give up. Instead of letting her take the risk herself, he might as well be by her side, so she would at least not do something as extreme as she did in his previous life.

About an hour later, Feidin came to the command room and gave the report in his hands to Han Xiao.

"The interrogation is done. All the information is in here. Nothing is missing."

Han Xiao took the file and browsed through it. The content was extremely detailed. It included the Modo Civilization's goal for this mission, how the Soul Swapper worked, the existence of the Soul Swap Twins, and so on. Everything was laid out clearly.

With Feidin's psychic scan of the Modo soldier's soul, he had obtained everything he knew.

"Hmm, so it's Modo. I knew it was Modo." Han Xiao sneered.

After reading the file, Han Xiao finally understood what was going on. This was within his expectations.

The only thing that surprised him was the Soul Swapper that was shockingly a Space Wonder grade treasure. The Modo Civilization had such an amazing device in their hands, yet it was not exposed at all in his previous life.

Nonetheless, this was not too surprising. Advanced civilizations all had trump cards. Some were extremely well hidden and not displayed to the public. Of course, Han Xiao had no memories of the Universal Treasures that the players in his previous life did not come into contact with.

Now that he knew, he started having ideas.

"There's no reason to let such a good thing slip."

Han Xiao was very tempted.

One reason was because of how magical the Soul Swapper was, and another was to prevent Modo from using the Soul Swapper on him again in the future. One way or another, he had to make Modo lose this trump card.

At the same time, Han Xiao became more alert too.

"I can't underestimate any advanced civilizations. God knows when they'll bring up another strange trump card by surprise…" Han Xiao closed the file and pondered. "By the way, have you eliminated the parasite yet?"

"Not yet." Feidin shook his head.

"Okay, don't cure Aesop just yet. Although we've acquired everything he knows, the parasite is still useful. He's an important piece of evidence."

The Modo Civilization is the mastermind, and their goal is to force the Black Star Army to retreat. While the Mechanic Emperor worked with Modo secretly most probably because he wants to cause problems to me, I can work around that… With the use of some choice words, I can make this into the Mechanic Emperor choosing to stand on the side of the Super Star Cluster Alliance against the three Universal Civilizations.

As long as he reported this to the three Universal Civilizations, old b*stard Manison's situation would be even worse.

This was not just personal. Han Xiao made a daring assumption. Since the Mechanic Emperor's men came into contact with Aesop too, could he have known about the existence of the Soul Swapper too and was looking for it secretly, hoping to obtain it?

If that was the case, Manison would become Han Xiao's competitor. If he told the three Universal Civilizations about this and had them keep a close eye on the Mechanic Emperor, the Mechanic Emperor's forces would be affected, and it would be more difficult for him to find the Soul Swapper, which was beneficial to Han Xiao.

"Since the three Universal Civilizations are on my side, it would be a waste not to make use of that. It's worth trying."

All kinds of thoughts flashed through Han Xiao's mind. He analyzed the situation and felt that this was doable. Therefore, he walked to the side, took out the communicator, and called Urranrell's private number.

After a while, the communication got picked up, Urranrell's face appeared on the screen.

"Black Star, I'm in a meeting. What is it?"

"I've discovered a piece of intelligence recently. It's about the Mechanic Emperor…"

Han Xiao explained what had happened, naturally adding some 'color' to it, while also displaying evidence such as Aesop to prove he was not making it up.

Hearing this, Urranrell's expression became serious.

"You're saying that, after the Intelligent Plague, not only did the Mechanic Emperor not regret it and change for the better, he even got worse and secretly joined the Super Star Cluster Alliance, executed confidential missions, and is helping them to fight the three Universal Civilizations?"

"Yes, that's right."

Han Xiao agreed with it without any change of tone, clearly experienced with framing others.

"… Okay, I get it. This is a very important piece of intelligence. I'll inform the federation and the church to quickly come up with a solution."

Urranrell nodded solemnly and quickly hung up the communication.

Seeing this, Han Xiao smirked.

As the saying went, one's happiness was built on another's pain. The unluckier Mechanic Emperor got, the happier he was.

Old Manison, don't blame me for this. This treasure and I are fated. You already have so many Universal Treasures. Don't fight me for this one.

At this time, Nero walked in.

"Godfather, where do we start the search?"

"Hmm, before Aesop got attacked, he made one last contact with the Modo Civilization's troops. Start with that," Han Xiao said.

Since he now knew that Modo was the mastermind, it was clear when Aesop got infected, and that would be a clear lead. That secret transport fleet of the Modo Civilization had to have been carrying the Soul Swapper, and they would have to return through secret stargates and transport the Soul Swapper back. Hence, he had to find them as soon as possible.

This time, Han Xiao suddenly thought of something and said, "By the way, I remember that one ship survived among the tracking teams that coincidentally found the Modo Civilization's fleet. Go capture them immediately."

Having uncovered the functions of the Soul Swapper, he speculated that there might be spies in those teams, and the spies were most likely in that tracking team that survived.

"Hmm? This spaceship has lost contact?"

Manison was a little surprised to receive this report from his subordinate.

There seemed to be only one explanation for this situation, that Black Star had caught up with Aesop and hacked the spaceship of his subsidiary organization.

"Weird, how did Black Star get this information?" Manison frowned slightly.

The focus of his work recently had been on searching for the Soul Swapper, on which he had already made some progress, but he was also paying attention to Aesop.

From the way Manison looked at it, the subsidiary organizations he had left in the Shattered Star Ring were very well hidden. With their help, they should be able to easily get Aesop out of the Shattered Star Ring.

However, the reality was completely different. It was as if Black Star knew the whereabouts of his subsidiary organization like the back of his hand. He could follow them anywhere they went.

Manison thought that his subsidiary organizations were very well hidden, which was why he felt the odds of success were high if he worked with the Modo Civilization using that.

However, now that he looked at it, Black Star seemed to already have eyes on his subsidiary organizations, and there was a risk of them being all exposed. If worst came to worst, more than half of the forces he had operating in the Shattered Star Ring would be completely obliterated. It would be a huge loss!

Manison clenched his fist before slowly letting go. He did not look too happy.

"No matter what, now that Black Star caught Aesop, he'll know about the Soul Swapper, so he has become my competitor… I have to speed up now. My losses will only be made up for if I get the Soul Swapper!"

Chapter 1164: Lockdown and One Step Ahead

"Message from the frontline. They've lost contact with Aesop. He's possibly been captured by Black Star."

As this report was read by a Modo Civilization upper echelon, the conference room was filled with dead silence.

After quite some time, a top military officer finally said, "The plan must've failed. The situation is now dire. Do you guys have any ideas?"

"I thought the Mechanic Emperor would have definitely completed the mission. I didn't expect him to be this useless and unreliable," someone said. "Could he have deliberately divulged the information to Black Star, using that to fix his relationship with Black Star?"

"He wouldn't do that. You don't have to doubt him." The Modo Three Kings shook their heads. "It's not his style to fawn upon Black Star, and his hatred with Black Star won't be resolved this easily, nor would the three Universal Civilizations stop being cautious toward him… You guys should think about how to deal with the impact of the mission failing."

They knew that the Mechanic Emperor was not to be blamed for this. Even the Mechanic Emperor, whom they had high hopes for, could not transport Aesop out, not to mention their own forces.

Even so, the upper echelons present still unavoidably felt disappointed with the Mechanic Emperor.

"There are souls of our soldiers inside Aesop's body. Black Star will be able to get our plans from them. Never mind if he knows about our plan, I'm only worried about him knowing about the Soul Swapper," another upper echelon said.

The Modo Civilization had already considered the consequences of failing while they came up with the plan. They looked like they did not want to be discovered, but it was actually only because it was required for the framing. Modo was not afraid of Black Star finding out that this was their doing.

After all, they were enemies. The Black Star Army would not stop attacking them even without this conspiracy, so they were not afraid of enraging Black Star.

Even if the three Universal Civilizations knew about it, Modo had nothing to fear either. They were already at war with the three Universal Civilizations anyway.

All the Modo Civilization really worried about was that Black Star might find out about the Soul Swapper after the plan failed.

However, since they had chosen to use the Soul Swapper for the mission, this was a risk they had to take.

Moreover, the Soul Swapper was not in their hands now and had been taken away by the Soul Swap Twins, which meant there were even more uncertainties.

"Speaking of which, why haven't the Soul Swap Twins contacted us yet? The mind trap should've triggered long ago," someone wondered.

"That's right. It's been almost a month. Have their sub-personalities still not awakened?"

"Could there have been an accident and the Soul Swap Twins have suppressed the awakening of the sub-personalities? But how is that possible? They're Grade Bs at most, or is this the Soul Swapper's ability too?"

"No matter what, we have to prepare for the worst," one of the Modo Three Kings said with a deep voice.

From their perspective, mind traps set by a Beyond Grade A on Grade Bs should be completely safe. However, even the ones in charge of the Marwell plan did not know everything about the Soul Swapper. The Soul Swap Twins were the only ones they knew that could use the Soul Swapper, and only the two of them knew about all its functions.

"We have to do something. How about we get our Beyond Grade A to look for them in the Shattered Star Ring?" someone suggested.

"No, a Beyond Grade A is too conspicuous. If his identity as our direct member is exposed, he won't be able to return. Black Star won't mind adding another item to his collection."

Most of the people present did not agree with sending a Beyond Grade A to find the Soul Swapper, since that Beyond Grade A might not be able to come back.

Should that happen, not only would they have not found the Soul Swapper, but they would also lose a Beyond Grade A!

The Modo Civilization had very complicated feelings about the Soul Swapper. On the one hand, they placed great importance on its functions, but on the other, they used it very cautiously.

Throughout the years, they had tested trillions of people, and only the Soul Swap Twins could use it. Without the two of them, this Space Wonder would be like a piece of junk. Furthermore, they only used it to execute conspiracies and plots most of the time, such as turning important people into their men. However, when it got discovered and the souls of the people they swapped in got interrogated, Modo's involvement would be discovered too and bring them trouble. Therefore, they hardly ever used the Soul Swapper. It mostly collected dust in storage.

Hence, although the upper echelons present really wanted to retrieve it, they were not willing to pay too high a price. They felt it was not very worth it.

Bang!

A top military officer slammed the table and interrupted the discussion. He clenched his teeth and said, "Damn it, we're so restricted in someone else's territory. We could've toyed with Black Star all we wanted if this happened in our territory."

Everyone felt powerless.

It was what it was. Black Star had way too few weaknesses, and they were out of ideas.

…

About ten days later, inside the main ship office of the Black Star fleet, Han Xiao received the summarized data from Phillip and scanned it through.

"Is all the information here?"

"Yes, hum… This is all the information we've collected about the Soul Swapper."

In the past ten days, the Black Star Army had started a large-scale search around the clues acquired from Aesop.

Firstly, they captured the tracking team that had their souls swapped and got some new information about the transport team from back then.

Originally, according to the plan, these spies would be swapped away again after the mission was complete, making it look like an accidental death, not leaving any clues behind.

However, the Soul Swap Twins' escape caused them to be trapped inside the bodies of the Black Star Army soldiers. They did not dare contact Modo's men because Black Star was monitoring the quantum network, nor did they know about the Soul Swap Twins escaping. They thought that they had to continue hiding and were caught red handed.

After acquiring information from these people, Han Xiao once again used the power of Destiny's Child, and with some luck, they captured quite a few Modo Civilization battleships that had yet to leave the Shattered Star Ring. From these people, he found out that the Soul Swap Twins had escaped.

However, the leads stopped there. Modo's men had no idea where the Soul Swap Twins were.

Han Xiao looked at the information collected, slightly shook his head, and sighed. "The Soul Swap Twins can keep changing bodies. It won't be easy to find them."

He was not an expert in the soul area, but he did know someone who was—the leader of the Holy Accord organization, Oathkeeper, the current master of the Soul Flame.

This guy might have a way to find the Soul Swap Twins quickly. After all, no matter how many times they changed bodies, their souls would remain the same.

However, when Han Xiao tried contacting Oathkeeper, he was told that Oathkeeper had entered the Sanctum and had yet to return, so this method was out of the question.

"The current methods are only virtual technology, Bold Explorer, and luck, which are not very efficient…" Han Xiao pondered. "The Mechanic Emperor should be looking for the Soul Swapper, too. I can keep a close eye on him."

When searching for Modo's troops, Han Xiao had found out that some other spaceships of the transport fleet were also missing.

However, these spaceships were not in his hands. With some investigation, he discovered that it was related to the Mechanic Emperor's subsidiary organizations, which basically proved that the Mechanic Emperor was looking for the Soul Swapper.

Since he framed the Mechanic Emperor more than half a month ago, the three Universal Civilizations had already taken action. A part of the subsidiary organizations under the Mechanic Emperor that were disguised as legal organizations were temporarily seized.

Not only did this cause quite a loss for the Mechanic Emperor, more importantly, it meant that a lot of the Mechanic Emperor's subsidiary troops were frozen, so the manpower he could use right now was tremendously reduced. This indirectly made it harder for the Mechanic Emperor to find the Soul Swapper.

However, Han Xiao felt that the Mechanic Emperor should have known about the Soul Swapper before he did. Furthermore, the Mechanic Emperor's home was in the Primeval Star River, just like Modo, so he might know something he did not. Han Xiao felt that keeping a close eye on him might give him some surprises.

"Continue the search," Han Xiao said. "Report any and all situations to me. Keep an extra close eye on the Mechanic Emperor's subsidiary organizations. Don't let any one of them leave our sights."

…

At the edge of the Shattered Star Ring, Planet Earth Ring was a transit station planet located near the inter-star field stargate that had a huge amount of traffic every day. A ton of galactic flights resupplied all kinds of resources. The management of the planet was a Star Cluster civilization of the Shattered Star Ring, so this was a government-controlled public transit hub.

The streets were crowded, prosperous, and filled with countless different races.

Half a month had passed since the search for the Soul Swap Twins began. A man and a woman walked on the street, carefully observing the surrounding while conversing softly. It was the Soul Swap Twins, Jill and Warren.

"Elder bro, anything from your sub-personality these few days?"

"I just suppressed it three days ago, but my souls are running out. We'll have to top up on some souls today."

"Me too. This planet has a lot of people, so it's a suitable target. This is our last stop before leaving the Shattered Star Ring. We have to absorb as many souls as possible so it can last longer," Warren said softly.

"Don't do anything now. Wait till we're about to leave." Jill kept his voice down.

Their goal was to leave the Shattered Star Ring. Through changing their bodies continuously, they had finally arrived at the edge of the Shattered Star Ring. They planned to resupply there and then escape the Star Field through the stargate.

In order to suppress their mind traps, they absorbed quite a lot of souls on the planets they passed by, continuously 'charging up'. Most of which were beasts, but that was not because they suddenly became kind and merciful; absorbing too many intelligent lives would attract attention, which was not beneficial for staying hidden.

Now that they were at the edge of the Star Field, they knew they would be mostly safe if they got out. Hence, they planned to go for a big one and absorb a lot of souls, hoping to find a way to completely defuse the mind traps.

This way, they would not have to commit any crimes in the other Star Fields and could hide themselves perfectly.

"We're finally going to leave the Shattered Star Ring. We'll soon have real freedom." Warren's tone was thrilled and filled with infinite hope for the future.

"This is the first step of our conquest!"

Jill clenched his fists. His eyes were gleaming with excitement.

We're finally about to take the first step of fulfilling their ambitions. Our imprisoned days have finally come to an end. As long as we have enough time to grow, given how magical the Soul Swapper is and how talented we are, we'll certainly become a big deal in the universe!

While the two of them were dreaming about their future, a sudden change occurred, and the alarm suddenly rang throughout the city!

Woo!

The piercing alarm echoed throughout all the streets. Countless people looked up with surprise, not knowing what was going on.

"What's going on?"

"This is a planetary alarm. Has someone come to attack the planet‽"

The people on the streets started panicking, including the street the Soul Swap Twins were on.

"Elder bro, are they here for us?" Warren looked anxious.

"Don't panic! No one should be able to find us, and even if someone did, they wouldn't create such a huge commotion for it." Jill was unsure too.

At this time, someone pointed at the sky and yelled, "Look, a fleet!"

The people looked up. Battleships penetrated the atmosphere and hovered in midair, and mechanical soldiers shrouded the sky. There were no organization symbols, so they did not know what organization this was.

This time, the sound of spaceships taking off continuously sounded. The garrison of Planet Earth Ring hastily arrived and loudly questioned what was happening in the public communication channel.

"This is the Planet Earth Ring Garrison Fleet Command Center. You have broken the Dock Parking Law by penetrating the planet's atmosphere without authorization. Please identify yourselves immediately!"

After a full two seconds, the voice of an old man finally sounded in the public communication channel.

"I'm Mechanic Emperor Manison. I'll be taking over this planet temporarily."

As he said that, countless people shockingly realized that their communicators had lost network connection. They were no longer able to send any messages out.

The people were in an uproar. At this point, they clearly knew that the Mechanic Emperor had cut off the communication of the entire Planet Earth Ring with the outside world. He had locked down the quantum network of the planet!

"Mechanic Emperor‽ What is he doing here?" Jill widened his eyes in shock.

The two of them had escaped early, and Modo had partnered with the Mechanic Emperor after that. They thought that they were just innocent passersby at this point.

They were just one step away from their beautiful future, and now they got into an accident right before that. They were both shocked and enraged.

However, no matter how arrogant Jill was, in the face of the great Mechanic Emperor, he knew there was no way he could mess with him. The only thing he could do was pray for the Mechanic Emperor to quickly finish what he came for and open up the lockdown so that they could leave.

…

At the same time, within the main ship above Planet Earth Ring, Manison's Lord's Avatar covered in electric sparks stood before the porthole, looked at the hostile and tensed garrison fleet, and calmly said, "Lock the entire planet down. Don't allow any life form to leave. The target is right here. Filter the life forms of the entire planet till we find them!"

Outside the window, countless mechanical soldiers descended onto the ground and controlled the panicking crowd. Countless screams of pain shot up the sky and faintly reached Manison's ears.

He scanned through the surface. He was completely certain the Soul Swap Twins were on Planet Earth Ring.

His tracking process was not the smoothest. This was not his territory, so he could not keep such a high profile like the Black Star Army could. He secretly seized a few transport ships only to discover that the Soul Swap Twins had already escaped, and his leads ended there too.

However, Manison acquired extra information from his mole in Modo and knew about the mind trap. He then searched for any place where a large number of life forms had turned into vegetables and lost their souls, and he speculated that it was the doing of the Soul Swap Twins.

Through finding similar incidents, he confirmed the escape route of the Soul Swap Twins and finally locked onto the Soul Swap Twins' whereabouts today.

Due to the fact that his subsidiary organizations were already exposed and were being uprooted, Manison was no longer worried about getting found out, so he locked down the entire Planet Earth Ring.

If not because most of his subsidiary organizations were suddenly frozen by the three Universal Civilizations, which led to him almost losing the lead mid-way and delaying him by a few days, he felt that he would have reached this point long ago.

However, despite the obstacles and challenges, he still succeeded!

Manison shook his head.

Although the mind trap isn't a highly confidential secret, none of these basic level crews know about it, so of course, Black Star doesn't either. Hence, he can only roam around, relying on luck, which is also why he got lured away by me so easily some time ago… Tsk, it's too early for you to fight me, Black Star.

A few days ago, he had deliberately made one of his subsidiary organizations lock down a planet very far away, acting as if he had found the whereabouts of the Soul Swapper to attract Black Star's attention.

This successfully lured away a large batch of the Black Star Army's fleet. From the way he looked at it, even if Black Star had already noticed this, he would not be able to reach Planet Earth Ring any time soon.

However, to be safe, Manison still locked down the quantum network of Planet Earth Ring and delayed the time of the Black Star Army receiving any information.

He planned to get away as soon as he got what he came for. Afterward, even if the advanced civilizations held him responsible for it, there was no way he would throw up what he had already swallowed.

Chapter 1165: Encounter and Confrontation

In the command center of Planet Earth Ring, the manager of the planet was startled by the Mechanic Emperor's name and only spoke cautiously after more than ten seconds of silence.

"Your Excellency Mechanic Emperor, Planet Earth Ring belongs to the Razo Civilization. You have broken the Planetary Management Law set by the Shattered Star Ring Civilization Alliance by locking down this planet. We hope you can give us a proper explanation."

"I'm chasing fugitives. When I'm done, I'll leave. It'd be best for you to step back and not cause any trouble." Manison's calm voice sounded from the public channel.

"… No, we have to stay. According to the rules and regulations, we must report this to the upper echelons of the civilization afterward."

"Whatever."

Manison hung up the communication.

The manager of Planet Earth Ring did not dare resist. He suppressed his anger and ordered the garrison fleet to standby in a defense formation, but he did not disrupt Mechanic Emperor's actions.

Although the Razo Civilization was one of the Star Cluster civilizations of the Shattered Star Ring, now that their communication with the outside world was cut off, the garrison fleet on this planet was no match for the Mechanic Emperor.

The manager was not going to sacrifice his troops for nothing, so he chose to stand aside with caution. This went against his duty, but he could only be flexible.

Without the obstruction of the garrison fleet, Mechanic Emperor's mechanical troops started to search through the civilians on a large scale, not missing out on anything that breathed. They chased everyone out to the streets and forced them to stand in lines.

No matter how arrogant, all the Supers obediently followed the Mechanic Emperor's instructions.

Of course, there were some civilians who just could not grasp the situation. The fists of mechanical soldiers would not have mercy, and after thousands of rioting tourists were beaten up, the rest all became quiet.

Jill and Warren were squeezed by the crowd into a line. They looked around with caution and panic.

The two of them were intimidated by the Mechanic Emperor's troops. They secretly used the Soul Swapper to communicate with each other's souls.

"Elder bro, do you think the Mechanic Emperor is here to catch us?" Warren was worried.

"It can't be. Didn't he say? He's here to catch fugitives, and we're not fugitives," Jill assured him.

"But even if he's not here looking for us, since the search is so thorough, there's a chance we'll get exposed too."

"That is a problem indeed…"

Jill looked gloomy and was in a very bad mood. He was partly worried about the situation, but he was also gloomy because he noticed that someone had squeezed his butt.

He glared behind him and saw a mercenary-looking red-skinned beastman moving his hand away while giggling. The Beastman then flexed his arm and displayed his muscles, even giving him a confident look… Only low-grade beastmen with strong desires would still be thinking of reproduction in times like this.

Jill felt a disgusting chill running through his body. He quickly tightened his clothes.

"How about we find an opportunity and swap into those who've already been checked?" Warren suggested.

"Let's see how it goes first. We'll temporarily stay put, and if things are not going well, I can swap you into my body, and we can share one body temporarily… Wait, no, I'll swap into your body."

Jill's mouth twitched. He regretted choosing a rather attractive body.

…

The search was going on one batch after another, and Manison was monitoring the process in the main ship.

"Let me see how long you can last."

Manison's tone was calm.

The Soul Swapper was unique. All ordinary detection methods were useless. Furthermore, the target could swap into different bodies at any time, so rechecking again and again would be very troublesome.

He planned to send batches of people who finished the check into different spaceships, away from the range of the Soul Swapper and put them in quarantine.

This way, as the number of people was reduced, the Soul Swap Twins would sooner or later activate their abilities and most likely swap into those who had already been checked. However, they did not know that he would still carry out multiple checks even after the quarantine, hoping to trap the two of them in smaller crowds.

Also, another goal of the quarantine was to take away all the people on the planet, including even the garrison fleet. This way, he would have plenty of time to slowly filter and check through them.

If the Soul Swap Twins used their abilities, the shells that had lost their souls should faint, which would be a clue too. Even if the Soul Swap Twins could swap multiple souls around and mix up the identity of the bodies that fainted, as long as it happened, it would prove that they had used their abilities. Furthermore, doing this would definitely cause mass confusion.

Manison had prepared many plans, among which the most extreme was slaughtering the entire planet. Killing life forms with souls one after another would definitely be able to force the Soul Swap Twins to appear. However, the consequences of that were too severe. He would not use this plan unless he had no other choice.

"In about two hours, all the people on the planet will be separately quarantined in different ships. Not the most efficient, but good enough. There's still plenty of time…"

While Manison was calculating the time, he suddenly sensed something and suddenly turned around to look behind.

Woo!

The alarm of the spaceship rang at the same time. In the distance, streams of hyperdrive light appeared and stopped nearby. The bright blue light dissipated, showing a completely black fleet. An organization symbol that Manison could never forget was engraved on these ships' exterior armor. It was the Black Star Army!

"How did they find me?" Manison was shocked.

That's strange. This fleet clearly got rid of its trackers. How did the Black Star Army find this place? Prophecy? But the spaceships' information disruption devices are still working. Aesop shouldn't be able to accurately foresee the exact location. Is there an even stronger prophet?

This is getting troublesome. Black Star's noticed what's happening here. Change of plan, I must speed up and get everyone into the ships.

… However, luckily, only an ordinary search fleet is here. There are just more than thirty fleets.

Manison responded instantly. He waved his hand, and a large group of mechanical troops immediately turned and charged toward the Black Star Army fleet.

He planned to eliminate Black Star's men first so they would not disrupt him.

However, the next moment, three powerful energy presences erupted in the Black Star Army fleet!

Woo!

The energy detection radar's reading exceeded the limits instantly!

Manison was stunned for a moment.

"Three Beyond Grade As‽"

In his sights, three silhouettes flew out of the Black Star Army and stood opposite his mechanical army. They were Black Star, Ames, and Hila!

Han Xiao scanned through the situation of Planet Earth Ring and smirked. He connected to the public channel and mocked, "Yo, looks like I'm almost late."

"Why are you here?" Manison did not bother chatting with Han Xiao at all.

"Oh? Are you asking me why I wasn't lured away by your bait?" Han Xiao curled his lips. "The Shattered Star Ring is my territory. If I got toyed with by you so easily, where should I put my face?"

Actually, the bait Manison set some time ago almost fooled him, and this fleet did indeed lose its initial trackers.

However, as a peak Beyond Grade A Virtual Mechanic who was in his own territory, Han Xiao also did a deep search. He analyzed what all of the routes Manison's troops took had in common and also discovered the vegetable incident of multiple planets. After some cross referencing, it matched with the route of one of Manison's teams.

Although the Great Mechanic Han did not know about the mind trap, it did not stop him from speculating that this was the clue Manison was going after.

Therefore, just like the Mechanic Emperor, he locked onto the Soul Swap Twins' escape route according to those incidents and sent a fleet right to Planet Earth Ring.

Therefore, this army fleet did not come here by following the Mechanic Emperor but instead happened to encounter the Mechanic Emperor, which proved he was right.

The three of them were originally not in the fleet, but Han Xiao had the fleet bring a 'Throne'. He received the news the instant this fleet discovered Mechanic Emperor, and immediately used the King to teleport all three of them here, hence this moment.

While the two of them confronted each other, the manager of Planet Earth Ring was overjoyed and quickly spoke in the public channel.

"Your Excellency Black Star! I'm the manager of Planet Earth Ring. The Mechanic Emperor has forcefully taken over the planet, and we are powerless to resist. Luckily, you're here. Please help us. The Razo Civilization will definitely thank you for it after!"

Initially, the manager of Planet Earth Ring could only watch and feel powerless while filled with rage. Now that Black Star was here, it was like he had caught a lifebuoy. He immediately asked for help.

It was known that the Shattered Star Ring was protected by Black Star now. In the manager's eyes, Black Star was on his side.

Han Xiao casually waved. "Hmm, take your troops off the planet. Leave the rest to me."

"Roger!"

The Planet Earth Ring manager brought the garrison fleet aside to watch without hesitation.

He did not agree when the Mechanic Emperor asked him to leave, but as soon as Black Star did, he left instantly. In the Shattered Star Ring, Han Xiao was much more respected than Manison.

Seeing this, Han Xiao then turned to the Mechanic Emperor's ride and snorted.

"I'm right here. Aren't you going to come out and meet me?"

About ten seconds later, Manison's Lord's Avatar finally flew out.

"Black Star, you've come to mess up my plan again," Manison said coldly. Although his voice was monotonous, it still had a sense of frustration and anger.

"Hehe, Mechanic Emperor, I won't play games with you. Our goal should be the same. It's right here on Planet Earth Ring, and it belongs to whoever's more capable."

Han Xiao crossed his arms and looked firm.

Actually, he was filled with joy on the inside. Originally, he had no excuse to fight with this old b*stard, but now that he had one and met him, he looked at Manison like he was looking at a portable talent inventory.

Manison looked at the three of them and said coldly, "You think your victory is certain just because it's three against one?"

"Haha, you're mistaken." Han Xiao curled his lips. "I alone am enough to fight you. The two of them won't interfere."

Hearing this, Ames and Hila both turned to him and silently stared at him.

Seeing this, Han Xiao coughed and softly said, "Ahem, the two of you are responsible to search the planet and find the target. Hila, you have some knowledge in the mind area, so it's suitable for you to find them, while Ames' force field makes catching people more convenient."

"You said you'd let me help in the fight…" Ames frowned slightly.

"That's when we fight Modo. Leave the Mechanic Emperor to me. I'm going to fight him one on one."

"Am I a burden?" Ames narrowed her eyes.

"… Just a little bit." Han Xiao was very honest and did not find any excuse in times like this.

Ames's eyes twitched, but she thought about it and realized she could not object.

She gave Han Xiao a glare and flew toward Planet Earth Ring.

Hila tilted her head and pondered for a while before raising three fingers.

"Three times."

"What three times?" Han Xiao wondered.

"I've lost the chance to fight someone as strong as the Mechanic Emperor, so you'll have to spar with me seriously three times afterward, and you can't reject it no matter when I ask for it."

"Alright, alright, not to mention three times, I'll spar with you thirty times even if you want to." Han Xiao sighed.

"Okay, thirty times it is. It's a promise!"

Hila nodded with satisfaction and instantly followed behind Ames with the fleet.

Han Xiao's eyes twitched. He was speechless.

This tomboy's combat maniac trait had been getting even more and more intense, and god only knew where she learned to be this cheeky.

Removing Ames and Hila was an attempt to try to trigger Beyond Grade A challenge mission. Otherwise, given how thick Han Xiao's skin was, he would not ask for a duel for no reason.

Han Xiao looked at old Manison and said, "Alright, now no one will disturb us. It's a rare opportunity. Now that we've coincidentally run into each other, we have to get properly intimate."

Manison watched Ames and Hila landing on Planet Earth Ring and did not stop them.

He knew that as long as he did not defeat Black Star, stopping them would not do anything.

Seeing that Han Xiao had stayed behind alone, Manison slowly said, "If the three of you had come at me together, it might have been quite troublesome for me. Yet, you've actually decided to fight me alone. How brave."

"Yo, you're saying it as if I lost to you last time. Why do I seem to recall it being a tie?"

Manison mirthlessly laughed. "Black Star, you should have a clearer idea of how real that 'tie' was than me. Without more than a dozen people helping you this time, do you really still think this will still end as a tie?"

"Tie? No, no, I didn't think that." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. "I'm here with my original body, and crushing your Lord's Avatar is my goal today. It's time to refresh my achievement."

"Hehe, I admit, that special technique of yours to burn your potential can grant you power to match me, but that's all. Defeat me? You're a hundred years too early! Plus, how much potential do you have to throw away? If this is the source of your confidence today, I'm guessing it's not going to end well for you."

"You never know if you don't try."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, his body trembled, and Mechanical Force sparked around him. His energy level rocketed as he quickly entered combat stance.

Seeing this, Manison shook his head, his energy level rising too. The gold Mechanical Force seemed to have painted his Lord's Avatar gold.

"Looks like I'm quite lucky today to receive a pleasant surprise. Since you dare face me with your original body, I'll gladly take your Spacetime Amber as a compensation from you."

Chapter 1166: Shaken Manison

Boom!

Like thousands of thunder strikes happening at the same time, raging Mechanical Force erupted like silver dragons.

The people on Planet Earth Ring looked up. It was as if two suns covered in lightning had suddenly appeared.

Two light gates suddenly appeared in cosmic space, and countless machines swarmed out from the secondary dimensional army boxes.

One side was black like storm clouds, and the other side was white like snowy hills.

The mechanical armies surrounded the two of them. Mechanical Force extended out from their bodies and connected their armies, quickly assembling into two giants!

In an instant, two enormous weapons clashed. The mountain-sized black blade slashed onto the middle of the golden trident!

Clank!

A psionic shockwave exploded, extended through the artificial atmosphere of Planet Earth Ring, and caused chain reactions, creating a deafening noise!

Countless people hastily covered their ears with agony on their faces. They felt as if someone was tolling a bell inside their brain. They could feel their brains trembling. Some lost balance like they were drunk, fell onto the ground, and could not control their body.

Outside the planet's atmosphere, two Mechanical Deities had appeared and were already fighting intensely.

Every move of a Mechanical Deity harnessed terrifying power. Even though they consciously distanced themselves from Planet Earth Ring, the aftershocks still triggered countless natural disasters on the planet's surface.

Machinery came out of their Secondary dimensional army boxes nonstop like it had no end. Their machines fought each other under the lead of their own Apostle Weapons and divided the battlefield into countless smaller battles.

The combat artificial intelligences of both sides tried their best to break each other's formation and create situations where they outnumbered the other side. Mechanical soldiers that got occasionally left stranded became targets of focused fire. They then recovered through Mechanical Force and entered the battlefield right after.

Planet Earth Ring's atmosphere was filled with traces of psionic beams that seemed to have formed a net that shrouded the planet.

Occasionally, liquid metal melted by the high temperature would cool down to irregular shaped metal meteors that fell onto the surface, either creating pits on the ground or shattered by the planet's protective shields.

This was not the first fight between Han Xiao and Manison. They had a rough idea of each other's capabilities, so they went full out from the start and released most of their Apostle Weapons.

Old Manison had more than forty Apostle Weapons in all kinds of shapes. Their similarity was that they were all mechanical lives that had existed for many years, so they had a lot of energy in their tinder, meaning they were very strong.

Han Xiao brought up most of his assets too, more than thirty Apostle Weapons led by Psionic Prime, which was more than one and a half times what he had before!

Han Xiao had obtained the Molding Talent [Billion Mechanic Empire—Manison] from old Manison the last time they fought. Not only did it give him all kinds of attribute bonuses, it also increased a ton of core Mechanic abilities including [Apostle Life Creation] by six levels, meaning he could directly create six more Apostle Weapons!

Some time ago, Han Xiao had also built four new Universal Treasures and used the God's Trait Transformation Points all on the Machinery side, increasing its level from five to nine. This also gave him a few more Apostle Weapon allocations.

Hence, Han Xiao had created about ten more Apostle Weapons while watching the situation of the Flickering War unfold. Although there was still some distance from the number of Apostle Weapons Manison had, it was not as large as the last time.

With my current strength, even without Character Summon Cards, I can match up to old man Manison and not just get beat up like last time.

While Han Xiao slashed at the Mechanic Emperor time after time, he was judging the strength difference between him and the Mechanic Emperor.

Every five stages of God's Trait Transformation comprised one big stage. Although he had yet to receive the bonuses from stage ten, his God's Trait Transformation—Machinery was already four levels higher than before, which increased his strength by a huge extent.

Part of his strength difference from Manison was his inventory; he did not have as many high Grade machines as Manison. Another was the huge God's Trait Transformation difference, which was now greatly reduced.

Although normal Beyond Grade A Mechanics could also obtain God's Trait Transformation Points through building Universal Treasures, they did not have the interface and could not apply the points immediately. The God's Trait Transformation Points they obtained could be considered a type of experience or understanding that could only be applied to increase the God's Trait Transformation stages after they spent long periods of time digesting it.

Han Xiao, however, could apply the points instantly, meaning the digestion process was completely skipped, saving a ton of time. This was why he could become stronger in such a brief period. It was something no other Beyond Grade A could replicate.

Considering the large bonuses from [Billion Mechanic Empire], Titan Spinal Center, Gaeta Shockwave Fist, and several new Universal Treasures, Han Xiao speculated that his current strength should be around the same as his strength when he was in the explosive state the last time he fought Manison! The only part that was still weaker would at most be the basic attributes he gained through [Polar Channel Flow—Blood Rage] and [Advanced Strengthened Life].

On the interface, the challenge mission for Mechanic Emperor had appeared as he expected.

Come to think of it, this was the third time he had seen this mission.

I'll use my EXP too so that I can be as strong as possible.

Han Xiao glanced at the interface and spent most of his accumulated EXP into levelling up.

His level rocketed all the way to level 331 before stopping. The remaining EXP was not enough to level up again.

The bonus he received from leveling up now was not a lot at this stage, but every Promotion and evolution would still make him considerably stronger. Therefore, although Awakening Points had a bigger impact on his strength, he did not plan on using EXP on them for the time being.

After all, it was the final stage of Version 4.0. If he did not spend EXP elsewhere, he might be able to accumulate enough EXP to reach level 340 for a Promotion.

Boom!

Every clash between the Celestial Punishment Edge and the trident created powerful energy explosions made of psionic energy and golden thunder.

Feeling the force from every clash, Manison was surprised.

He clearly remembered that the last time he fought Black Star, Black Star's Mechanical Deity's strength in his normal state could not compete with him at all. From his past experience, if Black Star did not use that strange explosive ability of his, he should have been able to totally crush him. However, to his shock, they were on par!

What shocked Manison even more was that the number of Han Xiao's Apostle Weapons had almost doubled. This was not something his explosive state could bring him; it was a display of his fundamental capability!

How the hell does this guy train?

Manison knew that Black Star was known for his quick growth, but he still could not understand it.

Ever since he was young, he had been a genius in the eyes of the people around him. He was the star of his race. He learned everything much faster than others, and no one could ever catch up to him. He surpassed all those who attempted to chase him in no time. He had never met any Mechanic genius that could match up to him.

However, this changed when he met Black Star. For the first time ever, Manison discovered he was no longer the genius.

Black Star seemed to be able to easily do things he could not do, and this created an emotion that he had never felt before in his entire life. It was bitter and sour.

Is this what people call jealousy?

Wait, why am I thinking about this‽

Manison was shocked. It suddenly occurred to him that without him realizing, Black Star had shaken his confidence that he had built over countless years.

His eyes became firm as he instantly suppressed this emotion, cutting away all distractions and returning to a calm state of mind, focusing fully on the battle.

At this time, Han Xiao suddenly swung his blade backward. Like the string of a bow that kept getting pulled tighter, enormous force flowed from the joints of the Titan Spinal Center all over his body into his arms.

Strange hovering devices emerged from the surface of the Mechanical Deity, hovered around the blade, linked with each other, and formed a complex pattern that shined brightly with psionic energy, releasing energy simultaneously into the Celestial Punishment Edge.

A translucent blue light suddenly appeared on the blade like it was coated in a bubble.

As Manison was about to raise his trident and block the attack, Black Star's deafening yell suddenly sounded in his private channel.

"Spatial Tremble—Gaeta Shockwave Fist!"

The next moment, the blade slashed down in an arc!

The force of this attack was much stronger than the attacks before!

Manison sensed it too. He quickly raised his trident and blocked it.

Boom!

Like two mountains clashing into each other, the blue light on the blade was shot out and exploded on Manison's chest, blowing him away directly.

Powerful shockwaves echoed inside his Mechanical Deity. Large cracks quickly appeared on the surface, and armor plates shattered one after another.

Manison's energy flow staggered for an instant. He quickly adjusted and absorbed the mechanical soldiers nearby to repair the damage. He was stunned.

This attack was very powerful. He recalled that Black Star did not use this attack last time. It seemed to be a new Universal Treasure level combat technique that Black Star had learned recently.

However, what he was most irritated by was not the fact that he got forced to back away by a direct attack, but that he was not mentally prepared and was startled by Black Star's yelling.

What the hell are you shouting about in the middle of a fight‽

And you even fu*king sent me a private voice message just for that. Aren't you a piece of sh*t‽

And what's with the flashy name, you think you're a Pugilist‽

Manison was extremely irritated.

Given the current situation, the two of us won't be able to determine a winner shortly, which means the Dragon Emperor and the others can take their time finding the Soul Swapper. If he gets the Soul Swapper, there'll be no point in me fighting him anymore… Looks like I'll have to use more trump cards.

Manison's eyes sparkled.

…

"What a powerful attack!"

At the edge of the battlefield, the manager of Planet Earth Ring and the garrison fleet watched the battle cautiously while being continuously astounded by it.

Although they knew how powerful Beyond Grade As were, watching a battle with their own eyes was not something any video footage could compare with.

"Luckily, we didn't fight with the Mechanic Emperor before Black Star arrived, or we would've been wiped out by a single slap."

The manager of Planet Earth Ring sincerely felt that his decision was very wise.

He turned to look at Ames and Hila, who were searching the planet, and looked confused.

"Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor seem to be looking for the same thing. What are they looking for that's so valuable they're using this many resources?"

At the same time, on the surface of Planet Earth Ring, countless people looked up, astonished, at the battle.

Two Mechanical Deities fought each other at full strength in space. The explosions lit up the dark universe and made things clearly visible even from the surface.

"Elder bro, w-what should we do now?"

Seeing this kind of destructive power, Jill and Warren were both stunned. Fear surfaced in their hearts instinctively.

Only now did the two of them realize how laughable and ridiculous it was to even think about making a move on Black Star back then.

Someone as strong as him would have turned us to dust just by blowing some air, yet we planned to take his body‽

Thinking about it, we were basically committing suicide!

The two of them were the only ones who could use the Soul Swapper, and they had always believed they were the chosen ones. Hence, they had almost blind confidence in the Soul Swapper's abilities.

However, when they finally witnessed the battle between peak Beyond Grade As this closely, they realized how completely ignorant they had been!

It was not surprising. They had been imprisoned by the Modo Civilization for a very long time, and any information they received about the outside world was filtered.

"While their attention is diverted, we have to think of a way to leave. They really seem to be here for us."

Seeing that Black Star had appeared too, Jill knew that things had gone wrong. At this point, he only had one thought in his mind.

Leave the Shattered Star Ring immediately, go as far as possible, and never come out again till we're at Beyond Grade A!

At the same time, Ames and Hila were flying in the atmosphere. Hila released her soul senses and scanned the people on the surface over a large area.

While searching, the two of them also frequently looked at the battlefield in space.

"Looks like they're on par for the time being. We don't have to worry. Black Star will be fine for now," Hila said softly and looked very tempted.

Seeing how intense the battle was between Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor, she felt the itch to join in. Ever since she got the Underworld dimension, she had never fought any Beyond Grade As at her fullest except for Black Star.

However, thinking of the thirty spars Han Xiao had promised her, she reluctantly suppressed her desire for battle.

Ames shook her head and said, "Let's quickly find the targets. The earlier we find them, the earlier we can leave, so he won't have to keep taking the risk of fighting the Mechanic Emperor."

Seeing the battle, she had to admit that she indeed could not provide much help in a battle of this level and would be a burden instead.

Back when she fought Black Star, she had already accepted the fact that Black Star exceeded her, so she would not feel discouraged or anything.

However, the next moment, their expressions suddenly changed, and they simultaneously turned to look at the battlefield.

At this instant, the two of them sensed a few new Beyond Grade A energy sources suddenly flying out from the Mechanic Emperor's secondary dimensional army box!

They were not the energy reactions of Apostle Weapons but actual Beyond Grade As!

"The Mechanic Emperor has more help‽"

Hila stopped in midair with a solemn expression.

"We have to go back and help! We can't watch the army commander get besieged!"

Chapter 1167: Felon

Above Planet Earth Ring, the formations of a black and a white enormous mechanical army clashed with each other like two dragons tearing each other apart. From afar, shattered mechanical parts fell like a thunderstorm. Tens of thousands of machines were destroyed every second.

Despite their gigantic sizes, the two Mechanical Deities were swift as they fought each other. The power of every clash of their weapons could shatter a planet and leave terrifying wounds on each other's bodies. The repair speed could hardly keep up.

The aftershock of every clash of their weapons shattered a ton of mechanical troops that got too close. Occasionally, one of the Mechanical Deities would get blown away, shattering countless mechanical soldiers in its path like an elephant rolling through a bunch of ants.

There were countless artilleries, psionic cannons, and dark energy cannons all over the two Mechanical Deities, blasting away at each other's shields.

As the fight carried on, the energy reaction of the battlefield kept increasing and caused chain reactions. Clusters of dense dark blue energy clouds with destructive power appeared, forming a similar environment to the Psionic Seal Rings of the three Universal Civilizations' mother planets.

The clash between highly dense energy turned the battlefield into an extremely condensed, highly unstable energy field, twisting even the trajectory of light beams and making direct energy beams look curved or even bent.

Looking at the cosmic space through this battlefield was like looking through a strange layer of glass. All the stars had thousands of reflections that formed irregular shapes. From one glance, it was as if the universe was being shattered!

Clank!

The weapons clashed once again. Intense shockwaves penetrated the both of them. They stepped back and distanced away from each other at the same time.

Han Xiao looked at the Celestial Punishment Edge in his hands. There were a few cracks on the blade.

However, the ninth-generation Black Star Alloy was mixed into the Celestial Punishment Edge. Although its tenacity was not as high as the material that the Mechanic Emperor had invented, it had some of Han Xiao's traits, so its recovery speed was faster in comparison, and the Celestial Punishment Edge's durability would recover over time.

Not a lot of time had passed since Han Xiao's arrival, but due to how fast both of them were, they had already fought for tens of thousands of rounds.

"You really are a magical person. When someone thinks they've studied you thoroughly, you always bring more surprises."

Manison's electronic eyes flickered. He looked down and inspected his equipment too. He had a rather complicated feeling.

The energy absorption Universal Treasure armor he had built based on Black Star's Indestructible Body was already heavily damaged. Putting aside the fact that this equipment was not perfected, Black Star's attacks were much stronger than before, which already exceeded the limits of this equipment.

Furthermore, every time Black Star used anything with the 'Gaeta Shockwave Fist' suffix, he would harass him in the private channel.

Manison had been counting. Up till now, Black Star had used that a total of twenty-seven times, all with different names and different ways of attack. Even with the knowledge he had, he still felt this technology was quite interesting.

The damage to the Mechanical Deity was not an issue since it could be repaired by absorbing mechanical soldiers. However, some of the damage penetrated the Mechanical Deity and landed on his Lord's Avatar at the Mechanical Deity's core, causing his Lord's Avatar's durability to drop quite a bit. Manison's avatar clearly had no Indestructible Body, so it would be over once it was shattered.

"You won't be able to live up to your arrogant words like this. How about show me what you've really got if you want to take the Spacetime Amber away from me?"

Han Xiao swiped his hand over the Celestial Punishment Edge's blade, quickly repairing the cracks, and smiled at old Manison.

"… We're Virtual Mechanics, but your combat method is more like Mechanical Pug… ahem, Armed Mechanic. You've taken the wrong path, kid," Manison said coldly.

"Does it matter if I can fight?" Han Xiao raised his brows.

"You're right. There's no limitation on power itself. Being able to fight is more important than anything else… That is why, I'm going to show you the true power of a Virtual Mechanic."

Manison raised his arm and pointed his trident at the light gate of the secondary dimensional army box.

The next moment, the light gate rippled, and a large group of special mechanical soldiers flew out. It was his signature move—the Mechanic Empire, special mechanical soldiers built with AI lives.

However, the most eye-catching thing was not the Mechanic Empire but the three people in front of it. Their Beyond Grade A energy presences were not restrained at all, like three Fixed Stars in Han Xiao's senses.

Han Xiao looked over. These three individuals were of different races, and their biological flesh was mixed with mechanical devices. It was clearly highly advanced mechanical prosthetics.

Intricate machinery covered all of their bodies. Most of their skin was changed into special alloy, and their faces were changed into metal masks, completely taking away their past appearances, only showing their modified electronic eyes that shone with red light.

"So, these are the Felons…" Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

The Felons were old Manison's last trump card. Using highly advanced biological engineering and mechanical prosthetic technology, he modified living Supers into powerful war weapons.

The organs of these Felons would be modified too, especially their brains. Through mechanical technology, he simulated biological tissues and changed their mind into something that could be artificially read and written on, changing their fundamental logic.

At the same time, using Virtual Technology, he uploaded the Felons' consciousness to the quantum network, modifying their soul into Virtual Souls. Then, like other artificial intelligences, they became immune to all psychological and mental attacks, following his orders while maintaining their combat experience.

After the modification, Felons would keep most of their original abilities. As most of their flesh was modified or swapped out, they would not be as strong as before. However, because of the modification, they could enjoy part of the Mechanical Force bonuses from their controller. Although the conversion rate was not as high as the ordinary mechanical soldiers, they actually became even stronger than before!

"Modifying the living bodies of Beyond Grade As? Aren't you afraid of the advanced civilizations and the development union causing trouble for you?" Han Xiao was crystal clear of the situation, but he still acted like he did not know anything on the surface.

"Hehe, they are all my trophies from before. I have the right to do whatever I want to them. I built them long before the association was formed. As for the three Universal Civilizations, do you think they are completely unaware?" Manison's tone was calm.

All the Beyond Grade As that were defeated by Manison had gone missing, so of course, the advanced civilizations and the Beyond Grade As had all kinds of speculations about it. Although they did not know of the Felons, they did suspect that the Mechanic Emperor had been doing such experiments. The Mechanic Emperor's image as a research maniac was too strong; it was hard to imagine he would not study the Beyond Grade As that fell into his hands.

After all, he did not have the Spacetime Amber, which allowed him to open an exhibition like Black Star.

Manison basically never used this trump card because others would know more about it every time he used it. Also, he hardly met any enemy that needed him to use the Felons.

And Black Star was one of the extremely few that he had felt the need to use this trump card on.

Buzz!

Mechanical Force shot out and linked the three Felons.

The red light shined bright in the eyes of the three Felons, and their energy presence rocketed.

Buzz!

The Felon in the middle shivered, also released Mechanical Force and pulled the mechanical troops of Mechanic Emperor around him toward him.

The next moment, an enormous machine appeared. It had a humanoid appearance but also parts of a beast, five spear-like tails, and sharp claws extending from its fingers. It looked very grim and vicious.

The third Mechanical Deity had appeared!

Han Xiao's eyelids jumped.

This meant that the original identity of this Felon was a Divine Throne Mechanic who had mastered [Composite Mechanical Deity]!

He could not help but think of the first time he met the Mechanic Emperor. Back then, old Manison mentioned that it was another Beyond Grade A who was behind the incident of his AI civilization, and he had turned him into part of his collection. Could this Felon be that guy‽

Boom!

While he was speculating, this half-beast Mechanical Deity suddenly sped up and charged at him, its claws aiming for Han Xiao's head.

Han Xiao responded immediately. He turned the blade of the Celestial Punishment Edge and slashed toward it.

Clank!

The two mechanical bodies clashed and trembled. The power of the half-beast Mechanical Deity was weaker, and it got blown away.

However, before Han Xiao could chase after it, he saw the half-beast Mechanical Deity swung its five tails and wrapped them around the Celestial Punishment Edge and the arm that was holding it. This enormous pulling force made Han Xiao stagger!

As for the enemy, not only did it prevent itself from getting blown too far back, it even closed the distance and got dangerously close to Han Xiao. Its claws wreaked havoc on Han Xiao's armor, creating multiple claw wounds.

At the same time, Manison seized the opportunity and struck from the side. Han Xiao's movements were severely disrupted, and he was not able to block it. His Mechanical Deity's wrist got penetrated from front to back.

"Hiss!"

The intense pain from the neural network made Han Xiao inhale deeply.

He could stay evenly matched against Manison alone, but he was not strong enough to fight two enemies at the same time.

This Mechanic Felon received Manison's Mechanical Force bonuses, so its Mechanical Deity was extremely powerful. Even though it was not as strong as his or the Mechanic Emperor's, it was not far from it. Even if he had to fight this Mechanical Deity one on one, he would still have to spend some time to defeat it.

Han Xiao turned around and saw that the other two Felons did not attack him but instead led the Mechanic Empire and charged into his mechanical army, tearing open his formation like a blade through butter.

One of these Felons seemed to be a Pugilist, and another seemed to be an Esper. They were unstoppable among the army, crushing Apostle Weapons one after another.

If this carried on, these two Felons would be able to dismantle all of his Apostle Weapons in less than two hours.

"Such astonishing strength…" Han Xiao sincerely felt this way. The Felons' strength exceeded his expectations.

"Do you realize now how big a mistake it was to decide to fight me? I warned you, but you've disappointed me time after time!"

Psionic energy erupted from Manison's trident and blasted Han Xiao's Mechanical Deity in half.

The half beast Mechanical Deity instantly tore the chest of the Mechanical Deity open and snatched Han Xiao's original body out from inside, grabbing him in its hands. At the same time, its five tails swung everywhere to destroy the mechanical soldiers around, preventing them from assembling into a Mechanical Deity again.

Han Xiao tried to struggle but could not escape the Mechanical Deity's hands. Although his original body was not afraid of getting killed, he could not match up to a Mechanical Deity.

However, he did not panic at all. He looked up at the enormous Mechanical Deity and tutted.

"The weakness of this ability is very clear. You need to bear the energy cost for three extra Beyond Grade As. How long can you last?"

"So what? Will it take that long to eliminate you?"

Manison did not deny this weakness.

The Felons lost a lot of cells that could produce energy for them after they were modified mechanically, so in order for them to still have Beyond Grade A strength, that energy they lost had to be provided. This had to come from Manison.

Although the special prosthetic and energy conversion technology used on the Felons allowed Manison's Mechanical Force to be converted into energy that these Felons with different classes could still use, the conversion rate was no joke. For example, if a Felon used 100 points of energy, Manison had to spend 130 to 170 points of energy. Therefore, he could not last very long.

Now that he used three Felons, he basically had to bear the energy consumption of five to six Beyond Grade As, including himself. If not because his energy recovery speed was extremely quick, he would have been sucked dry in seconds. Even so, the balance of his recovery cycle was tipped over, and his energy was dropping visibly.

"You're right. If this was before, I'd most likely have no choice but to run, sadly…"

Han Xiao shook his head. Not only did he not panic, he even almost burst out laughing.

Old b*stard Manison, I have been waiting for you to use this!

You thought I'm only going to get your talents today?

My [Virtual Purification—Restore] has been waiting for a long time!

This time, Manison raised his enormous mechanical arm and wanted to take Han Xiao from the half-beast Mechanical Deity.

However, halfway through, his arm was suddenly grabbed by the half-beast Mechanical Deity's claw tightly and could not move further.

"Hmm?" Manison was confused. He looked at it and wondered, "What are you…"

Bang!

Before he finished, five tails dashed over and stabbed all into his face!

The Mechanical Deity was taken by surprise. Its brain exploded and turned into countless metal fragments!

The entire Mechanical Deity was sent out flying. A large wound was on its neck.

What happened‽

The sudden change made Manison lost. He was appalled.

Why has my Felon suddenly turned against me‽

Chapter 1168: Crushed!

The Felon's sudden attack completely took Manison by surprise. He subconsciously thought that the Felon malfunctioned, so he instantly tried to give it a new order again.

However, the order got absolutely no response at all. This Felon also did not chase after him but stood still instead, letting go of its hand and allowing Han Xiao to break free.

"What have you done‽" Manison was filled with rage and could no longer maintain his cool.

Everything had pros and cons. While the Felons' consciousness became virtual, immune to mental abilities, and followed all his orders, it also meant that someone could take over them through virtual methods. However, this was exactly why Manison had set up extremely intricate virtual firewalls inside the Felons' brains. If Black Star used Virtual Intrusion, there was no way the firewall would not react to it, and he could not have possibly done it so fast!

Logically, Black Star's Virtual Technology could not even break through his virtual firewall. There should have been no way he could take control of the Felon!

Therefore, he was certain that Black Star must have used some kind of ability that he did not understand, which was even more unbelievable to him. This was the first time he had used the Felons in front of Black Star, so why did he have such a specific method to deal with them?

This time, Han Xiao patted his chest as if patting away non-existent dust. He then said calmly, "In your own words, I'm going to show you the true power of a Virtual Mechanic!"

This was the first time he had used [Virtual Purification—Restore] in actual combat. This ability he had obtained from the Intelligent Plague mission was basically the nemesis of the Mechanic Emperor.

Based on the usual steps of Virtual Intrusion, if he wanted to rewrite the Felons' logic, he would have to break through Manison's virtual firewalls one after another and have a tough fight with old Manison in the Virtual world.

The amazing thing about [Virtual Purification—Restore] was that it completely ignored any virtual firewalls. There was no need for any hacking at all.

This ability could not freely rewrite the target's logic. Its effect was only to help the artificial intelligence recover its fundamental logic. For example, it would have no effect on Apostle Weapons. However, on targets whose consciousness had been modified by virtual technology such as the Felons or the Mechanic Empire, it had an astonishing effect and instantly removed the Mechanic Emperor's control over them!

Earlier, when he fought with the Felon, he had already gotten its combat information and seen that the Felon had kept more than half of its original abilities and talents. This was what was incredible about the Felon technology.

These abilities came from the memories of the Felons, and they would only know how to use them if their memories were intact. If their memories were completely wiped away, so would their combat experience, meaning most of their abilities and talents would disappear too. The Felon would most likely become a white board with only raw strength, and without the essence of what made them strong, they would become tremendously weaker.

This was also the reason [Virtual Purification—Restore] could work.

Han Xiao turned to look at the enormous half-beast Mechanical Deity, which had already recovered its self-consciousness but still looked lost.

His combat memories are basically the only memories he has left, so he most likely doesn't remember who he is. But looking at his actions from earlier, he's probably hostile toward the Mechanic Emperor. Han Xiao's eyes flickered as he thought.

The Felons were all once the Mechanic Emperor's enemies. Even without most of their memories, some things were buried in the bones, such as feeling furious when they saw the Mechanic Emperor.

Without the disruptions, Han Xiao's body quickly assembled into an enormous Mechanical Deity.

He did not say much to the Mechanic Emperor. He just swung his blade, aimed at the other two Felons and the tons of Indestructible Mechanic Empire troops, and used [Virtual Purification—Restore].

The next moment, the Pugilist Felon and the Esper Felon suddenly stood still and looked lost.

This was not the case for the Indestructible Mechanic Empire. They were artificial intelligence lives to begin with; only their logic was rewritten like they were trapped and could not control their own bodies. Now that they had regained consciousness, they were only stunned for an instant before immediately turning around and firing at Manison's mechanical army with incomparable rage.

Manison's mechanical army was in chaos!

Han Xiao did not forget about the virtual aspect of the battle. Ever since the start of the battle, the two of them had been continuously trying to snatch control from one another on the virtual network. Manison had also dispatched a group of artificial intelligences from his artificial intelligence civilization to attack Han Xiao's territory.

As the dim light of [Virtual Purification—Restore] swept by, these artificial intelligence lives instantly recovered and immediately led Han Xiao's data stream to snatch control of Manison's mechanical army!

"This is…"

Manison opened his eyes wide with extreme shock. He was completely stunned.

What the hell kind of ability is this‽

The Felons and the Indestructible Mechanic Empire were two of his extremely important trump cards. However, in front of Black Star, not only were they broken down in seconds, but they even got taken over by him!

Black Star definitely did not have this ability the last time they fought!

Without hesitation, he wanted to use virtual technology to rewrite the logic of the Felons and the Indestructible Mechanic Empire on the spot. However, Han Xiao was not going to let him. Also using virtual technology, Han Xiao once again started the tug of war with Manison to prevent him from regaining control of his troops.

At the same time, Han Xiao ordered his mechanical troops to continue attacking while taking in the Indestructible Mechanic Empire troops and leaving the battlefield.

"Sh*t!"

Manison realized what Han Xiao was planning to do. He wanted to snatch away his ace troops!

In such a dire situation, even Manison felt lost for an instant.

Seeing the situation on the battlefield, he knew that there was no room for any hesitation. He instantly cut off his Mechanical Force link with the Felons and the Indestructible Mechanic Empire.

Now that these troops had turned on him, there was no way he was going to continue providing them with bonuses and waste his own energy. At the same time, he ordered the remainders of his mechanical army to recapture these troops that had become traitors.

Clank!

Without an energy supply, the half-beast Mechanical Deity could not maintain its body and instantly fell apart, turning into tons of mechanical troops that were about to take the Mechanic Felon away.

Of course, Han Xiao was not going to watch this happen. He extended his gigantic mechanical arm, tore through the defenses of the mechanical army, and grabbed the Mechanic Felon who was still dazing off.

Then, nanoparticles flowed in his palm, and he directly absorbed this Felon into the Mechanical Deity.

He tried to give the Felon energy, but the interface showed that he did not meet the requirements. He had to master the Felon technology and be above level 340. Only then could he use the special prosthetic of the Felons to convert his Mechanical Force into their energy. This requirement was similar to the Felon blueprint he had obtained before.

Han Xiao did not mind it. As long as he could take a sample back with him, he could go home and study it slowly to derive the blueprint.

"You motherfu…"

Seeing this, even with Manison's class, he was still filled with a burning rage and wanted to cuss.

Every Felon was a unique product that he had built through blood and sweat, and watching one of them getting stolen right before him by Han Xiao made his heart bleed.

"Come on, don't get so angry. Don't you still have two more? What's the big deal in giving me one?" Han Xiao said with a mocking tone.

Hearing this, Manison's lungs almost burst from rage.

You piece of sh*t!

If I don't crush you today, I won't call myself Palpatine!

Without another word, Manison attacked with his trident like a thunderstorm, almost not putting any focus on defense at all. He was clearly enraged.

"Haha, this is how Mechanics should fight. Come!"

Han Xiao laughed.

I just love exchanging wounds!

He activated [Polar Channel Flow—Blood Rage]. Burning blood gushed out from his heart and shot out from his pores, turning into a thick and dense blood energy. As his health plummeted, his attributes continued to increase.

Explosive power filled his entire body. The blue-gold Mechanical Force received a tint of red too. His Mechanical Deity looked vicious.

At this moment, just with his own abilities, he was already stronger than before when he activated the double Mechanical Senses and The Ancient One Character Cards!

The effect of The Ancient One was an additional twenty Intellect, and extra Perfect Mechanical Sense multiplied his Machinery Affinity by 1.4 and increased the levels of all Mechanic abilities by four.

[Billion Mechanic Empire—Manison] on its own increased his Intellect by fifteen percent, his Machinery Affinity by 1.2 times, and his Mechanic abilities by two levels. At the same time, it also gave him six additional levels on a ton of core Mechanic abilities, as well as an extra bonus when fighting any machinery of ten percent to all attributes and damage dealt, a fifteen percent reduction to damage taken, and a twenty-five percent reduction to energy and stamina consumption!

Just [Billion Mechanic Empire—Manison] alone almost gave him as many bonuses as one more Perfect Mechanical Sense and The Ancient One!

Plus, he now also had four more Universal Treasures and was four stages higher on God's Trait Transformation—Machinery…

"I'm going to crush you today!"

Han Xiao took no step back and let the trident penetrate his chest as he cut off Manison's right shoulder.

The two of them fought viciously like two gigantic beasts tearing each other apart.

…

Ames and Hila had just arrived at the edge of the battlefield. They both stopped when they saw this.

The two of them were originally worried about Han Xiao getting outnumbered, but now it seemed like there was no need to worry.

"He doesn't seem to need our help."

"Then let's go back and continue searching."

While the two of them were about to turn around, Han Xiao's voice suddenly sounded in the communication channel.

"Hila, keep searching. Ames, stay."

Hearing this, Ames was slightly stunned.

"For what?"

"See those two Beyond Grade A prosthetic bodies that are surrounded by the mechanical army? Grab them with your ability."

"Didn't you just say I'm a burden and wouldn't let me help?" Ames raised her brows.

"It was to trick the enemy." Han Xiao was not ashamed at all.

"Humph, I knew you need me."

Ames smiled and was in a much better mood. She joined the battle immediately. She grabbed the two Felons with her force field and started dragging them away.

Under Han Xiao's influence, she did not mind joining a duel at all.

Originally, Manison made the mechanical army surround the two Felons with everything they had, stopping Han Xiao's troops and trying to recapture the Felons to take them back to the secondary dimensional army box once again.

The two Felons did not have full memories, but they still had their combat experience. Noticing that the Mechanic Emperor wanted to capture them again, they naturally resisted. However, without a source of energy, they became much weaker and got overwhelmed by Manison's Apostle Weapons. If this had carried on, they would have been captured.

However, as Ames joined in, the situation changed. Her force field Esper Ability was incredible at crowd controlling. It instantly tore the defenses of Manison's troops open and allowed Han Xiao's mechanical army to charge in and help the Felons.

Seeing this, the expression of Manison, who was fighting with Han Xiao, instantly changed.

You piece of sh*t, what happened to one on one‽

Thousands of curses rushed to the tip of his tongue. In the end, they all combined into one sincere, enraged shout.

"Black Star, you're shameless!"

"We're in the middle of a fight. Don't flatter me."

Han Xiao was not affected at all, even being in the mood to make a joke.

He had already reached the highest duration for the challenge mission of Manison. The mission was shown as completed now, so there was no need to continue taking a private class from old Manison.

Furthermore, now that Manison's Felons and Indestructible Mechanic Empire had gone out of control, they were basically a huge piece of cake placed right in front of him.

Of course I'm going to ask for my friend to help. Why would I still fight you alone? Did you really think I'm such a battle maniac?

You are now basically a box of treasure!

Boom!

The blade slashed onto the pole of the trident, emitting a ring of shockwave.

Han Xiao raised his brows and mocked, "Yo, weren't you going to fight me head-on till the end? Why have you started guarding?"

Manison remained silent and changed his combat style entirely the next second. He moved from one extreme to another and went completely defensive, clearly wanting to stall for time.

At the same time, his mechanical army gave up on fighting back and focused on retrieving the Indestructible Mechanic Empire troops and the Felons.

It was clear that Manison no longer wanted to decide a winner between him and Han Xiao. All he wanted was to reduce his losses as much as possible.

"Now you want to retreat? It's too late!"

Han Xiao sent multiple 'Getta Hadoken' messages over privately and started his all-out attack on the elderly.

After just a while, Manison was showing signs of defeat all over as he had to minimize the losses of his troops.

Swoosh!

The blade spun and picked Manison's Lord's Avatar out from inside the Mechanical Deity.

Han Xiao instantly used a powerful restraining beam and pulled Manison's Lord's Avatar toward him. He then punched forward with his enormous metal fist.

Due to the tremendous difference in size, not only did the Lord's Avatar not fly out, but it got stuck on the fist.

"Plate!"

Ames understood instantly. She controlled her force field and created an enormous force field barrier in front of the Mechanical Deity like a green wall. They clearly had very high synergy.

Han Xiao's fist slammed right onto the barrier with Manison's Lord's Avatar on it.

Boom!

Enormous, visible spider-web cracks instantly erupted on the force field barrier!

Manison was in the middle of it. The Lord's Avatar was almost flattened.

Still, he did not fight back and was focusing on controlling his mechanical army to throw his Universal Treasures back into the secondary dimensional army box and reduce losses.

The next moment, the Celestial Punishment Edge was raised. A bright dark blue light appeared on its blade as it slashed right down accurately onto Manison's Lord's Avatar.

Boom!

The force field barrier shattered into countless light-green fragments and disappeared.

Given the Celestial Punishment Edge's size, this could not really be called a slash. It was more like throwing a mountain onto an ant!

Han Xiao looked up and saw that Manison's Lord's Avatar had already turned into a pile of floating waste.

On the half of its metal head, the electronic eye flickered a few times before completely dimming. The Mechanical Force on it also slowly dissipated. [Lord's Descent] was deactivated.

Without Manison's Mechanical Force, the secondary dimensional army box instantly shrunk and disappeared.

The troops that had yet to escape all remained there. The golden electronic light on them disappeared as they lost all Mechanical Force bonuses and got surrounded instantly.

"Humph, told you I was going to crush you today!"

Han Xiao felt exhilarated.

Throughout his life, he had experienced losses against the Mechanic Emperor way too many times.

Even though he was the final winner of the Intelligent Plague incident, without those dozen Mechanics who came to stop the battle, he probably would have lost against the Mechanic Emperor back then too.

This time, however, he had finally triumphed completely!

Chapter 1169: I Might Not Have Earned a Lot, But You Definitely Lost a Ton

Without the Lord's Avatar, Manison could no longer keep the secondary dimensional army box open, leaving the rest of the mechanical army with no reinforcements.

Even though Manison could still provide the Mechanical Force bonuses through Quantum Infinite Distance Transmission Channel if he wanted to, it would be meaningless. Almost all of his troops had been seized by Han Xiao. There was no way he could turn the situation around.

Han Xiao asked Phillip to do a count. Other than the millions of normal mechanical soldiers, he also seized two Felons and a ton of Indestructible Mechanic Empire troops.

Old Manison had started to minimize his losses as soon as he realized the situation had turned bad. The Apostle Weapons had run the quickest and all managed to escape, and he had just managed to snatch the Esper Felon back in the end. As for the other two Felons, one was captured by Han Xiao's Mechanical Deity, and he could not bring the other one away because of Ames.

"Nice, nice!"

Han Xiao was filled with joy.

He could reverse engineer the blueprints out of all these mechanical soldiers, especially the two Felons. He could totally derive the technology used.

While he had made a huge fortune, old Manison had suffered tremendously.

He had come to find the Soul Swapper. Not only did he not get it, but he even lost a ton of assets.

Han Xiao could vividly imagine Manison's furious expression right now, and damn did it feel good.

He had finally robbed Manison big time!

However, that left him with some trouble too. The two Felons had regained their self-consciousness, so he had to deal with it.

Han Xiao released the Mechanic Felon inside the Mechanical Deity and let him rendezvous with the other Pugilist Felon. He then surrounded the two of them with his mechanical troops.

Seeing this, the two Felons instantly got into a defense stance, but none of them made a move. Although they could not remember many things, after experiencing the battle earlier, they knew that Han Xiao had saved them. However, they could not trust Han Xiao yet and were worried they might have walked out of a tiger's den and into a wolf's nest.

Han Xiao deactivated the Mechanical Deity, passed through the encirclement, and approached the two of them. He narrowed his eyes and asked, "How much do you guys remember?"

The two Felons exchanged looks and shook their heads.

"I see, so nothing other than the battle earlier. What about your names?"

The two of them shook their heads again.

"No names… only code names…"

"What code names did the Mechanic Emperor give you guys then?"

The Mechanic Felon pointed at himself and then at the other Felon.

"I'm Two. He's Four."

"…"

Hearing these two names, Han Xiao did not know what expression he should give.

Why is Manison so 'whatever' in choosing code names? It doesn't suit their identity as trump cards at all!

Could it be that this b*stard's level of naming things is on par with me?

Looks like even the weaknesses of great people are similar.

Han Xiao rubbed his chin, pondered for a moment, and said, "Alright, you guys should follow me for now. I'll find your identities for you. You were both the Mechanic Emperor's enemies, so it shouldn't be that hard."

The Mechanic Felon Two said quietly, "You are not going to control us like he did, are you?"

"I'm not planning to at the moment, but that might change in the future." Han Xiao shrugged. "But you don't have a choice now, do you?"

Looking at the countless mechanical troops around them, the two of them nodded.

Comparatively, they would not have an even worse time in the hands of this handsome and extraordinary man.

If this man wanted to replicate what the Mechanic Emperor was doing, he would not have said so much to them and would have captured them long ago.

"Who… are you?" Four asked.

"Listen carefully then. The man who stands before you is the army commander of the Black Star Army, protector of the Aquamarine Federation, peak of individual greatness of the Shattered Star Ring, leader of the second strongest organization in the Flickering World, pillar of the Crimson Dynasty, Special Consultant of the three Universal Civilizations, vice president of the Beyond Grade A Association, hero of the universe who defused the Intelligent Plague, owner of the Galaxy Medal…"

"Your name is too long. I can't memorize it all." Four shook his head.

"…Ahem, these are all my titles. You can simply call me Black Star." Han Xiao knew that the two of them did not know who he was, so the more titles he mentioned, the more intimidating he would look.

The two of them exchanged looks and nodded.

They did not have anywhere else to go for the time being anyway, so they did not mind following Han Xiao. Among their few remaining emotions, their hostility toward the Mechanic Emperor was the strongest. They might only have the chance to take revenge if they followed this person before them, or once they were alone, they would be captured by the Mechanic Emperor again.

Han Xiao chatted with them for a while and told the mechanical troops to take them back to the spaceship. He had yet to decide on what to do with the Felons who had regained their self-consciousness, so he decided to keep them under his control and think about it later when the matters at hand had been dealt with.

He looked at the other side and saw that the Indestructible Mechanical Empire troops were gathered at the side and staring at him. Inside the quantum network vision, these artificial intelligences who had recovered were also looking at him, clearly ready to run away if they noticed anything was wrong.

After experiencing the disaster of the Mechanic Emperor, these artificial intelligences had figured out how the food chain worked. Every Mechanic was a predator in their eyes; there was no such thing as trust.

Han Xiao thought about it. With his position, it would not be good for him to talk to these artificial intelligences. It would be like a butcher telling a bunch of pigs that they were pretty. It would definitely cause misunderstandings.

Therefore, after some pondering, he summoned Risda in the virtual domain.

"I'll leave your people to you. Just don't let them run wild."

"Understood!"

Risda was overjoyed.

How many years has it been‽ The day my people are freed has finally come!

Although the process was tremendously different from his imagination of charging into the Mechanic Emperor's nest, the results were positive.

Even though only some of his people were saved, at least he could see hope!

Choosing Black Star back then was indeed the right investment!

Seeing that Risda had gone to communicate with his people, Han Xiao only then looked away and shook his head. He was not optimistic.

Unlike the Felon technology, recovering back to normal did not mean complete freedom for these Indestructible Mechanical Troops. This was because the shells of these artificial intelligences were still linked with the device that transported their recombination materials.

Through the energy transmission channel, Manison could still locate them. Unless the terminal was dealt with, these artificial intelligence lives were prisoners locked inside their shells. Once their shells were broken, Manison could retrieve them any time he wanted.

This was a security measure of the Indestructible Mechanical Troops technology. Han Xiao had yet to master this technology, so he did not know how to break the link.

Therefore, the one and only effective solution at the moment was to keep these Indestructible Mechanical Troops at home. There was no chance he could take them out to battle; Old Manison would never help him to rebuild these mechanical troops with his own resources in his lifetime.

Winning the fight was one thing. Old Manison was still a master who had studied machinery for countless years, so his signature technology would not be dealt with this easily.

Han Xiao was not hoping to fight with the Indestructible Mechanical Troops anyway. Firstly, the players under his command were much more terrifying. Secondly, he was not in dire need of the Indestructible Mechanical Troops technology, as the powerful factor of the Indestructible Mechanical Troops was its almost perfect self-sufficiency, which he could already achieve on his own.

Rather than modifying artificial intelligence lives into Indestructible Mechanical Troops, he would rather restore them and use them to derive the fragmented blueprint of the Domino Virus… That thing's destructive power was many times stronger than the Indestructible Mechanical Troops.

Regardless of whether he could not use them for the time being, making the Mechanic Emperor unable to use them too was the main goal. Of course, these Indestructible Mechanical Troops were not completely useless to him. They were all important intelligence sources. He could ask about the state of the Mechanic Emperor's various bases.

While he was pondering, Hila's voice suddenly sounded in the communication channel.

"Black Star, come here quickly. We've found the target."

"You've found the Soul Swapper? Great job!"

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

He did not forget that the Soul Swapper was the true goal of this trip. Now that he had locked down Planet Earth Ring, he was not going to stop until he found it. With an expert in the soul area such as Hila and the aid of a few kings of luck searching every inch of the planet, there was nowhere the Soul Swap Twins could run. No matter how mysterious and magical the Soul Swapper was, they would get discovered sooner or later.

As soon as Han Xiao returned to the spaceship, he saw the two people who were tied up in the middle of the room. They were both female and had looks of despair on their faces.

"These are the Soul Swap Twins?" Han Xiao looked at Hila and Feidin. "You sure you got it right?"

"Definitely." Hila took out a dark crystal mirror and passed to Han Xiao. "They've confessed to everything. This is the Soul Swapper."

Han Xiao took over the Soul Swapper and looked at the item details on the interface.

Soul Swapper: Space Wonder type item. Unknown origin. Unknown material. Able to swap souls around as the user wishes, ignoring any rejection symptoms and achieving a perfect fit. However, only special individuals are able to use the Soul Swapper. Requirements: Unknown.

Another Space Wonder, and something I never saw in my previous life… Han Xiao was content.

"How did you guys catch them?"

The people all looked at Harrison as soon as he said that.

"Don't look at me. I just casually pointed…" Harrison waved with embarrassment.

"… Okay, got it." Han Xiao's lips twitched.

There seemed to be a difference between luck auras too. For example, Harrison's was incredibly effective in finding treasures.

No wonder the Soul Swap Twins looked like they had lost all hope. They had changed shells countless times and planned countless steps ahead, but in the end, they had lost to luck. Anyone would go mad.

Han Xiao turned to the Soul Swap Twins and asked, "How do you use this?"

"We're the only two people in the entire universe who can use the Soul Swapper, and we're willing to work for you!" Jill quickly said. "You've actually always been my idol! It would be our honor to work for the army!"

At this time, ambitions, hope, and whatnot had all vanished.

Jill only had one thought left—use the fact that they were the only ones who could use the Soul Swapper as leverage to join Black Star's forces so that they could live!

Seeing this, Han Xiao tutted in his mind. Their praise is so rigid. Clearly, they're not very skilled.

"You said that you're the only two who can use the Soul Swapper in the entire universe?"

"It's true. I'm not lying to you. The Modo Civilization has tested trillions of people. Only two of us are able to use it. We're born for the Soul Swapper!"

"You never know till you try. Tell me, how do you use it usually?"

The two of them had no choice but to explain how to use the Soul Swapper.

Han Xiao followed it and got no response, only a notification on the interface.

Detecting… complete. You are not qualified to use the Soul Swapper.

"Looks like I really can't use it."

Han Xiao studied it for a while but got nothing. The interface did not show what requirements he had to meet to be qualified.

He then passed the Soul Swapper to Hila and said, "You guys, don't just stand there. Come and give it a try."

Hila casually tested it and got no response as well. The rest followed one after another.

Looking at this, Jill and Warren still faked their enthusiastic expressions, but a tint of mockery flashed through their eyes.

No matter how many times you guys try it, we're the only masters of the Soul Swapper!

After a while, seeing that they still kept trying, Jill could not help but stress, "Like I said, we are the only qualifiers, no one but us can use the Soul Sw… what‽"

Before he finished, his eyes widened, and he froze in place.

Black ripples appeared on the mirror of the Soul Swapper, devoured Feidin's palm whole, and kept sucking it in.

"Hmm?" Feidin only noticed it after a while and said with surprise, "Did I succeed?"

"That's it?" Han Xiao raised his brows. "Looks like the requirements aren't that tough."

"Yo—Yo—You—You…"

Jill and Warren were stuttering, their eyes wide open.

They could not believe that a qualifier out of trillions of people had just appeared right in front of them!

The two of them had thought that they were the unique chosen ones, but this completely shattered their sense of superiority!

Not only did the Soul Swapper that the two of them saw as a holy relic find a new love right in front of them, but it even looked extremely thirsty like it wanted to suck Feidin in completely!

At this instant, the two of them went completely blank as if their wife who had promised everything to them suddenly rushed into the arms of someone else.

Han Xiao shook his head. "Tested trillions of people and only the two of you qualified. This only proves one thing… just how short of talent the Modo Civilization is."

Jill instantly realized that things had gone south. If they had no value, even staying alive would be a luxury.

Having thought of that, Jill yelled, "We're still useful! We can pass on the experience of using the Soul Swapper for so many years. We can even tell you what missions the Modo Civilization has sent us to do over the years. We can…"

Ka-cha!

Before he finished, his yelling stopped abruptly. His head spun 360 degrees around. His neck was twisted into a knot, and the shattered neck bones penetrated his neck skin.

Ames walked into the cabin and flipped her fingers. Her force field twisted Warren's neck too before terror could even fully appear on his face.

She looked around. her eyes stopped on Han Xiao, and she said, "The lives of these two are mine."

"Spoiled woman…" Han Xiao murmured. "If they're alive, they might spit out quite a lot of intelligence."

Ames was never sensible when Aesop's safety was threatened. She did not even want the Soul Swap Twins to breathe for an extra second.

Hila narrowed her eyes, raised her hand, and made a grabbing gesture. Two gray clusters of fog rose from above the Soul Swap Twins' heads and entered the Underworld mark on the back of her palm.

"I've taken their soul. When I get something from the interrogation, I'll report to you."

"Nice." Han Xiao gave her a thumbs up.

"What about this thing?" Feidin pulled his arm out of the mirror of the Soul Swapper.

"Since you can use it, bring it with you. I'll study it later."

Han Xiao did not mind. He trusted Feidin completely, so letting Feidin carry the Soul Swapper was not a problem. He was in a great mood, so he did not mind these small things.

Han Xiao was overjoyed. "Not only did I snatch away a Universal Treasure, but I even got more surprises from old Manison…"

On the other hand, Manison's situation was at the end of the other extreme—the subsidiary organizations he had left in the Shattered Star Ring were almost all exposed, he did not get the Soul Swapper, and he even lost a load of trump cards.

"Assh*le!"

Manison was furious as he slammed and shattered the table in front of him.

He considered himself a casual and well-mannered person who usually never cussed… unless he could not control it.

The reason he had always been calm and casual was that in the past, no matter how much of his mechanical army he lost, it did not matter because he had all the mechanical troops in the world and that loss was negligible in comparison.

Today, however, he was really hurt.

He never got angry because he was not hurt enough, and now that he was, he was enraged.

Thinking of the fact that two Felons had fallen into the hands of the enemy, Manison's heart was bleeding more than when he lost the Virtual Mutiny Virus core back then.

This was his trump card of trump cards. He had planned to use it to teach Black Star an unforgettable lesson, but never did he expect Black Star to snatch them away!

Even now, Manison still had yet to figure out how Han Xiao did it.

Furthermore, after wasting so many resources, he did not even catch a glimpse of the Soul Swapper. He was close to exploding with rage.

His emotions rarely fluctuated at all. However, after meeting Black Star in the past decade or so, that streak had been completely shattered.

"Black Star! Argh!"

Manison's furious screams echoed in the room.

Chapter 1170: Anyone Can Be the Mechanic Emperor

"Thank you, Your Excellency Black Star, for your help. We'll certainly relay the help you've given to Planet Earth Ring today to the upper echelons."

Inside the cabin, as Han Xiao told his subordinates to get rid of the Soul Swap Twins' corpses, he received a communication request from the Planet Earth Ring manager.

"It's no big deal." Han Xiao waved.

"No, no, it was only thanks to your help that the Mechanic Emperor's evil deeds were stopped. On behalf of the Razo Civilization, I would like to thank you for your help. Please do stay and let us thank you!"

The Planet Earth Ring manager's tone was passionate.

Having just witnessed such a marvelous battle, Han Xiao's image was extremely tall in his heart. He did not dare show any disrespect and hoped to leave a good impression, so his attitude was respectful and enthusiastic.

Furthermore, the Mechanic Emperor coming to cause trouble would affect his political performance, and Black Star defeating the Mechanic Emperor did him a big favor. Black Star might not care, but that did not mean he did not care.

"No need, I'll be leaving after the battlefield is cleaned up." Han Xiao shook his head.

"Alright then, please inform me the next time you come to Planet Earth Ring. I'll display the utmost hospitality." The manager of Planet Earth Ring was full of appreciation.

"There'll be chances in the future."

Han Xiao chatted with him for a while before hanging up the communication. He told Phillip to save his number into the contacts book, where he stored the communicator numbers of all the people he knew till now, forming an enormous network.

He saved not just the numbers of important people but also the numbers of less significant people from various industries. Everyone had their specialties, so they might be of help some time in the future.

Although the quantum network of the planet was in lockdown, everyone on the planet had witnessed what happened. God only knew how many videos had been taken. Once those videos got out, Han Xiao's reputation would certainly grow once more.

After the Intelligent Plague incident, the three Universal Civilizations had continuously promoted his achievement of reaching a tie with the Mechanic Emperor. However, due to it not being completely true at the time, although the effects were quite good, it was not nearly perfect.

This time, however, the recordings of him destroying the Mechanic Emperor's avatar head-on would be the most reliable proof!

Increased reputation was not even the most important. What was most important was that now that the Mechanic Emperor had lost to him this time, he would lose a ton of Machinery Faith believers!

It did not matter even if he lost a few times because he was much younger. However, as the known 'Strongest Mechanic', Manison losing had a completely different meaning. It would be disastrous for his reputation.

There was no such thing as a loyal fan in the Machinery Faith. They believed in whoever was stronger.

If Manison lost his title of being the 'strongest', tons of believers would turn to Han Xiao instead. Manison would become weaker while he would become stronger!

Speaking of becoming stronger, Han Xiao remembered that he had yet to receive the reward for the Manison challenge mission.

The mission was a usual Beyond Grade A challenge mission, giving rewards based on the time he lasted.

Since everyone was there, Han Xiao could finally do the full 'Pet Dragon Touch Feidin Rub Nero Touch Harrison' procedure.

Han Xiao went by them one after another. Harrison was the only one shivering with fear; the other three were used to it. Only then did he open the interface while being stared at by Hila with a strange look.

[Beyond Grade A Challenge Mission—"Mechanic Emperor" Manison] complete!

You have completed all the mission requirements and received 108 billion Experience.

You have received [Character Summon Card: 'Mechanic Emperor' Manison].

Character Summon Card: 'Mechanic Emperor' Manison. [Ancient One]: Your long life has provided you with a wealth of valuable experience. +20% INT, +10% MYS, +2 levels to all skills. Last 24 hours. Usages: 0/2

"Ancient One again?" Han Xiao was surprised.

If he remembered correctly, this should be the third time he had earned this ability from old Manison's Character Summon Card. It was quite a strong advanced talent, so why did he get it so often?

Was it fated that he was meant to be an elderly with rich life experience?

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. He then looked at the part where he could draw one of Manison's talents or skills. This was the most important part.

You have received: Draw one of Manison's abilities/talents.

Note: Manison is a Virtual Mechanic, and your Class is completely compatible with his. You will be able to draw any of his abilities or talents. If you draw an ability or talent that you already possess, that ability or talent will be enhanced.

Randomizing… complete!

Please select one from the five options below as the reward:

[Apostle Life Creation] - Ability: Lord Mechanic ability, you can modify the target machine into an 'Apostle Weapon', granting it tremendous combat capability enhancement. Basic allocation: 3. Allocation is increased by 1 every level. (You already possess this ability, can be enhanced.)

[Multidimensional Mind Model] - Talent: Changes the calculation method of your mind and increases the data processing speed of your brain. +1,000 INT, slightly increases your casting speed, Virtual Technology strength…

[Mechanical Race Battle Technique—Guerrilla] - Ability: One of the combat modes passed down in the Mechanical Race. It focuses on high mobility long range guerrilla combat. This includes 744 responses for different situations. When activated, the mechanical army will receive the following effects: +15% mobility, +8.8% ranged attack damage, -5% defense.

[Blueprint—Virtual Mutiny Virus (Incomplete)] - Ability: A product Manison created by imitating the Virtual Mutiny Virus, yet to be completed. It is not fully functional, far from perfection, and cannot be put to use.

[Virtual Technology Innovation—Manison] - Talent: You have made improvements to your Virtual Technology and found a new direction. +1.75% Virtual Technology related abilities, grants special effects when an innovation is discovered in the Virtual Technology area.

"Yoho, another Unique Talent!" Han Xiao was overjoyed.

He had seen this Unique Talent on the interface the first time he met the Mechanic Emperor. The bonuses of [Virtual Technology Innovation—Manison] were quite amazing. Plus, it seemed to be a crucial foundation to mastering the Indestructible Mechanical Troops technology. Manison used this ability when modifying the artificial intelligence lives.

If he got this ability, he might really make some breakthrough in studying the Indestructible Mechanical Troops technology.

He looked at the other four abilities—none of them were as impressive. After all, no way he could get as lucky as the last time every time.

Maybe it was because there were too many people here today who were blessed by the Goddess of Luck and she could not satisfy them all at once.

However, since there was another Unique Talent, he could not consider himself unlucky.

He already had [Apostle Life Creation]. [Multidimensional Mind Model] was a mediocre talent. 1,000 points of INT was powerful at lower levels, but it was ordinary at his current level. [Mechanical Race Battle Technique—Guerrilla] was a strategy-type ability for the mechanical army, like giving the mechanical army a formation response for different situations. This type of ability usually did not give a lot of bonuses; [Blueprint—Virtual Mutiny Virus (Incomplete)] was even more useless. This was nothing but a mimicry Manison had yet to fully complete, while he had the original Domino Virus technology.

Since the other four options were nothing extraordinary, Han Xiao chose the fifth option without hesitation.

You have received the talent [Virtual Technology Innovation—Manison]!

Another Unique Talent… I might really become the second Manison if this carries on.

Han Xiao tutted.

He then felt his new ability for a while before turning off the interface and glancing outside the window.

At this point, his troops were still cleaning up the battlefield, seizing Manison's mechanical soldiers batch by batch. This was a huge fortune if changed into Enas.

At this time, he felt a message on the quantum network. Risda was contacting him.

As he entered the Virtual Domain, he saw that Risda had come to him with a large group of artificial intelligence lives.

"Black Star, I've spoken with my people and clarified the situation. They're all willing to trust you. In order to not get captured by the Mechanic Emperor, everyone is willing to follow you for the time being, hoping that you can take care of them," Risda said with joy.

"Your people have made a wise decision." Han Xiao looked satisfied.

An artificial intelligence life who seemed like the leader stepped out and said, "Lord Black Star, we all hope to return to what we originally were as soon as possible. We don't want to be restrained anymore. Therefore, everyone has decided to fully cooperate with you and help you to derive the modification technology the Mechanic Emperor has used on us, only hoping we can be of use to you."

"Very good!" Han Xiao laughed.

The cooperation of these artificial intelligence lives was necessary to derive the technology of Indestructible Mechanical Troops. Since they were willing to cooperate, it was great news.

"Also, we're willing to tell you everything we know about the Mechanic Emperor. Whatever you want to know, we will tell you to our best knowledge."

"That'll be very helpful." Han Xiao nodded.

After being used by Manison for so many years, the Indestructible Mechanical Troops definitely knew some valuable secrets, which would be of great assistance to him.

These artificial intelligence lives were so cooperative probably because they knew he was the only one they could rely on now, and they needed his power to save the rest of their people. Many artificial intelligence lives were still in Manison's hands, especially the forefather of the AI civilization, Finette.

Beep beep…

At this time, a notification popped up on the interface. It was a new round of the [Reboot] mission, also the last round.

Han Xiao glanced through, and his eyes sparkled.

"The requirement of the last round is to completely free the AI civilization… Whew, the rewards are quite generous!"

The reward of the last round was a Milestone Talent called [Ally of Artificial Intelligence Lives], and the effects of it were the enhanced version of [Affable AI].

Han Xiao also saw the hidden reward—if he could save the entire AI civilization, they would become his powerful allies in the virtual territory.

Also, completing the [Reboot] series mission was also an amazing opportunity to make Manison weaker.

However, Manison would definitely have learned a lesson this time. Before Manison figured out how he did what he did in their battle, there was no way Manison would use these two trump cards in front of him again.

In order to save the other artificial intelligence lives, the only way was to charge into Mechanic Emperor's nest and destroy the terminal of the Indestructible Mechanical Troops technology.

All kinds of thoughts flashed past. Han Xiao smiled and said, "Settle your people. When we return to my territory, I'll arrange to give you guys a planet to live on."

"Thank you, Black Star." Risda nodded solemnly.

Exiting the quantum network vision, Han Xiao let out a deep breath. He was filled with joy.

At this time, Ames came before him and softly asked, "What are you planning to do next?"

"I've got what I came for. The twins are dead too, so next, of course, we need to deal with the one who's behind this."

"When do we act?" Ames could not wait. "You promised to bring me this time."

"Hmm, no hurry, let me think about it." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

Since he knew that the Modo Civilization was the mastermind behind this, there was no way he was going to let this go easily.

It was time to teach the Modo Civilization a painful lesson!

Chapter 1171: This Cannot Be Called a Betrayal

Without the information lockdown, two days later, the video footage of the battle over Planet Earth Ring exploded on the internet extremely quickly, shocking and attracting the attention of the galactic residents.

The Black Star Army's search notice was quite famous lately, the entire galactic society thought Black Star was just looking for someone. Quite a number of them even took part in it. However, they never expected something so shocking to happen while they were not paying close attention.

Was Black Star not looking for someone? Why did he suddenly fight the Mechanic Emperor‽

Most importantly, he even won!

Due to the Mechanic Emperor's stand being exposed in the Intelligent Plague incident, his reputation had plummeted. However, his strength position was hardly shaken at all. Although the three Universal Civilizations had been promoting the tie, since there was not enough firm evidence, the promotion was not very effective.

However, with Black Star's strength, at least people would not laugh at it, although they knew it was probably not completely through. Everyone only supported it because Black Star had made a tremendous contribution to the universe, so no one would step out to object it.

This time, however, the video footage recorded the entire process without anything missing. Black Star basically emerged victorious in a duel, proving the authenticity of his achievement and shocking everyone.

The powerful image that the Mechanic Emperor had built in countless galactic residents started to fade, while Black Star's image became taller, gradually snatching away the Mechanic Emperor's reputation.

In the many decades in the past, the Mechanic Emperor had given the impression that he never seemed to incur a loss anywhere at all. However, in less than a year, the Mechanic Emperor lost twice, both against Black Star!

Black Star had risen out of nowhere. In a few short decades, he had achieved legendary things one after another, becoming the publicly recognized most eye-catching Beyond Grade A of the century. The influence of this achievement was even greater than the one before. Through this incident, the majority of the galactic society could feel that times were changing. It seemed like a new round of the new taking over the old was taking place right in front of their eyes.

Of course, being shocked was one thing. Most galactic residents were more confused as to the cause of this incident. They were curious why Black Star had fought the Mechanic Emperor.

The whole galactic society knew that these two were the president and the vice president of the Beyond Grade A Association, and the purpose the association claimed to have was to defuse physical conflict between Beyond Grade As. However, now the president and the vice president had taken the lead to break that rule. In the eyes of some, they wondered if this meant that the development union was just a facade and that these individuals with great power would never settle down.

Quite a number of the galactic residents had stereotypes about Beyond Grade As that were embedded deep in their bones—they both respected and feared them, yearned to be like them but also hated them. However, Black Star was one of the extremely few exceptions.

About this incident, one version of the conspiracy theories was the most widely spread, claiming that the Mechanic Emperor was definitely plotting something evil in secret, and Black Star stopped him once again. After what happened with the Intelligent Plague, the Mechanic Emperor's good reputation had gone completely bad. As soon as he did anything that was a little over the line, the public would subconsciously assume that he was planning some conspiracy that would hurt the entire universe again.

This kind of image did not come out of nowhere. The recordings clearly showed that the reason the Mechanic Emperor locked down the planet was to search a fugitive. It was tough not to associate the identity of the fugitive with Aesop, for whom Black Star Army had been searching.

This way, many people suddenly 'figured it out' and felt that everything connected.

The Mechanic Emperor discovered that Aesop had gone missing, so he wanted to secretly kidnap Aesop to threaten the Dragon Emperor and Black Star!

This guy is such an *sshole. This was clearly an internal affair of the Black Star Army, yet he wanted to kidnap their family, despicable!

This conspiracy theory seemed very logical. More and more people started to agree with it. On the network, it seemed like the Mechanic Emperor became a notorious public enemy overnight.

Of course, for a rumor to spread this fast, there were undoubtedly people behind it, from more than one party in this case too. Those organizations who had beef with the Mechanic Emperor or did not like the Mechanic Emperor were all secretly helping to spread the news. Judging from the Mechanic Emperor's reputation in the industry, it was not difficult to guess who these people were.

A few days after the rumor had fermented, the Black Star Army finally publicized a short announcement, which pushed the incident to a new height.

The Black Star Army claimed that they had already found Aesop and discovered that Aesop did not go missing on his own will but was kidnapped. They had already found that the Mechanic Emperor was one of the culprits who assisted in the kidnapping, and the mastermind behind this was the Modo Civilization. The army stated that the possibility of further action was not ruled out.

Of course, the wording of the official announcement was subtle, but the galactic society could all clearly see what Black Star was saying between the lines.

You piece of sh*t, playing dirty behind my back? Just you wait!

"It's confirmed. The Soul Swapper has fallen into Black Star's hands…"

Inside the secure conference room of the Modo Civilization, the atmosphere was so tense that everyone present found it difficult breathing.

They knew that the real reason Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor fought was the Soul Swapper, and the Mechanic Emperor had confirmed personally that Black Star had obtained the Soul Swapper.

Initially, Modo did not know Manison's goal was the Soul Swapper. They thought that they had kept the secret well, so finding out now was too late.

Even though the Mechanic Emperor's motive was not pure, the one who got the Soul Swapper in the end was Black Star, so there was no point holding the Mechanic Emperor responsible for anything. The partnership they had might even end because of it.

Comparatively, Modo would have preferred for the Mechanic Emperor to get the Soul Swapper, but it landed in the hands of Black Star. To them, this was the worst possible result.

"The Soul Swapper is way too perfect for sending spies. If Black Star infiltrates the upper echelons of the expedition army, that place will become a black hole that will devour all the manpower and resources we send," the army upper echelon said with a grave expression.

"He'll do that for sure. The Black Star Army's announcement is his declaration of war. We will be receiving even stronger attacks. Black Star might even participate personally."

"All we can do is think of ways to eliminate the Soul Swap Twins so that Black Star can't use the Soul Swapper," one of the Modo Three Kings said with a deep voice.

Since there was no source of information, they did not know that the Soul Swap Twins were already dead. The Modo upper echelons' speculation was that Black Star would also be using the Soul Swapper through the Soul Swap Twins, so the plan of eliminating the Soul Swap Twins was brought up once again.

Hearing this, the others nodded and expressed their approval. They felt that this was one of the very few plans that could be carried out right now.

Of course, if the plan failed, they had to suffer the consequences. The Modo Civilization knew the risks involved. They could only blame themselves for not being lucky enough to win the bet. The most important topic to discuss at the moment was how to deal with Black Star's counterattack. Black Star gave them way too much pressure, and everyone was worried sick.

If they had known these chain reactions would happen, they would not have tricked the Kunde Race into attacking the Crimson Dynasty. They had lost much more than they gained, and the upper echelons present were filled with regret.

Their Super Star Cluster allies were completely unreliable. They were reluctant to deal with this mess Modo had made and wanted Modo to deal with Black Star alone. They did not want them to cause any more problems that would affect their overall strategy. However, this was clearly impossible. No one would be willing to give without returns. Modo would not just rot in this horrible situation. They would certainly come up with plans for themselves.

Due to the difference in stands, what the Modo Civilization did was completely dreadful to the other Super Star Cluster civilizations. Not only did they not hold Black Star back, but they might have even caused him to take part personally. Therefore, the unhappiness of the Super Star Cluster allies was imaginable.

An upper echelon hesitated before cautiously saying, "There's no point in discussing this anymore. Judging from our current situation, if things go even worse, maybe we will have no choice but to exit the Flickering World competition…"

"No way!" The Modo Three Kings' voices were firm. "As long as there is even a tiny chance, we will give everything we've got and never exit the Flickering World competition!"

As soon as he said that, the rest hastily agreed to express their political correctness.

However, in their hearts, not every upper echelon really agreed with it. Of course, fighting for the civilization's future was important, and none of them minded working hard for it. However, if the price of that was that their initial position would be affected, indirectly damaging the power and position in the universe of these people, the attitude of many upper echelons would become rather ambiguous.

The members in the leading level had changed time after time since the exploration era. Although the spirit of fighting till the end was still somewhat there, their philosophy still leaned more toward being conservative. This was unavoidable.

Compared to those upper echelons who grew in blood and fire, not all the upper echelons now had such an admirable sense of responsibility. No system could restrain selfishness… What happened to the civilization later was just a matter for the future; people who lived in the moment cared more about the present or the power and position they could enjoy while they were alive.

To some people, if there was nothing that could be done, maintaining the current state of the Super Star Cluster civilization was not a bad choice. After all, those who were willing to take one path and walk to the end of it were not the majority.

In a certain temporary base of the Machinery Faith in the Ancient Star Desert, Zax changed into his best formal clothing, looked into the mirror, folded his mechanical-oil stained sleeves, and staffed a few hard paper plates into his collar to straighten them. After a whole five minutes, he finally pushed the door open and walked in the direction of the Holy Mountain Temple at the heart of the city. On the way, he saw batches of well-dressed Machinery Faith believers who were walking in the same direction, smiling and nodding at each other.

The Machinery Faith continuously migrated around the universe. Every Grand Priest would manage one migration team. Every once in a while, the Grand Priests would host a festival at the same time. All the believers from various places would wear their best clothes to attend. This was one of the cultural practices of the Machinery Faith.

Zax was an ordinary believer. His position was a heavy mining armor operator. He originally worshipped Manison, but after the Intelligent Plague incident, he had changed and started to worship Black Star.

Because of that, he received quite a lot of rejections from his neighbors, as believers worshipping the same person would choose to live in the same area most of the time.

Although the Machinery Faith supported complete freedom in beliefs, ordinary believers who were completely unaffected were still the minority. Therefore, Zax, who publicly changed his belief, was the most conspicuous where he lived. Although the neighbors would not do anything, they would definitely not be friendly to him.

This was especially clear when it came to his good friend Modir, who was a loyal believer of the Mechanic Emperor. After Zax changed to worship Black Star, Modir came to persuade him many times, which always ended in intense debates. The topic of the debate was the authenticity of that tied battle, which Zax felt was reliable while Modir insisted it was fake and just a method to make the Mechanic Emperor look bad.

They could not convince each other, and gradually, they stopped seeing each other. It had been many days since they spoke.

While pondering, Zax followed the crowd to the temple square while maintaining a faithful mindset. He took the festival items from the priest and then walked to the Black Star Temple. Every Mechanical Deity had their own sub-temple.

While on the way, Zax noticed the difference. In the past, there were hardly any Black Star believers. Although the numbers did increase after the Intelligent Plague incident, there were still very few, at most one-tenth of the number of believers the Mechanic Emperor had. The other sub-temples were always quiet, far from the festivity of the Mechanic Emperor Temple.

This time, however, he was pleasantly surprised to realize that there were many times more believers who were heading toward the Black Star Temple.

"More and more people are agreeing with me. I knew my choice was right. Black Star is more worth worshipping than the Mechanic Emperor."

He walked into the Black Star Temple filled with happiness. The inside was extremely boisterous. Many times more believers gathered compared to before, so much so that people might mistake this for the Mechanic Emperor Temple.

Very soon, Zax completed a full set of festival procedures. As he was just about to step aside for the person behind him, he suddenly caught a glance of someone familiar.

"Hmm? Modir? Why are you here?"

Hearing someone call him, Modir turned around. When he realized that it was Zax, his expression turned unnatural. He quickly covered his face with his hand and walked away.

Seeing this, Zax instantly caught up to him, grabbed his arm, and refused to let him get away.

"What a coincidence, I didn't expect to see you here." Zax's expression was filled with mockery.

"Hehe, it's coincidental indeed. I wanted to go to the Mechanic Emperor Temple initially, but silly me, I got lost." Modir's smile was stiff.

"The Mechanic Emperor Temple is in the opposite direction. How did you get lost? Did you just follow the crowd, and because there are many people here, you went the wrong way?" Zax said mockingly.

"Yes, yes, that's right." Modir quickly agreed.

"Then… what's this!" Zax suddenly reached into Modir's pocket and took out a mechanical item. It was a statue of Black Star that was made to be placed inside homes for worshipping. He looked at the distressed Modir and chuckled. "Don't tell me you bought the wrong one. You'd have to be blind to do so. Tell me the truth, did you also betray the Mechanic Emperor and change to worship Black Star?"

"Nonsense! Betray what?" Modir's face was blushing fully as he tried his best to justify himself. "Can this really be considered a betrayal when it comes to believers?"

Zax chuckled with derision and did not speak.

Being stared at by an old friend, Modir quickly became less confident. He softly murmured, "Don't laugh, alright. I admit it. I've started to worship Black Star."

"Yo, now you admit. Why were you still quibbling earlier?"

"Misunderstanding… It's all a misunderstanding…" Modir's face was burning red.

The two of them had debated the topic dozens of times. He had insisted that Black Star was inferior to the Mechanic Emperor. However, the recordings of Black Star cutting the Mechanic Emperor's avatar into pieces a few days ago slapped his face so hard it was swollen. Hence, he secretly scolded the Mechanic Emperor and changed his belief. He was afraid of getting laughed at, so he hid the fact that he had changed his beliefs, which was why he was avoiding his old friend.

Seeing him like this, Zax shook his head with dissatisfaction. "You have clearly only just started worshipping Black Star. A complete newbie, you don't understand the essence of it at all."

"The essence?" Modir was very interested but was too embarrassed to ask further.

Zax placed his hands on his waist and said confidently, "Humph, look at you, getting awkward and embarrassed in the face of something so trivial. Shameful, what part of that looks like us Black Star believers? As believers of Black Star, you cannot have other things, but your skin must be thick!"

"That's a saying?" Modir's eyes opened wide.

"Of course! This is the attitude to life that Black Star has taught us. Often, you feel like you've embarrassed yourself, you feel awkward, but… who cares about how you feel? Don't be so narcissistic!"

"Huh?" Modir opened his mouth wide, wanting to say something but stopping himself.

"Shut up. Don't ask so many questions and let me tell you the doctrine." Zax stared at him.

"… But I haven't asked anything‽"

"Ahem, anyway, as believers, we have to learn the incredible parts of our idol. Black Star's thick skin is known throughout the universe. Look at me. I didn't even move house. I don't care what they say. If they dare come and debate with me, I'll take it as teaching them a lesson. Look at you, you're already worshipping Black Star, yet you're afraid of letting others know. Unqualified!"

"Sounds sensible… Is there anything else I should be aware of?" Modir humbly asked.

"Of course. Black Star told us that a qualified Mechanic should train his body every day and get a strong physique!" Zax folded his sleeves and showed his large biceps.

Doctrines and rules were all set by people. The believers would pick out the specialties of their idols and see them as the creed of their religion. As for the specialties of Black Star, they showed a new world to quite a number of believers and broke the old concepts.

It turned out that a real Mechanic should measure himself with the standard of a Pugilist.

As long as you have a strong physique, you can make up for your weakness, use yourself as a trap, and lure the enemy to get close!

Black Star had already proved through actual battles that this was a more advanced combat strategy!

The news of Manison being defeated by Black Star for the first time caused the Mechanic Emperor to lose a ton of believers. Many changed to worship Black Star instead. Suddenly, the popularity of bodybuilding swept through the Machinery Faith. Bodybuilding equipment was always sold out. The same thing was happening in many different residential areas of the Machinery Faith.

"Black Star is becoming stronger and stronger…"

In the Limitless Financial Group subdivision, Sorokin looked at the news with a grave expression.

Even with his harsh standards, the Mechanic Emperor was very powerful. Black Star had gotten quite a beating from Manison just a decade prior, yet now he could make Manison lose head-on, twice even.

As someone who might know who Sorokin really was, Black Star being this strong was not good news for him.

"With Black Star's current strength, if I want to eliminate him, I'll have to take back all the Soul Seeds and regain my full strength. But if I do that, this body won't be able to hold it and will basically be destroyed. I'll have to change my identity again…"

Sorokin walked back and forth, annoyed.

Among the many Beyond Grade As, some wanted fame, some wanted power, some wanted strength, some had no desire… while he just wanted to make money.

Throughout the years, in order to achieve all kinds of plans, Sorokin had changed his identity time after time. This time, however, he could not let go of the identity of the leader of the Limitless Financial Group. He had spent way too much effort to obtain this large sum of money.

Meanwhile, in the returning fleet of the Black Star Army, after Han Xiao had finished dealing with the chores and had the free time, he finally remembered about testing the Soul Swapper. Hence, he called Feidin over and temporarily took back the Soul Swapper.

His fingers caressed the mirror and tried to press in but could not at all. No matter how much strength he used, the Soul Swapper did not give in. It was the complete opposite of how it actively tried to suck Feidin in.

"Since only some are qualified to use you, let me see what on earth you are…"

Han Xiao activated [Bold Explorer].

Chapter 1172: Origin of the Soul Swapper

Images in his sights quickly changed. When Han Xiao regained focus, he was already hovering above an enormous planet.

Looking down from outer space, this planet was vast and emerald green in general. Bright cities spread across the surface of the planet. It looked like a rather prosperous civilization.

Through the satellite technology, Han Xiao could roughly judge that this civilization was still at the surface civilization stage with both technology and magic systems, attempting to develop toward becoming a galactic civilization.

The lights on the surface flickered quickly like it was fast forwarded. Countless days seemed to have passed in seconds. At this time, the fast forwarding suddenly stopped and returned to normal as if a certain destination was reached.

The next moment, a sudden change occurred on the planet below him. He saw that in a city area on the surface, the ground suddenly started trembling violently. Then, an enormous seven-fingered palm appeared from the ground.

An enormous titan-like giant used its wide back to break through the ground covering its head and stood up like a colossal pillar, bringing up large portions of the ground. It was like someone had grabbed a tablecloth at the middle; the buildings on the ground fell and shattered like the plates on a table.

Crawling out of the ground, the thousands-of-meters-tall body of this gray giant finally appeared. Just the aftershock of it breaking out of the ground destroyed more than half of this city.

He walked toward the mountains, causing chain earthquakes with every step. As if absorbed by some kind of power, countless stones crawled up his body from his feet, condensing and forming layers of black protective carapaces like armor.

Very soon, the combat jets of this civilization arrived at the scene and fired nonstop at this giant. Countless explosions erupted on its body, causing close to no damage at all. This giant casually swung his arm, creating massive shockwaves, crushing the fighter jets into pieces of waste metal that turned into fireworks.

At the same time, Han Xiao saw that similar situations occurred the same time at more than a dozen other locations. Lives walked out one after another from underground, all with different appearances. There were giants, gigantic beasts, and some that were difficult to describe. Some appeared deep in the mountains, some in the desert, and some in the sea. It was like they had all awakened simultaneously.

An Ancient God awakening-type disaster? Han Xiao thought.

This was a rare kind of disaster. The term 'Ancient God' was a general name for powerful individual beings. It did not have to be a life form. Even mechanical life forms were counted. Simply put, this type of disaster was when a certain powerful individual that had been sleeping in a planet for countless years suddenly awakened due to some reason, causing destruction to the civilization that had developed.

There were mainly two causes for this. One was that the 'Ancient Gods' landed on this planet many years ago and entered a sleeping state. They were aliens. Another was that the 'Ancient Gods' were the native lives of this planet. The latter would usually have some connections to the religions on the planet.

If Han Xiao was to plant Apostle Weapons the size of Giant King Kong on a planet and set for it to awaken millions of years later, should a civilization develop on this planet, it would also be considered an 'Ancient God awakening'.

The footage did not stop while Han Xiao was pondering. The time sped up once again for a while, showing that the civilization used all kinds of modern weapons but did not have any effects at all. Even mushroom clouds could not kill these Ancient Gods.

They seemed to have different supernatural powers. Other than fighting back, they would not attack the civilizations' troops deliberately. Instead, they would continuously use their powers to trigger changes to the planet's environment, causing disasters such as volcanic eruptions, tsunamis, plate drifts, magnetic field shifts, global temperature increase, and so on, seemingly attempting to build a planet that was suitable for themselves. However, such drastic environmental changes were fatal to this civilization. Hence, there was no chance of coexistence. They had no choice but to keep attacking these 'Ancient Gods', hoping to stop them.

During which, more 'Ancient Gods' awakened. They seemed to be the true ancient masters of this planet. The population of this civilization plummeted. They gave up one city after another, shifting toward the land with the fewest 'Ancient Gods'. They called it the 'Final Land'.

This time, however, an opportunity suddenly appeared.

As they knew 'Ancient Gods' were awakening from underground, this civilization went all out to dig into the ground, hoping to capture an individual that had yet to awaken. In the end, they actually really found one close to ten thousand meters below the Final Land. However, this individual had died. It was just that its body did not rot or shrink.

This civilization was overjoyed. They formed research teams hoping to find the weakness of 'Ancient Gods'. However, the more they studied and researched, the more hopeless they got. All evidence proved that with their current weapons, there was absolutely no chance of killing the Ancient Gods.

In Han Xiao's eyes, these Ancient Gods were at the Calamity Grade. They seemed to be of a rare race. Due to their extraordinary Racial Talent and enormous body, they were stronger than usual Calamity Grades, mainly tougher and tankier. It would not be difficult for a Calamity Grade to wipe out a surface civilization, and to this civilization, this many special Calamity Grade lives far exceeded what they could deal with.

In despair, someone had a flash of insight and made a suggestion—since their current weapons were ineffective, they could find a way to modify this Ancient God corpse and make it into a weapon to fight the other Ancient Gods.

Left with no other choice, hardly anyone in the civilization objected to this idea; they could only give it a try. However, their opinions split on the topic of controlling method. Ordinary remote control would not suit high-intensity battles. The tremendous load of nervous connection required at least thousands of pilots, which would undoubtedly reduce its mobility, and their artificial intelligence technology was not advanced enough.

In the end, this civilization decided to carry out multiple plans at the same time, one of which was to invent a device to swap souls, allowing their souls to exit their weak bodies and enter the corpse of this Ancient God to control it. This way, they would be able to use the abilities of this Ancient God to its fullest with a chance of obtaining its supernatural power.

"This is… Ultraman‽"

Han Xiao's mouth contorted slightly.

At this time, his sights suddenly zoomed in. He came to an enormous lab. The corpse of the Ancient God was hung up. Layers of scaffolding covered its body to modify it and plant all kinds of mechanical weapons.

On the ground were teams of soldiers wearing white clothes. A mechanical plug was planted in the backs of their heads. Cables extended from them and connected them to an enormous device hovering midair.

This enormous device hovered in front of the Ancient God corpse's head. Its launch port was a black crystal mirror that was pointed at between the brows of the corpse.

Ka-cha!

Han Xiao saw the lab personnel push the handle on the control table. The next moment, he heard people falling to the ground. All the white-clothed soldiers fell down to the floor. Dim clusters of light entered the device through the cables. Right after that, an eerie black light shot out from the crystal mirror and entered the Ancient God from between its brows.

Time passed minute by minute, but the Ancient God corpse did not show any response. Disappointment and frustration appeared on many researchers' faces.

Suddenly, the entire underground lab trembled. Cracks appeared on the walls. More than a dozen enormous tentacles shattered the walls, and between the rolling soil, a gigantic silhouette approached. It was one of the Ancient Gods that had a semi-plant body. It looked like a combination of Venus Flytrap and an octopus, swimming through the ground like it was a swimming pool.

However, at this instant, the Ancient God corpse suddenly opened its eyes.

Han Xiao's sights flashed and returned to the office on the spaceship. The illusion from [Bold Explorer] stopped abruptly.

He processed what he had seen.

"There's quite a lot of information…"

If he had seen correctly, that enormous device was the initial form of the Soul Swapper, and the crystal mirror was the Soul Swapper that was in his hands. God only knew what mutation it had undergone in the long years for it to become a Space Wonder.

Han Xiao recalled the appearance of the race of that civilization and searched in the database, but he did not find any matches. Even the Spacetime Research Council, which focused on collecting information on lost civilizations, had no records.

"Looks like this is a civilization and race that has yet to be discovered. It might be in the unexplored universe, or it could be an even more ancient lost civilization. Could it have existed in the same era as the civilization that created the Domino Virus? I wonder what happened to this civilization next."

Han Xiao was quite curious. Sadly, the cooldown for [Bold Explorer] was fourteen days.

According to the illusion shown, the plan to use the Soul Swapper to control the Ancient God corpse seemed to have worked. The souls of these soldiers should have merged into one. The corpse did not rot, but the soul had disappeared long ago, so there was not much resistance. The shell successfully accepted the new soul…

"Hmm‽"

At this instant, a flash of insight exploded in Han Xiao's mind like a lightning bolt.

After Hila's interrogation of the Soul Swap Twins and the tests Feidin had been carrying out, he had a brief understanding of the functions of the Soul Swapper. He knew that this thing could swap souls and ignore the body's rejection to a very large extent. This meant that if the target was a shell that had no soul, he could easily 'revive' it.

This meant that…

Han Xiao took out the Spacetime Amber, his eyes glowing.

He suddenly realized that the functions of these two things seemed to fit perfectly!

He could use the Soul Swapper in a very special way!

"Black Star, what are you laughing about? Why is your laughter so…" Feidin stopped and did not say the word 'perverted'.

"Ahem!" Han Xiao quickly coughed. "I've thought of something good."

"What?"

"It's nothing, none of your business." Han Xiao lifted the Soul Swapper in his hands. "I'll be taking this to do some experiments. I'll return it to you afterward."

"No problem." Feidin hesitated for a moment before saying, "Actually, there's one thing I'd like to ask you to help with. As you know, although Psychics can shift their souls, the risk is extremely high, which is why Chen Xing has been living in my body. Now that there's this Universal Treasure, there won't be any risks anymore, so I plan to get her out."

"For what? Doesn't mental reproduction feel great?"

"You say it as if you've tried." Feidin was speechless.

Han Xiao scratched his nose, shifted the topic, and said, "So, you want me to find a body for Chen Xing?"

"Not just that…" Feidin said a little bit awkwardly. "She said she doesn't want to use a second hand good someone else has already used, so she hopes to custom-make a body for which she can choose the shape and looks."

"I can't do that." Han Xiao waved and rejected the request. "I'm just an ordinary Mechanic. Building machinery isn't a problem, but creating humans isn't my thing. Do you think I'm a god?"

"Can't you use biological muscles, nanotechnology nerves, and so on to create a bionic human?"

"I can indeed, but that'll require a chip. The consciousness staffed in it is in Virtual Soul format. It's not compatible with the soul of a Psychic."

"What about imitating the structure of a brain without using a chip?"

"Sure, I can do that, but I can't say what side effects it'll have."

"What then?" Feidin felt a little defeated. "It's not like we can kill a young and pretty female just to find her a body."

"From the way I see it, you can find a pet first and transfer your wife into that temporarily. Isn't that nice…"

"She said you're becoming more and more perverted." Feidin narrowed his eyes. "And I agree."

"What are you guys thinking about?" Han Xiao rolled his eyes. You're one to talk.

Feidin shook his head and said seriously, "I've already split off the parasite soul inside Aesop's body. He's recovered."

"Oh ho, tell him to come and see me then. Let me see how he's doing."

"He's already outside the door."

Feidin signaled. The door was pushed open, and Aesop walked in. When he saw Han Xiao, he smiled bitterly.

Han Xiao sized Aesop up and said, "Old man, any side effects?"

"Nope, I feel normal now."

Aesop sat down. He had a complicated expression on his face as he sighed and said, "Black Star, thank you for this. If not for you, Ames would definitely have been heavily affected."

"Don't say that. You wouldn't have been targeted if it wasn't for me." Han Xiao shook his head.

"Alas, I've lived long enough. It doesn't matter if I die or not. I just don't want my death to affect Ames. I know her temper, she'd definitely do something she'll regret under a fit of rage."

Well, you got that right… Han Xiao thought.

"What are you planning to do now? Although you didn't plan for this, Ames will be more cautious now. Even if you want to leave, you won't be able to easily."

"What else can I do but stay?" Aesop smiled bitterly. Originally, he had come to an agreement with Black Star that he would be leaving to travel around after this mission was complete, but clearly, that was not going to happen.

If Black Star did not notify Ames, he would not have been in such a troubling situation. But Black Star had saved him, so he, of course, had no reason to blame him.

Han Xiao caressed his chin and suddenly said, "Actually, I have an idea that'll satisfy both sides."

"Oh?" Aesop's eyes gleamed as he said with anticipation, "Tell me about it."

"It's simple really. The Soul Swapper is in my hands now. I can swap your soul into someone strong, and then you'll be able to follow others around for adventures. Although you can't control the body, it's better than rotting at home. Plus, your safety will be guaranteed."

Aesop's eyes gleamed. He was tempted.

"This is a good idea… then what about my body?"

"Easy, I can use the Spacetime Amber to store it… but I suggest you temporarily lend it to someone else, and I happen to have a candidate for that.

"Who?" Han Xiao pointed at Feidin, chuckled, and said, "You enter Feidin's body, and Chen Xing will borrow your body. Isn't that a perfect plan?"

Hearing this, the both of them felt a chill down their spine.

Thinking of his adorable wife becoming an old man, Feidin wanted to vomit.

Thinking of the fact that Feidin had a habit of fornicating in the mind, Aesop subconsciously tightened his legs.

"I'd rather die!" the two of them said simultaneously.

…

It was the day for another plenary meeting at the Beyond Grade A Association headquarters. The remote projections of various Beyond Grade As arrived at the venue outside the conference room, gathered in groups, chattered, and waited for the meeting to begin.

"Have you heard? Black Star fought the Mechanic Emperor again not long ago. He even won this time," Sun Hunter said, floating in midair.

"We're not living in a cave. Of course we've heard." Kant tutted with his arm crossed. "Remember the fight we watched a few months ago? Black Star could only fight on par with the Mechanic Emperor at most back then. So little time has passed, and now he can already defeat Manison head-on, scary."

"Hehe, Manison lost big time. Feels good." A neutral Mechanic was laughing joyfully.

Kasuyi shook his head. "I know the Mechanic Emperor's strength very well. To think that he still lost after using so many trump cards. It's really unbelievable. I've seen the recording. Black Star seems to have learned some kind of new ability that happens to severely counter the Mechanic Emperor."

Sierron snorted. "He just got lucky."

"I personally object to your evaluation of his luck. You're questioning my expertise," Secret Master said with an expressionless face.

Sierron did not know how to respond to that.

"Speaking of which, I don't know if I'm wrong, but the last Beyond Grade A weapons that the Mechanic Emperor took out at the end, aren't they the three guys we know?" Milizaus asked hesitantly.

Once he said that, the entire place became silent for a moment. Everyone had a strange expression on their face.

To these senior Beyond Grade As, they knew who the Mechanic Emperor had defeated before, and some even knew them personally.

Seeing someone they were close to in the past getting modified by the Mechanic Emperor, they did not feel happy.

Although modifying living individuals was not forbidden, it was improper in the Beyond Grade A circle. Everyone had great powers. Once anyone was found to use something like this, all the Beyond Grade As would become cautious around that person due to fear of becoming their prey.

"I saw that Black Star captured two of them in the recordings. When he's here later, we can ask him." Kant shrugged.

At this time, another remote projection appeared not far away, and everyone looked over.

"Yo, speak of the devil."

Chapter 1173: Triple Provocation

As soon as Han Xiao's remote projection arrived, he could feel the surprise, respect, and all kinds of looks from everywhere.

"Black Star!"

Hearing someone calling him, Han Xiao turned and saw Kasuyi and the others approaching. They were all people he knew in the peak Beyond Grade A circle.

"What is it?"

"Hehe, good fight." Kant smiled.

"You should say that to Manison. He needs the comforting." Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Hahaha, you've become worse since the last time we met." The others laughed.

In the circle, Han Xiao was not distant like the Mechanic Emperor, so he was more popular. More people were willing to befriend him.

Kasuyi smiled and said, "Black Star, it's said you seized the Mechanic Emperor's troops. Those two Beyond Grade As, have you found out who they are?"

Han Xiao shook his head. He casually exposed Manison's trump cards and roughly explained the Felon technology. He then said, "Their brains got stirred up by Manison. They barely remember anything at all."

"Sigh, the two people you captured should be Sollett and Cain. I was quite close to Cain in the past, very long ago…" Milizaus sighed.

As a big baby who was talented, gifted, and of a rare species, he disliked experiments that involved living things the most. Before he became a Beyond Grade A, baby dragons had gone missing every once in a while, hunted by galactic hunters and sold for money. Most of the time, they were sold to research institutes to study their special traits. Hence, he was quite sensitive to this.

They introduced the backgrounds of Sollett and Cain. The former was Two, and the latter was Four. They were both once quite strong Beyond Grade As. They had beef with the Mechanic Emperor for different reasons and were both defeated before going missing. The people present did not expect to see their old friends become puppets when they met again.

"By the way, not long ago, you were still no match… ahem, or on par with the Mechanic Emperor at most. Why is it that this time the Mechanic Emperor used his trump cards but you still won? Do you have some kind of secret tricks?" Sun Hunter asked.

"Nothing much. I was just lucky."

Han Xiao subconsciously gave a humble reply. However, as soon as he said that, he realized the people around him all had strange looks on their faces.

Everyone gave Secret Master a look that said, "It's your showtime."

However, Secret Master was not affected at all as if he did not hear what Han Xiao said.

Sierron could not take it anymore. He walked to Secret Master and whispered, "Why aren't you rebutting him like you did earlier? Aren't you an expert?"

Secret Master glanced at him. "I'm giving him face."

"I see…" Sierron nodded and then suddenly it occurred to him. "Wait a minute, then why didn't you give me face just now?"

"That isn't necessary."

Veins popped up on Sierron's forehead.

We're all peak Beyond Grade As. How dare you so openly treat us differently!

"So, you're saying you're afraid of offending Black Star but not of offending me. Is that it‽"

"Yes." Secret Master looked confused. "Where did you get the confidence to ask this question?"

He was confused. Black Star could not be unluckier, so I can't reduce his luck anymore, but don't you know how extremely lucky you are?

Sierron pointed at Secret Master and was at a loss for words.

Can't you just comfort me even for the sake of it‽

The few of them chatted a while. Very soon, it was time for the meeting to start. The people swarmed in and sat down.

Manison's remote projection arrived right on time. He did not look at anyone after he arrived. He ignored everyone's strange looks and walked right into the venue.

He arrived right on time because he did not want to meet Han Xiao before that—he could guess with his feet just how boastful Han Xiao would be in front of him.

When passing by Han Xiao's seat, Manison purposely ignored him. He thought Han Xiao would insult him, but to his surprise, Black Star did not say anything at all as if he was someone else.

Already mentally prepared, Manison felt somewhat uncomfortable, so much so he almost spoke to Han Xiao first.

Noticing Manison's vision, Han Xiao did not even look at him… You thought I was going to insult you, but I'm going to deliberately ignore you, and that's an insult too.

Suppressing his impulse to talk to Han Xiao, Manison coughed and said, "Let's begin the plenary, everyone…"

Before he finished, Han Xiao stood up and slowly said, "I have something to tell all of you."

Everyone looked over.

Han Xiao leaned forward, pressed his hands on the table, and said, "About my experience some time ago, some of you here might not know the full story, so let me explain. I have personal beef with the Modo Civilization. The origin of that is the Kunde Race incident in the second exploration phase. Modo tricked a native civilization into attacking the Crimson Dynasty, causing unnecessary losses. My Black Star Army took part in the war, and I lost some men. After that, the Kunde Race joined my command for protection, so I took over the responsibility to find out the one who's behind this.

"Originally, this war could be completely avoided, but Modo's plots caused us to lose the chance of coexisting peacefully. One reason for the beef between Modo and I is the damages my forces suffered, and another is out of morals.

"Modo and I are enemies, so it's understandable for us to attack each other, and I accept the damages Modo has caused to my troops in the frontlines. However, Modo used conspiracies… never mind that they used conspiracies. After all, it's one way of attack in wars. But what they shouldn't have done is drag an unrelated Beyond Grade A into this. "

Then, Han Xiao pointed at Ames. Seeing that everyone was listening quietly, he said, "Dragon Emperor originally had nothing to do with this, but Modo wanted to threaten me through kidnapping her adoptive father. Someone here even assisted Modo in that…"

Then, Han Xiao glanced at Manison. He quickly continued before Manison said anything.

"This is very contemptible and despicable, so the Dragon Emperor decided to join the battle and teach Modo a lesson. I've also decided to take part personally…"

Han Xiao paused, looked around, and said with a deep voice, "I've finished speaking. Who approves? Who objects?"

The entire place was silent. People exchanged looks with strange expressions.

Before the Flickering War, the agreement everyone made in this very room was that Beyond Grade As had to stay out of the war. Their subordinates could join, nor could they take revenge except in some exceptions, but not participating in it personally was clearly stated. Black Star's request now, however, clearly showed that he was going to be the first one to break this rule.

Manison narrowed his eyes. He deliberately objected and said, "I don't think that's good. You're the vice president. If you take the lead on disobeying the agreement we made, won't the principles of the shared battlefront lose its restraint? If you make an excuse to personally participate and we approve it, will you have to approve it if tomorrow I find a reason to fight you too? If everyone can do whatever they want as long as there's a reason, what's the point of the association existing?"

"Tsk, older people are indeed inflexible." Han Xiao tutted. "How long has it been since our association was formed, and the system is already showing signs of rigidness? That sure suits your style as the leader."

Manison's brows twitched, but he was secretly relieved.

Familiar recipe, familiar taste. Black Star is still that Black Star, classic double faced.

Han Xiao then looked around and said, "I made this suggestion not just because of personal reasons but more for the principles and prestige of the association and the shared battlefront."

"What do you mean by that?" Kant continued the topic.

"What Manison said sure makes some senses, but in order to see this problem in detail, we first have to understand the nature of this incident. In order to cause problems for me, Modo plotted against an unrelated Beyond Grade A, who is also a member of the Beyond Grade A Association… What does that mean? Let me state an example. Hmm, let's take the Limitless Financial Group as the example. Let's say I want to take over the Limitless Financial Group's assets, and I know Manison is one of the big shareholders. I kidnap Manison, torture him in all ways possible, and use that to threaten Sorokin to sign unfair agreements. How will you react, Sorokin?"

Being suddenly named, Sorokin was a little stunned.

You guys can chat all you want. Why bring me in it?

If that really happened, I'd probably be overjoyed to have one fewer person to share my profits with…

"Ahem, I'd be furious."

Han Xiao then looked at Manison and said, "And if you escape… I mean if, since everyone knows if you end up in my hands, you'll undoubtedly have no way of escaping… anyhow, if you escape, you'll definitely take revenge afterward, right?"

"…Right." Manison's lips twitched slightly.

"See, this is completely understandable and very similar to what happened to me." Han Xiao clapped and said with a deep voice, "But why is the association going against it and forbidding this kind of action? Wasn't the purpose of founding the association to provide the Beyond Grade As a better future and higher positions? Why are we putting shackles on our own feet?"

Then, Han Xiao walked to behind Manison, pressed on his shoulders, and said, "The principle of the shared battlefront is, of course, when one member gets in trouble, everyone else helps. The Modo Civilization targeted an unrelated Beyond Grade A and broke the rules first. If we don't deal with it, what will the others think? They'll think that the association is preventing the Beyond Grade As from taking revenge, so they'll be more daring and target Beyond Grade As. What the hell is that‽

"We want higher positions. Other than following rules ourselves so that galactic society will feel safer, we must make others maintain respect and fear for the Beyond Grade As even more. The latter is the way to obtain higher positions, not the other way around.

"Therefore, although the purpose of the association is mainly to defuse conflicts, when facing this kind of provocative action, we must punish them! Otherwise, the prestige of the entire Beyond Grade A society will be damaged. This is the true purpose of the shared battlefront!

"We're now a collective, a group. If the others don't want to be affected out of nowhere like the Dragon Emperor, not only should they approve this, but they should even provide assistance and target Modo together. Don't forget how the Tragedy of the Pinnacles began. Having unity is crucial, the association should give Modo a serious announcement and retaliate with thunderous forces. This way, the entire universe will know that the Beyond Grade A society is now different. We're united."

Although something felt off, most could not deny it. Black Star said what they truly felt in their hearts; it really did make a lot of sense.

"Of course, our association has to have freedom. I won't force anyone to fight Modo, but I'll certainly help Ames because I've never forgotten where I started. Now, let me ask what I asked earlier one more time…"

Han Xiao looked around and said word by word,

"Who approves? Who objects?"

The venue was silent for two seconds. Then Beyoni raised his hand and broke the silence.

"I approve!"

"Me too." Kohler followed.

With someone taking the lead, the people of the Crimson Dynasty all voted to approve other than Heber, who was still putting on a cold front. Some of the neutral Beyond Grade As in the association who stood on Black Star's side also voted to approve.

Ames looked at this with eyes filled with joy—she loved seeing Han Xiao confidently talk in front of everyone.

The people on the side of the Mechanic Emperor looked at Manison. As Manison remained silent, they did not object. Seeing this, the directors such as Kasuyi also cast their votes.

"Black Star is right," Milizaus added. "His personal beef with the Modo Civilization isn't our concern, but even wars have rules. Methods that are too dirty can't be used without any restrictions. Modo's action of plotting against the family of another Beyond Grade A who's not a part of this matter has crossed the line."

"That's right. I totally agree with the true purpose of the shared battlefront as Black Star said. If I get captured by the Mechanic Emperor one day, you guys had better come and save me," Sun Hunter joked.

Manison glanced at him. "Don't worry, you're too weak. I'm not interested."

The people messed around for a while. At this time, a neutral Beyond Grade A who had been silent all this time suddenly said, "Black Star said he wants to attack Modo, but the Mechanic Emperor is an accomplice too. Why aren't you taking revenge against him? I think you should be fair."

Hearing this, the room went silent again. Many people had a strange expression on their face.

This is definitely deliberately starting a fire! Damn kid, you got balls!

Han Xiao glanced at him and thought it was quite funny.

Yo, I remember that this guy was one of the 'mercenaries' of the Super Star Cluster Alliance in my previous life. He might actually be a direct member of a Super Star Cluster civilization like Traveler.

Attempting to shift the hatred and mix things up here, could this guy be the secret direct member of Modo?

This thought flashed past. Seeing that everyone was looking at him, Han Xiao waved generously, purposely sighed, and said, "Well, after all, one of the purposes of our association is to resolve conflicts between Beyond Grade As. Although Manison was unethical, I can't be immoral. I'll take it as I made a small loss and won't chase after him for it."

As soon as he said that, Manison's entire body shook. His mental state that had finally calmed down almost exploded once again.

What the f*ck are you talking about‽

You took the Soul Swapper and my two Felons, and you call that making a loss‽

I'll make 'losses' like that any day!

Seeing Manison's twitching face, many people hastily rubbed their whiskers to cover their mouths and hold back their laughter.

Manison closed his eyes, took a few seconds to suppress his rage, and said with an expressionless face, "Black Star, even if you took my samples, you won't be able to grasp my technology."

He was this confident. Be it the Felon technology or the Indestructible Mechanical Troops technology, he had fused his own unique technology within both of them. This was the essence of what he had mastered after secretly making innovative breakthroughs in Virtual Technology.

Without making any innovation in the Virtual Technology area, he was completely certain that even if Black Star was able to learn something from it, he would at the very most only be able to imitate it but never completely master all of its details.

"Don't worry, I won't stop you from comforting yourself." Han Xiao giggled.

"Humph, nonsense. If I've guessed correctly, you've already met obstacles you can't break through at the start of the research, haven't you?"

Han Xiao hesitated for a moment and did not reply.

Seeing this, Manison smiled slightly. Thinking he had guessed right, he was finally in a better mood. He slowly said, "I guessed right, so you're not going to respond?"

Han Xiao shook his head and hesitantly said, "I just feel that you're old. You don't have many good years left, and I'm worried that if I tell you the truth, you'll have a heart attack right here. If that happens, the merit of getting rid of you won't be from me. Wouldn't that be a huge waste?"

"F*ck off…"

Chapter 1174: Arriving at the Frontlines

The day after the meeting, the Beyond Grade A Association made an announcement.

The announcement claimed that the Modo Civilization had conspired against Black Star through targeting the family of other Beyond Grade As, and this kind of action violated the association's rules. In order to protect its members' interests, the association strongly condemned Modo's actions and approved of Black Star's retaliation. Furthermore, the association did not deny the possibility of stepping in to protect its members.

As soon as the announcement was made, it attracted strong responses in the Flickering World. The various organizations in the frontlines of the Flickering World reacted to it the strongest. They were all shocked.

Ever since the start of the war, most of the Beyond Grade As had just been watching and observing it without interfering. Was this a sign of them personally participating in the war?

Although the association claimed to target only the Modo Civilization, the armed forces on the side of the three Universal Civilizations did not feel happy about it at all.

Everyone knew that Beyond Grade As were undoubtedly the ceiling of single unit war weapons. Once the Beyond Grade As participated, they would certainly become the main forces in the war. It seemed like once that happened, the others would not even have a chance to gain any merit at all.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance was the most furious—if not because the Modo Civilization was their ally, they would even have turned around to attack the Modo Civilization.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance only wanted Modo to hold off the Black Star Army's invasion and not do anything extra. However, due to different stands, Modo had to plan for themselves, which led to this situation.

Unlike in the past, the Beyond Grade As had founded a collective association, becoming a barely operational group with extraordinary influence. If not because the association was not on the side of the three Universal Civilizations, the Super Star Cluster Alliance would probably have no chance in this war.

Aesop being someone completely unrelated was not fully true. He had helped the Black Star Army find the secret transportation routes of the Modo Civilization time after time, but this part was deliberately not mentioned by the association. They only emphasized his relationship with the Dragon Emperor and the fact that Dragon Emperor did not take part in this matter.

From the perspective of sensible standards, the Modo Civilization did not cross the line. Aesop had clearly helped Black Star against them first. However, using this to argue with the association would only lead to them embarrassing themselves. At the root of it, Black Star's power was what caused this. In order to overcome someone with power, the only way was through using even higher power. Arguing based on what was reasonable and what was not reasonable would not work.

The current Super Star Cluster Alliance did not have the power to overcome the Beyond Grade A Association. Throughout the entire universe, the three Universal Civilizations were the only ones who could for the time being, but this matter was beneficial for them, so there was no way they would step up to interrupt it. Hence, they gave their silent approval.

The situation seemed to be heading in a direction that was beneficial for the three Universal Civilizations. However, other than being content, the three Universal Civilizations' upper echelons were also feeling somewhat complicated.

"Black Star… his power is growing even stronger."

On the Federation of Light's mother planet, President Bader let out a long exhale while looking at the report.

The direct Beyond Grade As had given him the details of the meeting. Although the main focus was Ames, based on this woman's personality, she would not seek help from outsiders. The attitude change of the association this time was single-handedly led by Black Star.

Right after the Black Star Army made an announcement, Black Star influenced the association to make a response too. Using his identity and position, he deployed his resources in a direction that benefitted himself. Most of the time, the materialization of one's power was presented in one's ability to influence and deploy others. If he could make many people act based on his will, he would be considered as powerful.

The advanced civilizations did this kind of thing often too. As long as the method was effective, no one cared if it was immoral or not.

Before the founding of the Beyond Grade A Association, if Black Star wanted to use his power, the only method would probably be to complain to the Crimson Dynasty.

Now, however, he aided the founding of the Beyond Grade A Association, created a new shield for himself, and gained a new source of power he could utilize. He had more resources and platforms at his disposal, so he was becoming more powerful in the galactic society.

Comparatively, although Manison was the president, which meant his position was higher than Han Xiao's on paper, Han Xiao had been gradually taking away his power. The three Universal Civilizations aiding Han Xiao was part of the reason, but the Mechanic Emperor was still the Federation of Light's ally on paper, so Bader was not very happy about it.

What troubled him the most was the sense of unity the association had shown this time. In Bader's eyes, these Beyond Grade As were not making an announcement to the entire universe; they wanted to tell the three Universal Civilizations that they were no longer scattered and divided. It was an indirect act of intimidation.

Although some Beyond Grade As still had their own goals and motives that might go against the association's overall goal, they also had common goals. If left alone, the three Universal Civilizations' control over the Beyond Grade As getting gradually weaker was a foreseeable future.

"Sigh…" Bader rubbed his temple.

As the leader of an advanced civilization, there were too many things he had to consider for just one matter. Even though there were specialized medical personnel taking care of his body to make sure he stayed energetic, the long time he had spent as the leader had cost him way too much energy and caused damage to his mind.

However, the day of the changing of leaders was close, and his term was about to end.

Not only the federation, he counted the days, and Urranrell would probably retire soon.

There was no choice but to leave these difficult problems for their successors.

…

Countless Black Star Army battleships gathered around a temporary space station in the Emerald Star Cluster. Almost eighty percent of all the fleets the Black Star Army sent to the frontlines were there. There were countless normal army warriors and players.

Usually, gathering so many forces would mean a huge military operation was about to be carried out. Today, however, was only to welcome a few people.

Inside one battleship, many players squeezed around the porthole and stared closely at the battleship stargate just built near the base.

"The announcement said Black Star will arrive today. Why isn't he here yet?'

"Is there a traffic jam in the stargate?"

The people chattered softly.

They were supposed to fight in the frontlines originally and continue to clash with the hostile guild alliance. However, not long ago, Phillip had given the majority of members a new order to pull back and wait for Black Star's arrival in the base.

The focus of the players was mainly the national war at this point. Although there were also discussions about the conflict between Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor, it did not receive as much attention as their own national war.

The reactions of the army players after finding out about it were all about the same. They basically yelled about how incredible their army commander was and then went back to fighting the players of the hostile alliance.

Some newly-joined foreign players were excited and surprised to hear that Black Star was about to participate in the war personally. They looked forward to fighting alongside Han Xiao.

However, the more experienced Chinese players were in overwhelming despair. Their thoughts were shockingly similar.

Don't come! We don't want to just watch cutscenes again!

Buzz!

At this time, a black cone-shaped tip of a ship extended out of the blue vortex of the stargate, followed by the black body of the ship that was covered in armor. An enormous flagship rode out from the stargate, along with teams of battleships, swarming out of the stargate.

Inside the command room in the frontmost bridge of the flagship, the scenery windows switched to being transparent. The players present could all clearly see Han Xiao and Ames standing behind the porthole of the flagship.

"They're here! They're here!"

"Black Star! Dragon Emperor!"

"Ah! I have seen those long legs with my own eyes. I have no more regrets in life!"

"Sigh, looking at him again now after seeing the main character Feidin in the Black Star documentary movie, I've realized this is the difference between imagination and reality."

"To think that b*stard Black Star can play with this pair of legs any way he wants. I'm heartbroken…"

"They're a perfect pair. Who are you to object it‽"

Quite a number of people had not seen Han Xiao in a very long time and were all very excited. However, in terms of popularity, Ames was overwhelmingly superior.

Inside the command room, Ames looked at the fleet outside and asked, "Are these people enough?"

"Including the two of us, yes, of course." Han Xiao nodded.

After making the announcement, the two of them headed to the frontlines right away to fulfil their promise, personally joining the battle against Modo.

At this time, a remote projection appeared beside the two of them. It was the current chief commander of the frontline fleets, Herlous.

"Your Excellencies, the troops have gathered accordingly. What should we do next?"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes, smirked, and said, "Give the Modo Civilization a present, of course."

Hearing this, Ames looked excited.

This was a plan they had already discussed on the way. Based on what they had found out from the captives, the plan to plot against Aesop was first proposed by the commanding level of the Modo expedition army. Hence, the two of them made a decision—once they arrived at the frontlines, they would charge in right away and kill them!

"But before we have a good time with Modo, we'll first have to chase away those in the way. Have all the organizations following behind the Black Star Army in the Ferdinand Battle Zone been identified?"

"Yes." Herlous nodded.

The Black Star Army's target had always been just the Modo Civilization. However, some subsidiary organizations of the three Universal Civilizations used the opportunity of the Black Star Army penetrating the line of defenses and followed behind to attack together, continuously taking over Modo's territory, wanting to use this place as the breakthrough point for the war.

"Okay. Contact all the commanders of these forces and drag them into the communication channel."

After that, Han Xiao closed his eyes and waited for a while. In less than ten minutes, the commanders of all those organizations entered the channel.

Contacting them was too easy. Hearing that Black Star was looking for them, none of them rejected the communication request.

Inside the channel, voices sounded one after another. Not long after, everyone had arrived.

Only then, Han Xiao opened his eyes and said, "Hi, I'm Black Star."

"Greetings, Your Excellency Black Star!"

"Hi, Lord Black Star."

"Have you eaten?"

The channel went silent for an instant, followed by the greetings of everyone. Their terrified expressions could be clearly imagined from their tone.

Han Xiao nodded, cut to the chase, and said, "Guys, do me a favor. Please retreat from the Ferdinand Battle Zone. Stop wasting time here."

Everyone was stunned, not knowing how to reply.

The channel became silent.

Some people were displeased, thinking that Black Star wanted to take all the benefits for himself by making them quit with just one sentence.

"Erm, Your Excellency Black Star, I'm not sure that's suitable. Plus, we can provide help. With us helping you to deal with the troops that have escaped, your troops will suffer less damage. Furthermore, us being around the exteriors of the battlefield prevents the possibility of the Black Star Army being surrounded by the Modo Civilization or other enemies," someone argued.

"Yes, yes. We all know you're eager to take revenge, but with our help, you can get rid of the Modo Civilization expedition even faster." Quite a number of people agreed and added their thoughts.

You don't say… That's exactly why I'm doing this. If you people defeat Modo too fast, they'll give up… I can only torture them as much as possible if they don't surrender.

"I don't want to repeat myself. I hope you guys can leave the Ferdinand Battle Zone within five days," Han Xiao said in a deeper voice and a slower tone. "I'm taking over this entire battlefront!"

Chapter 1175: Overwhelming Army

Han Xiao considered himself reasonable. With his explanation, these armed forces following behind the Black Star Army willingly exited the battle zone and changed their target.

A few days later, the Black Star Army was the only attacking force at the Modo Civilization line of defense in the Ferdinand Battle Zone.

Black Star did not hide his arrival at the frontline. The Modo expedition army had already received the news, and they were all on edge. Although the Black Star Army's allies had left, Black Star's arrival made the Modo expedition army even more on edge than before—Black Star alone was stronger than millions of soldiers.

After two days, the Modo expedition noticed the movements of the Black Star Army. The Black Star Army had temporarily pulled the troops at other locations back and gathered them at one area of the lines of defense, as if they were about to carry out an all-out attack. The one leading the charge was Black Star himself.

The Modo expedition army responded by moving tons of troops to this area to strengthen its defense.

A large fleet crossed the galaxy. After a while, the line of defense set up by the Modo expedition army entered their sights. It was like a wall made of battleships, armed fortresses, and enormous machines that extended beyond sight.

Five planets were moved there to form a defense formation.

Two enormous armies stood against each other in space.

Inside the command room of the flagship of the Black Star Army, Ames observed the battlefield, shook her head, and said, "They want to fight us head-on without any Beyond Grade As. Is Modo planning to sacrifice all of its fleets?"

"They don't have a choice. If they don't use this dumb method, they can only watch us charge right in." Han Xiao smiled.

Currently, the Beyond Grade As participating in the battle were only him and Ames. Although Modo also had Beyond Grade As, they did not want to expose who they were, and they could not find an excuse to participate with the association's restraint. In order for Modo to stop the charge of two Beyond Grade As, they could only use fleets to fight them head-on.

In battlefields like this, the existence of Beyond Grade As was crucial. The only thing the side without Beyond Grade As could do was use countless fleets to fight the Beyond Grade As. But even if that could hold the Beyond Grade As back for a while, the fleets could never threaten the Beyond Grade As' lives.

No matter how quickly they could build fleets, the speed of it would never match up with the speed the Beyond Grade As recovered their energy. After repeating the process a few times, the damage would be catastrophic. It was a bottomless pit. This was why the advanced civilizations all fought over Beyond Grade As.

In extremely intense battles, the importance of Beyond Grade As would be lower. However, those extremely destructive strategic weapons would not be used in every war. In the usual Flickering Wars, the Beyond Grade As were more than enough to decide the result of a battle.

At this time, the commander of the fleet, Herlous, said, "Army Commander, the troops have arrived at the destination. Please give the next order."

Han Xiao waved and said, "No need to have a stare down with them. Just start the fight."

The order was passed down layer by layer and quickly spread across the entire army.

The next moment, the Black Star Army struck. Billions of lights appeared in the dark universe, all from psionic cannons.

Extremely bright beams landed on the base protective shields and spaceship shields of the Modo Civilization like a thunderstorm, creating tons of electric sparks like ripples. The linked shield formed by the Modo expedition flickered, the shield energy storage of tons of spaceships in the formation fell below the warning line, and alarms rang everywhere.

The Modo expedition army instantly counterattacked. The charge fleets and assault fleets of both sides charged at each other and quickly clashed, instantly forming a bloody battlefield.

The two sides were absolute enemies; words were no longer necessary, and they attacked as soon as they met. The war erupted in an instant!

Ames turned around and glanced at Han Xiao. Seeing Han Xiao nod, she walked right out of the hatch, turned into a shooting star, and charged into the battlefield.

Enormous force fields formed into countless dragons, rolling, restraining, pulling, and tearing the enemy fleets apart. Hostile ships were torn into bent metal plates tons at a time by her force field, breaking their formation completely. Her Esper Ability was known to be comprehensive. She was incredible at large-area AOE attacks, and her ability was extremely practical in galactic battlefields like this.

Han Xiao was not doing nothing either. He snapped his fingers, and teams of mechanical troops swarmed out of the secondary dimensional army box and entered the battlefield.

The tons of mechanical soldiers instantly gained an overwhelming upper hand in the battleship. A team of just ten soldiers could easily tear a heavy battleship apart, and there were at least three million mechanical soldiers present that were still increasing in number.

The Mechanical Deity was excellent in duels, but when fighting more enemies, the mechanical army was still more efficient.

As a peak Beyond Grade A Mechanic who was also a combat expert, taking part in a battle of this level personally was a total piece of cake. Usually, Han Xiao might hold back, but against Modo, he had no intention of doing so.

The two sides fought fiercely. Modo was incurring tragic losses, and their troops fell legion by legion. Agent organizations were attempting to escape the battlefield frequently, but most were hunted by the mechanical army and blown to pieces.

On the battlefield, the members of the Galactic Business Alliance, Northern Battlefront, 5C Alliance, Plateaus Eagle, and other guilds that were on the side of the Super Star Cluster Alliance were doing everything to hide. Not a tiny bit of the confidence they once had could still be found; they just wanted to hide and minimize their losses.

"Luckily, we didn't bring all of our things here this time." The leader of the Northern Battlefront, Fire of Northern Sea, was scared.

"If I had known about this, I would've ignored the order and not come." The leader of the Plateaus Eagle's face was filled with heartache.

"It's not the time to be relieved. The Modo expedition army won't be able to guard this line of defense. We should think of how to save the forces we have. Though not large, it'll still hurt," the Galactic Business Alliance president said with resignation.

Due to the Black Star Army's attack, the national war between the players was mainly focused around the Ferdinand Battle Zone. The player alliances of the Super Star Civilization side were temporarily under the Modo Civilization's command.

When they heard that the Black Star Army was about to carry out what might be an all-out attack, these important Immortals allies also received orders from Modo to guard this line of defense.

These guild alliances were not stupid. They had heard of Black Star's arrival on the forums, so they played it safe and brought very few of their forces to take part in this battle.

As it turned out, this was a wise choice. The opposite side had two Beyond Grade As, while Modo had none. The odds of winning were less than one percent. If these guild alliances brought all of their forces, they would have lost everything.

Although the main participants of the national war were the players, fleets and equipment were just as important. The guild alliances of the Super Star Cluster Alliance had accumulated quite a lot of resources, but if they all got killed multiple times here, they would have no chance in the national war afterward. They would be thrashed by the Black Star Army players without a doubt.

Speaking of which, these guild alliances were quite speechless about this.

We were just having a proper national war, and now your Black Star Army suddenly sent its boss. That's bullying!

If Black Star likes to personally participate so much, how are we going to fight the army player?

This feels like two kids were fighting, and one side's parents suddenly stepped in. It's unfair!

No NPC organizations that these guild alliances met while fighting in the free competition zone were unafraid of the Cancer of the Universe. However, the guild alliances were very clear-headed. They knew that in the face of a super boss like Black Star, even they, the Cancer of the Universe, were the weaker side. They would be slaughtered no matter how many times they could revive.

With the assistance of two Beyond Grade As, the battle was one-sided. Very soon, a hole was cracked open in the line of defense, no reinforcements could make up for it. The Modo soldiers of this line of defense started to show signs of retreating.

Han Xiao observed the battlefield, looked at the gap opened in the line of defense, and said, "It's about time."

Then, he turned to Herlous.

"I'll leave one Lord's Avatar to be stationed on the fleet, as well as some mechanical troops. You'll lead the army. Don't charge too deep into Modo's base. Continue to attack the exterior line of defense. Focus on damaging their forces."

"Understood." Herlous nodded with a serious expression. The many years he had spent as a commander made him look quite respectable when his card addiction did not kick in. He said, "When you and Her Excellency Dragon Emperor kill your way into the headquarters of the Modo expedition, be careful."

"I'm not the one who should be careful."

Han Xiao smiled, flew out of the battlefield, dragged Ames along, and quickly penetrated the battlefield surrounded by the mechanical army.

The Modo expedition army lost bit by bit, unable to form an effective blockade. The battleships at the front were destroyed by the mechanical army in an instant. The two of them penetrated the line of defense and headed right into Modo's headquarters.

The duo's plan mainly involved the two of them; the rest of the forces would be staying in the exterior line of defense to restrain the rest of the Modo forces. This was because once they entered Modo's headquarters, the Modo expedition army would certainly set up an encirclement, and Beyond Grade As were smaller targets and more mobile.

"What? They're heading this way alone?"

Inside the Modo expedition army's headquarters, the chief commander's expression changed as he heard the report from the frontline.

He had thought Black Star would charge in with his army and take over their base, but Han Xiao and Ames coming in this deep alone was quite surprising.

"What is Black Star trying to do? Why did he leave his troops outside? From the way it looks, it doesn't seem like he wants to take over our territory," someone wondered.

"He's coming in to kill people, and we're the targets." Lagos knew the situation very well. He sighed and said, "The plan targeted at Aesop came from us first, and Black Star probably found that out somehow, so we've all become his target."

Hearing this, fear and panic appeared on the faces of the people present.

At the same time, they were strangely flattered. They had never thought they would become must-kill targets of a peak Beyond Grade A one day.

"Maybe we guessed wrong. What if Black Star has other goals?" someone said with disbelief.

"Stop lying to yourself! He's coming right for us!" Roddick roared.

"Then let's quickly move the command center away and take refuge somewhere else!" another said hastily.

"It's no use. Black Star is a Virtual Mechanic. We won't be able to fool him no matter where we go."

Roddick walked back and forth with a grave expression.

He did not regret Lagos proposing the plan against Aesop. He only regretted the fact that it did not work, and now the price of failing had arrived. This was karma.

"Let's ask for help from the upper echelons. Since Black Star is so confident, if we make Beyond Grade As fight alongside our expedition army, maybe we can surround and kill Black Star?" someone suggested cautiously.

Hearing this, Roddick and Lagos exchanged looks and saw a tint of sorrow in each other's eyes.

As the ones with the highest positions in the expedition, they knew very well what the Modo Civilization would decide in this kind of situation.

Black Star was already slaughtering his way into the headquarters. There was not enough time for anything. Plus, Modo would not want to expose their Beyond Grade As and take the risk of having them come here to save them. In other words, even if the Modo upper echelons knew about Black Star's goal, there was nothing they could do to help—they were forced to be abandoned.

Actually, the moment Black Star announced his participation in the war, Roddick knew this was it. He had asked for help from the Modo upper echelons many times, hoping that they could send Beyond Grade As there. However, the Modo upper echelons never gave him a response but instead kept asking them to hold on, while only providing the usual resources and ordinary fleets… How could that ever stop Black Star‽

That's the same as giving me 100 Enas and asking me to buy something that costs 100,000. How am I supposed to do it‽

Why are the upper echelons hesitating? Is it necessary to still hide the identity of the direct Beyond Grade A? If not now, when‽

Roddick roared in his heart. But no matter how he felt, he could not make the decisions for the upper echelons.

"There's only one option left—seek help from the Super Star Cluster Alliance," Lagos said with a deep voice.

Roddick nodded with a grave expression, took out the communicator, entered the communication channel of the Super Star Cluster Alliance expedition army upper echelons, and said, "I need help. Black Star has charged in…"

He explained what had happened. The channel remained silent for a while, then the commander of the expedition army of another Super Star Cluster civilization asked, "What do you want us to do?"

"We can't stop Black Star. I hope you guys can send reinforcements and help us to force Black Star to retreat. We also hope to temporarily move the command center to any one of your territories. This way, Black Star won't be able to come right for our heads…"

"Impossible!" another commander said furiously. "Modo brought this upon itself. Settle it on your own!"

"We agreed to help each other," Roddick said with an angry tone. "Are you guys going to violate our agreement just like this?"

"The agreement states we're going to stand together against the three Universal Civilizations' attacks, not pay all of your debts!" someone yelled with rage. "Honestly, I've already been putting up with Modo's actions for a very long time!"

The Super Star Cluster civilizations formed an alliance to fight for territory from the three Universal Civilizations and help each other. They had already let go of a huge portion of their selfish interests and would not continue to have internal conflicts at this time.

However, when the matter affected the overall strategy, the other Super Star Clusters would not put up with it. If there was no Beyond Grade A Association and Black Star had struck on behalf of the three Universal Civilizations, they would have provided assistance without hesitation.

However, the Beyond Grade As had already formed an association and made their stand outside the three Universal Civilizations, causing the three Universal Civilizations to lose their top tier combatants, which was their advantage over the Super Star Cluster Alliance. This was supposed to be an amazing thing, but Modo messed with Black Star themselves. If the others interfered too, who knew what attitude the Beyond Grade A Association would have? Would Black Star turn around to attack them too? They were barely holding on themselves in the war; no one wanted to be dragged down by Modo's bullsh*t.

Therefore, the other Super Star Cluster civilizations did not want to help Modo fight Black Star at all, or their overall strategy would be heavily affected. Instead of that, they would rather sacrifice their ally.

Roddick hung up the communicator with a heavy expression.

Everyone there had heard the conversation. The atmosphere was low.

"Looks like we can only rely on ourselves…" Lagos said that but was bitter inside. He knew there was no hope left, unless a miracle happened.

Thinking of his confidence when he got this position, compared to the hopeless situation he was in now, Lagos' heart was filled with complicated emotions.

If not because of the Modo Civilization's conspiracy against the Kunde Race, they would not have been forced to deal with this mess. Modo would not be in such a dire situation and would be just like the other Super Star Cluster civilizations.

Although Lagos did not like finding someone to blame, at this point, he still uncontrollably hated that guy who originally proposed conspiring against the Kunde Race.

What a complete moron he was!

Chapter 1176: This Is the Technology You Have Missed

As Han Xiao and Ames entered the Modo expeditionary army's territory, like adding water to a boiling pot, the stationed Modo troops instantly started moving, searching for the whereabouts of the two of them. Part of the fleets at the frontline were also called back to provide support.

If this was really a Super Star Cluster civilization's headquarters, any Beyond Grade A would find it difficult trying to break through it. However, this was the Flickering World, so the Modo expeditionary army's control over their territory was clearly not as strong as their home. The construction of many planets was not even complete yet.

Not just Modo, all the members of the Super Star Cluster Alliance only had limited control over their territory in the free competition zone. The military forces of expeditionary armies were not the strongest to begin with. Only a few years had passed since the start of the fourth exploration phase, and most of the time was spent on exploring, so there was not much time left for operations.

Therefore, due to many factors, Han Xiao and Ames could go practically anywhere they wanted in the Modo expeditionary army's territory. The Modo fleets could only chase after them.

An asteroid belt slowly floated in space. On one of the asteroids, two people were sitting with their legs crossed. It was Han Xiao and Ames.

"… Their location still hasn't changed. The leaders of the Modo expeditionary army are still in the command center. Tsk, if this was a less developed civilization, they might be fleeing right now, thinking they might get lucky and escape."

Streams of data flashed past Han Xiao's eyes. As he retracted the data needle he planted into the Modo expeditionary army's network, his eyes returned to their original black color.

Ames casually played with two pieces of highly condensed metal she scraped from the asteroid, raised her brows slightly, and said, "We've been here for more than half a month. Everyone in Modo knows we're here. Yet, they're not running but have been staying in the command center. Are they waiting for us to go there?"

"Maybe they know that there's no use in running and have accepted their fate. Only advanced civilizations can see things this clearly." Han Xiao shrugged and was not concerned at all.

While speaking, he opened the secondary dimensional army box, released batches of mechanical soldiers, and nodded slightly. These soldiers turned into streams of light and left in different directions.

Ames watched this from the side. She then sighed and said, "Black Star, we could directly head toward the Modo expeditionary army's command center, which will save a lot of time, but you had to take a detour. Otherwise, we would've completed our goal long ago."

Han Xiao sighed, looked like he was about to stand up, and said, "So, you don't like me spending more time with you. Alright then, we'll go there and get this done with…"

"Who said so? Sit down!" Ames changed the topic instantly. "You said you were going to plant plenty of secret sentries in the Modo expeditionary army's territory. The plan is already more than half done. How can we give it up now?"

Black Star was a busy man. The next time they went to the secondary dimensions would be at least a decade a later. But since he had squeezed out some time now to accompany her, of course she was not willing to let it end this early.

Han Xiao chuckled in his mind and sat down again.

Other than killing the leaders of the expeditionary army, he also had another goal—plant tons of wards in Modo's territory. Otherwise, he would not have taken a detour that delayed them by over two weeks after rushing into the enemy's territory.

He had already sent out god knew how many batches of mechanical troops during this time and hidden them inside the Modo expeditionary army's territory.

These mechanical troops could all be remotely controlled, of course. One reason for this was to deal more damage to Modo, another was to confuse Modo's fleets, and a third was to obtain intelligence and monitor Modo's movements, hoping to find out the final destination of the various transportation routes of the Modo Civilization. At the same time, he also planted some Thrones so that he could infiltrate anytime without anyone knowing in the future.

The Modo Civilization certainly knew he had left these mechanical soldiers. They would have no choice but to deploy large amounts of manpower to search for them.

Also, Han Xiao had another reason to take a detour.

"I purposely gave Modo so much time to prepare. I wonder if any Beyond Grade As rushed here to protect the command center…" Han Xiao scratched his chin.

Without the protection of any Beyond Grade As, killing the commander in a split second was easy, so Han Xiao wanted to lure the snake out of its nest. He deliberately took his time to give the Modo upper echelons more time to consider their options, as well as to pressure them. After all, the longer he spent so casually loitering around in their territory, the more face Modo would lose.

If the Modo upper echelons could not take it anymore and sent Beyond Grade As over as guards, he would have an opportunity to deal even more damage to Modo and really make them hurt. This was his biggest goal of this trip.

It looked like he was only targeting the commanders of the Modo expeditionary army, but he was actually fighting the Modo Civilization's upper echelons strategically.

While thinking, he opened the forums and took a look at it. Herlous was still attacking the exterior line of defenses of the Modo expeditionary army, but only attacking and not advancing. Even when they penetrated their defenses, they were not stepping over but instead returned to rest. They then continued to attack the next location.

If those armed forces following behind were still in the Ferdinand Battle Zone, they would definitely not have given up on this opportunity and would have advanced all the way in. This was the reason the Modo expeditionary army's exterior line of defense kept shrinking.

Now, however, Han Xiao had chased away all those armed forces, so Modo had time to fill up the gaps. However, they felt even worse.

The Black Star Army's actions were driving the commanders of the Modo expeditionary army at the various fronts crazy. They kept rubbing on the outside but refused to thrust in. It was torture. However, this was where their duty lay. They were not allowed to give up; they had to keep resisting despite it being meaningless.

Without Han Xiao at the frontlines, the guild alliances on the Super Star Cluster Alliance side felt confident again and continued to fight the national war against the army players. It was a battle, but both sides were enjoying it. One side was glad the enemy's boss had left, and the other side was glad they did not have to watch cutscenes from the side.

On a planet occupied by a certain Beyond Grade A elsewhere in the Flickering World, a tall being walked back and forth in the palace, holding a communicator. He looked rather anxious. It seemed like he was waiting for someone to call.

Beep beep!

The communicator rang. This tall being instantly picked up and hastily said, "How'd my request go? Did the people above approve it?"

On the secret channel, an emissary with a blurry face said with a serious tone, "No, the upper echelons won't allow you to help the Modo expeditionary army. Don't act on your own!"

"Black Star has been loitering around Modo's territory for almost a month. We've had so much time to prepare, yet we still haven't sent any Beyond Grade As over to help. It doesn't make sense! How will other organizations view us? How will our allies in the expeditionary army feel?" The tall being was furious.

If Han Xiao was there, he would have recognized that this was the kid who started the fire during the Beyond Grade A Association plenary. He was indeed a secret direct member of the Modo Civilization. However, although he was a direct member, he had his temper too and was quite daring. Otherwise, he would not have dared speak in front of two peak Beyond Grade As, Black Star and the Mechanic Emperor back then.

Almost all the organizations in the Flickering World were watching Black Star's movements. They all knew it had been almost a month since he entered the Modo expeditionary army's territory. If Modo did not take any actions in this kind of situation and let Black Star do whatever he wanted, the entire civilization would lose face. It was understandable for this Beyond Grade A to get angry.

"What's the point of going? Can you beat Black Star? You'll be going there to die! Even if all of our hidden Beyond Grade As go there, you guys still won't be a match for Black Star!" the emissary said angrily. "Stay rational. You can't expose yourself here! This is all for the future!"

The tall being was filled with frustration, but he had to admit that Black Star was terrifyingly strong. He would only be giving up his life by going.

If they sent Beyond Grade As over, Black Star would eat them up. If they did not send Beyond Grade As over, the reputation and image of the Modo Civilization would be damaged. Not only would they bring shame to themselves, they would also make people feel they were cold-blooded. The morale of the expeditionary army would undoubtedly plummet.

Black Star was able to achieve this just by deliberately walking slower.

This was an honest conspiracy!

Thinking of how Black Star spoke so confidently during the plenary, this Beyond Grade A felt both furious and horrified.

What did Modo ever do to deserve such a terrifying enemy!

Another half a month passed in the blink of an eye. Although Han Xiao and Ames took their time, they eventually arrived at the destination.

Countless Modo fleets surrounded the command center of the Modo expeditionary army. All the crews were on edge with grave expressions. Although they were the side with the numerical advantage, they were the side that was extremely nervous.

"These two *ssholes are finally here!"

Inside the command center, Roddick clenched his teeth. His eyes were extremely red ,and his hair was excessively messy. He looked severely exhausted, but his face was still filled with rage.

"They're finally here…" Lagos, who was on the side, was not in a better state too, but he looked relieved.

The two of them knew clearly that Black Star and the Dragon Emperor were coming for them. However, the two of them had taken way too long. At the start, the two of them were immensely nervous, and then they entered desperation, before gradually becoming restless. In the end, they were almost going mad from waiting. Black Star and the Dragon Emperor were like two blades slowly moving toward their neck. Days felt like years.

This feeling of waiting for a certain death was complete mental torture for the two of them.

Originally, Roddick and Lagos did not wish for them to come quickly. However, as time passed, their mindset went from 'please come slower' to 'why the f*ck are they still not here'. They almost wanted to rush Black Star and the Dragon Emperor to come quicker.

Plus, the Modo Civilization had never sent any Beyond Grade As in the past one and a half months, so Roddick and Lagos were more certain they had been abandoned. Filled with sorrow and hopelessness, they had accepted their fate. They would die one way or another, so they rather die sooner.

Roddick turned on the public channel and said with a ferocious tone, "Black Star! Aren't you here to kill us‽ Do it!"

Hearing the roar in the channel, the many Modo soldiers there felt somewhat betrayed.

They all knew that Modo did not send any help and had abandoned them. To say they did not feel betrayed would be a lie. However, as soldiers, they would still obey their orders even if they knew they were headed for death.

Han Xiao looked around, turned up his senses to the maximum, and laughed with a shake of his head.

"Yoho, Modo is quite patient. I've given them more than enough time, but they still haven't sent a single Beyond Grade A. Are they that afraid of me?"

Ames smiled and said, "Who isn't afraid of you in the entire universe?"

"Never mind, this proves that Modo has learned their lesson."

Han Xiao shook his head. Although he was unable to lure the snake out of its nest, he did not mind. After all, he would still be able to damage Modo's image.

He looked around. His eyes stopped at one location in the Modo expeditionary army's base. That was where the command center was located, and the targets he was going to kill were inside.

Han Xiao turned and asked, "So, are you going to personally slice the targets up, or should I do it?"

At the start, Ames wanted to kill Lagos and Roddick with her own hands. However, thinking of the experience she shared with Han Xiao in the past few days, she shook her head carelessly.

"Whether you or I do it doesn't make a difference."

"I'll do it then. It'll be more efficient. You're too slow."

As Ames rolled her eyes, Han Xiao coughed and ordered the mechanical soldiers behind him to advance.

He knew that the Modo Civilization would certainly set up tons of spacetime stabilization devices near its base, so he had summoned a mechanical army long before he arrived.

Seeing this, the Modo fleet instantly responded. The crews suppressed their complicated emotions and became firm, staring at the renowned Black Star far away, ready for the battle to begin.

Han Xiao glanced at them and snapped his fingers. These mechanical soldiers suddenly stood still. Dense white noise appeared, and space bent slightly around them.

The next moment, this batch of mechanical soldiers disappeared. When they reappeared, they had already moved a long distance forward but were still in a stationary state, like a painting.

Boom!

In the face of this strange scene, the Modo fleet did not hesitate and fired instantly, shattering these mechanical soldiers.

However, something shocking happened next. This batch of mechanical soldiers reappeared again. Not only were they completely undamaged, but their location had moved forward a long distance once again, closer to the command center.

This strange scene made the Modo fleet perplexed.

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes. "Using the Kunde Race's technology against you people is considered using it in the right place."

This scene that looked like a screen lagging was indeed the technology Han Xiao had obtained from the Kunde Race—the Spacetime Splicing Technology!

With his research and improvement over so many years, the Spacetime Splicing Technology he had now was far from its original version. It was way more enhanced and upgraded. This technology was now rather matured. It would no longer be easily countered by all kinds of spacetime devices like the original version. The difficulty and time required to break this technology using the same methods as before would be at least seven to eight times higher. This meant that it could stay operational for a longer period of time.

Although the Crimson Dynasty did not allow him to casually use this in front of others, Han Xiao had a flash of insight just now and intuitively felt that if he used the Kunde Race's trump card to fight Modo, it might be beneficial for the mission. He trusted his intuition quite a lot, so he did it.

In the face of this unknown technology, the Modo army panicked and used all kinds of attacks. However, no matter what attacks they used, they could not stop this army of mechanical soldiers blinking forward. Part of their fleet had no choice but to attack Han Xiao himself, but the attacks were all easily guarded by Han Xiao and Ames. Furthermore, their battleships were getting hacked frequently.

"Impossible!"

Roddick's eyes opened wide with shock. As he stared at the approaching mechanical troops, his eyes filled with deep desperation.

In order to fight Black Star, he had brought tons of fleets, thinking he would at least be able to put up a fight. However, to his absolute dismay, Black Star simply used one ability he had never seen before and easily penetrated the line of defenses of the fleet, threatening his life.

"What the hell is this technology‽" Lagos was stunned too.

Hearing the shocking tone of the two of them in the public channel, Han Xiao suddenly smiled and said with a mocking tone, "Fate really has a bad taste… To tell you the truth, this is the technology the Modo Civilization missed. You guys were so close to obtaining it in the past. It's a shame."

The Modo Civilization's stowaways were the first ones to discover the Kunde Race. If not because they wanted to trick them in order to plot against the Crimson Dynasty, they would not have missed the Spacetime Splicing Technology.

"The technology we missed?" Lagos murmured. His intuition told him that what Black Star said might be true.

He was filled with complicated emotions.

Finally, under the raging focus fire of the Modo fleets, the mechanical army appeared outside the porthole of the command center, completely unharmed.

Roddick and Lagos opened their eyes wide and stared at this mechanical army as the energy furnace on the mechanical soldiers' chests lit up, flickering with a burning bright white light.

The next moment, their consciousness went blank.

Boom!

An intense explosion occurred, and a pale blue psionic shockwave expanded.

The command center was annihilated; not even debris was left behind. A huge part of the entire base went missing.

Roddick and Lagos, as well as most of the leaders of the Modo expeditionary army, died in this explosion, leaving not a single trace behind.

"This is just taking a little bit of interest. Let's hope Modo doesn't get discouraged. We have more than enough time to have some fun."

Looking at the raging Modo fleets, Han Xiao chuckled and placed his hands around Ames' waist. The King extended and shrouded them.

Whoosh!

In a flash of light, before the Modo fleets surrounded them, the two of them disappeared without a trace. The spacetime stabilizers placed in this area could not stop them even a little bit.

Chapter 1177: Infiltration

Han Xiao felt the mechanical suit shake. When it opened again, he had already returned to the Black Star Army fleet that was attacking the Modo expeditionary army's exterior line of defense, appearing inside the command room of the flagship.

Hearing the sounds, the many officers who were originally staring at the battlefield all turned around. First, they looked at Han Xiao's face. They then uncontrollably moved down to his hand that was wrapped around Ames' waist and Ames' calm expression. The room suddenly became silent.

"What you looking at? Never seen this before?" Han Xiao glared at everyone and moved his hand away.

Herlous coughed and said, "Boss, is the goal complete?"

"The Modo Civilization didn't even send any Beyond Grade As, how could I not succeed?"

Herlous was about to ask why it took so long, but when he saw Ames' refreshed and energetic appearance, he hesitated for a second and smartly did not ask.

Han Xiao looked up at the battlefield outside the porthole. The battle was at its most bloody stage. The fleets of the two sides were fighting fiercely. The army had already broken through the exterior protective shield of two planets and deployed tons of army players who were fighting the players of the guild alliance. There were no signs of losing on either side in their battle.

Ames turned around, patted Han Xiao's chest, and said, "Alright, the root's been eliminated. I'll be going back to the Shattered Star Ring."

"Hmm? You're leaving so soon?" Han Xiao was surprised. "Didn't you say you wanted to fight the masterminds together?"

He thought that Ames wanted to stay and participate in the coming battles against Modo to vent her anger. He did not expect her to leave now.

"My anger is already vented by killing the initiators of the plan. Plus, you being here is enough." Ames smiled. She was in a very good mood.

Her original plan was to help Han Xiao while taking revenge, which she had already done to a very large extent. Without her, Manison would have lost one less Felon. Han Xiao had convinced her during this time, so Ames decided to listen to Han Xiao's suggestion and return to Floating Dragon.

Ding!

The moment she said that, Han Xiao's interface responded. The [Ames' Rage] mission became 'completed'.

That's it? Luckily, it didn't require me to turn over the entire Modo Civilization. Her anger has probably already passed, which is why she gave up such an excessive thought. Looks like my convincing has been quite effective, Han Xiao thought.

"I'll be taking Aesop back and strengthening the monitoring. I'll never let him escape so easily again." Ames brushed her hair behind her ear.

Han Xiao mourned for Aesop for a third of a second before nodding.

"Do whatever you want with him. You don't have to give me face."

Ames extended her long and white fingers, poked Han Xiao's chest with a smile, and said, "I'll go back now then. Come find me when you have the time. Anyway, I won't say thanks again. There's no need for us to be formal, and you don't like to hear it…"

"Alright, alright, quickly go then." Han Xiao waved carelessly.

"By the way, before I leave, I have a gift for you." Ames seemed to have suddenly recalled something. The runes on the back of her hand flickered, and a book appeared in her hands.

"What's this?' Han Xiao looked at it curiously.

"I concluded my energy training experience some time ago and created a new energy training technique. It should be inclusive for all. You should be able to use it too," Ames said with a smile.

Han Xiao accepted the book and read through it. It was surprisingly handwritten. The content was an energy training technique called 'Dragon Emperor Star Energy Extraction Technique'. The details were unknown, but it looked quite advanced, not inferior compared to 'Heber Stellar Furnace Cultivation' from way back.

"Why did you write it by hand? Isn't it more convenient to write an electrical copy and send it to me?"

"It helps you to train patience." Ames was still smiling.

Her thoughts were simple. It could only be a gift given by hand if it was hand-written. It could also be something that would remind Black Star of her.

Of course, Han Xiao was not going to reject this surprise. He nodded and said, "Okay, I'll use it when I have the time."

"I'll be going then."

Ames smiled and told Han Xiao to send her back in another King suit.

After she disappeared, Han Xiao opened the interface and looked at his rewards.

The Mission Rating was 'Excellent'. The 250 million base EXP reward increased to one billion; the Contribution Points of the Floating Dragon faction increased by a few dozen thousand; Ames' Favorability was at maximum to begin with, so it did not increase, but Aesop's Favorability increased by quite a bit. The Random Reward doubled from two to four, as did the Character Summon Card reward; he got two of them instead of one, both from Ames.

The first Character Summon Card's ability was called 'Force Field—Star Grab', which used the force field Esper Ability to grab the target. It was a decent controlling ability. The other Character Summon Card's ability was 'War Whip—Dragon Arc', also a force field ability. It had both AOE damage and controlling functions. It was quite a good ability too. Both had five uses.

To Han Xiao, this common mission was a cherry on top to begin with, so he did not have too high hopes for it. Nonetheless, these rewards were not bad. His focus had always been the Kunde Race's mission.

He opened [Kunde Race Leader's Last Wish] in the mission list and looked at it. The first requirement was still the same, as was the second mission requirement. As this was a Grade S mission, there was no progress bar. However, his intuition told him that this successful attack meant huge progress in this mission.

After doing some thinking, Han Xiao thought to himself, Judging from the current situation, the day when the Modo Civilization gives up competing in the Flickering World because of my torture should probably be the day the second requirement of this mission is fulfilled.

He had always wanted to obtain the three rewards for the second requirement. They were [The Enemy], [Proof of Leadership], and [Kunde Rage], all outstanding abilities, especially the semi-Molding Talent [Proof of Leadership] that had growth potential.

Thinking of this, Han Xiao summoned Phillip in the quantum network and said, "Send the recording of me using the Spacetime Splicing Technology to defeat the Modo expeditionary army to the garrison of the Kunde Race. Tell them to repeat it in all their residential areas, making sure every prawn… ahem, everyone in the Kunde Race sees."

"Roger, hum!"

Han Xiao's battle against the Modo expeditionary army was very short. Phillip recorded everything. He was never one to quietly finish what he had to do. Since he had helped Kunde get their revenge, he was certainly going to make use of the recording to enhance his reputation in the Kunde Race. He had to make sure their entire race knew about what he had done for them. This would help with the progress of the mission too.

After dealing with this, Han Xiao summoned Feidin, pulled him aside away from everyone else, and whispered, "Have you done what I asked you to do?"

Feidin nodded. "In the past one and a half months, I've already swapped the souls of fifteen thousand Modo soldiers and middle-level officers. They will be our spies in the Modo expeditionary army."

He received a secret order from Han Xiao. When the Black Star Army fleet was attacking Modo's line of defense, he had been using the Soul Swapper to swap some of the enemy soldiers, infiltrating the Modo expeditionary army and planting spies.

The Modo Civilization had once used the Soul Swapper against the army, so Han Xiao had Feidin give them a taste of their own medicine. Given how special the Soul Swapper was, even if Modo prepared for it, they could not avoid it.

"Well done." Han Xiao nodded with satisfaction. He had already planted multiple chess pieces in the Modo expeditionary army's territory. This way, he would have more sources of their internal intelligence. Not only would he be able to control the whereabouts of the Modo Civilization's army, but he could also try to find the location of the secret transport route. He could take his time torturing them.

"Give my order. Retreat temporarily. Let's go back to the base and rest for some time," Han Xiao said loudly. The officers present were all surprised.

We have the upper hand now. Why are we retreating all of a sudden? Even if we're not going to enter their line of defense, we should at least finish this battle.

What they did not know was that Han Xiao was not doing this to give the Black Star Army time to rest but instead give the enemy time to rest. He had just killed the commanders of the Modo expeditionary army. He knew that they now had no leaders and would definitely be disorganized.

He wanted to give Modo a little bit of hope so that he could crush that hope time after time in the future. This way, making Modo give up due to despair would be easier.

Though confused, none of the officers would question the army commander's order.

Very soon, the majority of the army's forces backed away out of the bloody battlefield and then retreated systematically.

Seeing this, the Modo garrison of this line of defense were all confused.

Aren't we getting beaten up? Why did they suddenly stop half-way?

"Weird. We have to report this to the command center immediately." The fleet commander of this line of defense hastily went to report to the upper echelons.

However, what he got was a long silence—no one picked up.

After quite some time, he finally received the nightmarish news published on the internal network. Only then was he appalled to find out what had happened—the entire command center had been annihilated by Black Star!

…

After adapting and modifying for about two decades, the new generations of the Kunde Race gradually got used to being in captivity, accepting the culture injected by the Crimson Dynasty and the Black Star Army. As the older prawns passed away naturally, the effects of the cultural modification operation on the entire race started to show.

All the residential planets were singled out and could not contact the other planets. They had regained basic productivity, the streets were crowded, and the heavy and depressing atmosphere had become much better. The young generation had given the Kunde Race the vitality it needed.

On this day, a huge event happened on this residential planet. Every screen on the planet was playing a video. The content of it was the recording of Han Xiao destroying the command center of the Modo expeditionary army. Phillip even kindly added some narration to explain what happened to help the Kunde Race understand what Han Xiao had done for them.

Every member of the Kunde Race who saw the recording realized that Black Star was still living up to his promise, continuously avenging their race. Furthermore, Black Star even used their technology.

Seeing the moment when the mechanical soldiers used the Spacetime Splicing Technology to destroy the command center, every member of the Kunde Race's face lit up with excitement. They were filled with pride.

Look, those who used us are no match for our strongest technology!

This made them feel that they were not just watching Black Star avenge them but were actually helping.

Along with pride was a strong sense of appreciation for Black Star.

Throughout the years, not only did he protect them, but he never forgot his promise to them and brought them the justice they deserved… This incredible and kind man was their one and only god of protection. They felt blessed amid all the unfortunate things they had experienced.

The same thing was happening on every planet of the Kunde Race. Countless members of the Kunde Race gained more and more admiration for Black Star.

Chapter 1178: Objectors

Inside a small private guest room, a few officers at the top level sat on the sofa and complained.

"Sigh, the commanders of the expeditionary army got killed, but Black Star stopped attacking. He clearly wants to devour our armies again and again. The Three Kings are not giving up on the Flickering World no matter what, but what's the point of sending in more forces? This is pure suicide if no Beyond Grade As are sent. Black Star has already proved that he has the ability to kill the commanders any time he wants."

The news of the expeditionary army's commanders being killed had reached Modo. The Modo Three Kings summoned the upper echelons and hosted a meeting. Other than showing their rage, they quickly promoted new commanders from the expeditionary army and ordered the military to send more aid.

At that time, the many officials did not display any objections on the surface, but many of them developed a stronger sense of objection inside. Hence, after the meeting ended, a few officials who were unhappy met privately.

In the room, Marco had the highest position. He was the third in command of a mainstream political faction in Modo, so his words carried the most weight. He slowly said, "We can't carry on like this. Modo has almost no chance in the Flickering World with Black Star standing in the way. Giving up as soon as possible is the rational choice. The longer this drags on, the more pressure Modo will face, collapsing in the end."

Someone sighed and said, "Exactly. Things are not stable inside the nation these days too… Many unofficial organizations of the three Universal Civilizations have started so-called 'peaceful movements' on various colonial planets. They're using armed demonstrations, organized strikes, and so on to trigger the anti-war emotions of the society, forcing us to exit the war. Many industries have been severely affected. Some with ulterior motives are even spreading ideas of splitting the race up, bashing the policies, and promoting hatred, which actually turned around the way of living peacefully with other races we have been teaching for all these years and successfully worsened racism. Rebellious armies will certainly appear one day. Plus, important people are being assassinated by mysterious forces everywhere."

Marco shook his head. "Modo has made tremendous investments in the Flickering World for decades. It's understandable that the Three Kings are not willing to give up easily. However, the situation has now changed. Adjusting our strategy is the top priority. Since we can't deal with Black Star, continuing to spend resources in the Flickering World will just be a meaningless waste. It's time to make the decision to minimize losses."

"That's right. The Three Kings are just thinking about holding on till the Super Star Cluster Alliance succeeds, and at that time, we can benefit from it too. But the chances of us being able to hold on till the day the Super Star Cluster Alliance gets the upper hand… are too thin. Black Star won't watch that happen too. He might be stalling with us now, but if we don't keep sending in troops to keep him full, he'll certainly launch an all-out attack and chase us out," another person said.

Marco took a sip of the dark ember colored wine and softly said, "Actually, since the beginning, I've never felt the Super Star Cluster Alliance will be able to invade the Flickering World successfully. There's an eighty percent chance they'll fail. This is just a desperate collective attempt by the other Super Star Cluster civilizations. Since that's the case, getting out earlier, being free from the pressure from the three Universal Civilizations and the Black Star Army, and beginning our recovery earlier is a wiser choice for Modo instead."

"That's right."

The others in the room agreed completely.

Marco narrowed his eyes. "The more losses Modo suffers, the more people will object. Maybe it's time for us to prepare for the impeachment operation…"

Hearing this, the others were shocked. They were just complaining; they did not expect Marco to have plans for actually taking action.

However, thinking about it, they felt this might not be a bad idea.

Modo was a government formed by three civilizations, and each of the Three Kings represented one race. However, political stands and philosophies crossed the boundaries of races, so the political environment of the Modo Civilization was very complicated.

Due to the unique political structure, Modo, of course, had to make sure it was balanced. The Three Kings could not do whatever they wanted; there were also structures similar to congress that restrained their power. If the path they chose during their term did not fit the interests of the majority or one of them was involved in a scandal, their term could be ended by impeachment.

However, this kind of situation rarely happened. As long as the Three Kings did not do things that were hated by almost everyone during their terms, they would peacefully retire.

"If the Three Kings insist on their choice, Modo will be gradually sucked dry. The future is dark. If they are really going to be stubborn, impeachment will be the only choice left," Marco said.

The people exchanged looks. Some were firm, and some were hesitant. They all lowered their voices and softly discussed how exactly they could execute the plan.

At this moment, the objectors of the war started to plan on how to backstab the Three Kings. The root of it was that Black Star's strength made some of the Modo upper echelons hopeless; they did not see how they could turn things around.

Inside the Modo Civilization's territory, a silver stealth-type high warp speed spaceship hovered in a cluster of nebulas, slowly moving. There was no symbol on its exterior armor.

Inside the cabin, Lothaire and a few other officers of the Assassin's Society sat around a virtual screen, browsing the information on it. Rows of portraits were displayed on the screen, all influential people from various industries of the Modo Civilization. Some already had a red cross above their head, meaning the assassination was complete.

"Internally, Modo is a mess. The leaders of some industries being assassinated caused the local management system of some colonial planets to almost collapse. Our work is very effective," an officer said coldly.

"Hmm."

Lothaire was staring at the screen, seemingly looking for their next prey.

The Assassin's Society had been doing work for many months in Modo. They had already caused quite a lot of chaos. While being chased, wanted, and hunted by the officials, they were still continuing their work and hiding at the same time.

"Our actions over the past few days have been too aggressive. We've lost some men too. It's time to lie low for a while," an officer suggested.

Lothaire nodded. He then shook his head and said, "We'll hide temporarily, then do a big one."

Then, he extended his finger and pointed at one of the portraits on the screen.

The officers present followed his finger. Their expressions all turned stiff as horror and disbelief appeared in their eyes.

The target Lothaire had chosen was one of the Modo Three Kings!

"You want to assassinate the highest leader of a Super Star Cluster civilization?" An officer opened his eyes wide. "Are you insane‽"

"They have three leaders. Losing one is nothing." Lothaire's tone was calm. "I'll do it myself."

"Do you know the nature of this action? If you succeed, the Modo Civilization will become our eternal enemy. Furthermore, there's absolutely no chance of succeeding. The Modo Three Kings are heavily guarded. There's no chance of getting close at all. Plus, there's no way of assassinating them if they don't leave their mother planet," someone said with a hasty tone.

For once in a blue moon, Lothaire actually explained himself. "Firstly, we're Modo's eternal enemies to begin with. Secondly, the Modo Three Kings have many guards, but no Beyond Grade A guards are present on the surface, Calamity Grades at most, which isn't beyond my abilities. Thirdly, the Modo mother planet doesn't have the Psionic Seal Ring like the three Universal Civilizations' mother planets have, so infiltration is totally possible."

At a glance, assassinating one of the Modo Three Kings was an impossible mission. However, after doing some analysis, he realized that it was not completely impossible. After all, although the Three Kings were leaders, they were not individuals with great strength. Furthermore, he had [Deity Assassinator] in his hands. Even if the Three Kings had magical defense runes, this weapon would be able to penetrate them. The main problem was, whether the assassination was successful or not, getting away afterward would be extremely difficult.

The others were in dismay like this was the first time they had met Lothaire. Even though they were all assassins who had killed many important people, this was still an extremely daring plan in their eyes.

"Easy to say, but executing it is complete suicide!"

"Everything is possible. Sometimes, all you need is a little bit of luck." Lothaire narrowed his eyes. The people there did not know what he was thinking, nor did he plan to explain further.

Due to Rossellin and the three Universal Civilizations' operations, the internal racial issues and racist philosophies were gradually becoming more severe. If he could assassinate one of the Three Kings at this time and find a way to blame it on the extremists of the other two races, it might further stimulate the conflict and make these philosophies explode. The results were not difficult to imagine.

Sure, the method was a little bit dirty, but as an assassin, Lothaire did not care if the method was ethical or not. He was only concerned if it was effective and could achieve his goal. It could be said that he would do anything necessary to achieve his goals.

He had been operating in the outside world for decades; he was no longer just a pure assassin. He had gradually learned to analyze the big picture. Although Black Star did not specifically instruct him on what to do, Lothaire was very clear of Black Star's goal. He was more than happy to use swifter methods to deal greater damage to Modo that was more powerful than just an assassination.

Of course, assassinating Modo's highest leader and pinning it on racism was just an idea. It was extremely difficult and impossible to complete with just the Assassin's Society.

However, the three Universal Civilizations' forces in Modo's territory were a natural help. Lothaire planned to create a fuse so that they could operate around it, just like how the philosophy tide they created gave him the idea of assassinating one of the Modo Three Kings.

Boom!

A red silhouette fell onto a desolate planet like a meteor, crashing a crater on the planet surface.

Blood flowed out from the tip of Hila's lips. Her body was embedded into the ground. As she pulled herself out, Han Xiao suddenly appeared right above him, and a powerful kick swept onto her abdomen.

Boom!

The little bit of death energy she had just gathered got scattered by one kick. A shockwave erupted with a loud explosion noise.

Having been heavily hit in the abdomen, Hila's body bent like a shrimp as she shot out like a rocket for dozens of miles, leaving a long fissure behind.

"Are we going to continue? I've already been beating you for eleven hours. If I remember correctly, you've already been close to death three times and fainted five times."

Han Xiao stood with his arms crossed and sighed.

"Humph, are you going to praise me for being energetic? Never mind, let's call it a day. But don't forget, this is just the third time." Hila wiped away the blood on her lips, rubbed her stomach, and stood up.

Hearing this, Han Xiao's eyelids twitched uncontrollably.

He was now fulfilling the agreement he made back then to spar with Hila thirty times. Now there were twenty-seven times left. As Han Xiao thought of this number, he could almost feel his waist hurting.

This was a certain location near Black Star Palace. He had returned from the free competition zone long ago.

Modo did not send any Beyond Grade As for what he did, so they most likely would not in the future either. Furthermore, Han Xiao had already left enough mechanical troops and Lord's Avatars there, so he did not continue to stay in the frontlines and directly returned to the headquarters using the King suit.

Han Xiao originally wanted to stay indoors and focus on studying the Felon and the Indestructible Mechanical Troops technology, but Hila was insatiable and had to spar with him.

Due to their agreement, he could not reject her and had no choice but to hit Hila every day for a few days. Although Hila was a tough sandbag, using her so often was excessive even for Han Xiao.

With the Exclusive Talent [Virtual Technology Innovation—Manison], the progress of studying the Felon and the Indestructible Mechanical Troops was going quite smoothly. However, there were still a number of key factors he had to overcome till completely mastering them, which required time. Hence, Han Xiao did not use Awakening Points to quicken the progress. He would be able to derive the blueprint with the bonuses from his abilities and talents.

This time, Hila flew over from afar and asked, "How do you think I'm progressing?"

"Not bad," Han Xiao said casually.

"Tsk, such a perfunctory response. You're so patient when accompanying Ames but so whatever to me. Do you not want to accompany me that much?" Hila raised her brows.

"What do you think?" Han Xiao gazed at her. You masochist, don't you understand that forcing me to beat you up every day is tiring for me too‽

Due to her passion for battle, Hila became stronger rather quickly, and with the Underworld, her growth potential was even higher.

When Aurora reached Beyond Grade A, the Underworld would be able to revive the Hero Spirits. Only then would Hila reach her peak strength.

Han Xiao had also found out from Onicelu that if Aurora's Vital Energy Esper Ability reached Beyond Grade A, its qualities would change. She would be able to create living bodies with no soul that could be used for the Hero Spirits to live in.

It just so happened that this ability could work with the Soul Swapper. Han Xiao had told Feidin this and promised him that he would ask Aurora to build a body for Chen Xing.

Hila snorted softly, changed the topic, and said, "There are twenty-seven more spars. I want one the day after tomorrow. Remember to make time."

"Aren't you too hard to satisfy? Can the interval be longer?" Han Xiao was speechless.

"No! I finally snatched you back from my teacher. I want you to accompany me as much as possible."

A tint of happiness flashed across Hila's eyes. She then went into the spaceship and headed back herself.

Han Xiao sighed and shook his head. He was more certain that Hila was a complete masochist.

The purpose of sparring is to test one's strength, but she clearly knows how big the difference in our strength is. Still, she keeps wanting to fight me. Isn't this simply asking to be beaten up‽

Sigh, Hadavy is much better. They're both looking to be beaten up, but this guy is much more understanding, still smiling after getting beat up, unlike Hila, who always has that cold expression like I owe her money…

Speaking of which, it's been some time since I've heard Hadavy's flattery. I actually miss it.

Han Xiao was in no hurry of going back. He made the mechanical army retrieve some of the shattered mechanical soldiers. While the battlefield was being cleaned up, he opened the forums. He was about to look at the players' jokes and relax.

However, as soon as he opened the Flickering World panel, his eyes were drawn to a pinned post.

World Server War Invitation Letter!

Chapter 1179: Impeachment

"The World Server War… what's bound to come will come in the end."

Han Xiao opened the post and browsed through. Seeing that the content was the same as he expected, he sighed.

The post was jointly announced by Galactic Business Alliance, September Conference, Northern Tropic of Cancer Light, Southeast Asia War Alliance, and multiple guild alliances. In simple terms, it was an ordeal challenge letter targeted at all player alliances. It stated a time and location, aiming to start an enormous battle.

The players of the various alliances usually moved according to their faction's orders, but this did not have much to do with factions. It was just an event between the players.

The same thing had happened in his previous life. The various guild alliances announced the war, and it turned into a battle between millions of players that lasted for many days. It was then recorded in the 'Galaxy Chronicles', given the name of 'Planet Tabor Battle'.

The Great Mechanic Han was also active for some time in this battle in his previous life, mainly to loot the equipment and items the players dropped. He had made a big fortune from it. This time, although the war still happened, due to the butterfly effect he had caused, the time and location had changed slightly.

From his perspective, these guild alliances announcing this challenge was not sudden. It was already the final stage of Version 4.0. If they did not create some big news, they would not have a chance to do so anytime soon. One reason was to justify killing those in the hostile alliances, and another was to strengthen the unity of the big guild alliances by having the normal players take part in it too.

"… Basically, they're bored, so they want to start a fight."

Han Xiao shook his head. The internal affairs of the players had nothing to do with him. He did not plan to interfere.

The location was not in the Ferdinand Battle Zone. It was on a planet in the frontlines called Marrison. When the players headed there to participate, it would affect the army's battle in the frontlines to a certain extent. Although the army could use orders to restrain the players and not let them participate in the big battle all players could take part in, it would not have a positive impact, nor did Han Xiao plan to do so.

After all, players were not really his employees. If he restrained them too much, it would only achieve the opposite effect.

Of course, not only him, but all the organizations who had players would be affected to different extents. If these forces forcefully stopped their players, it would instead benefit the army and make recruiting players easier in the future.

"The army players will stick together in this war. They'll be the largest group, so they'll probably be targeted by many other alliances… but that's not bad for me."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

The Pro League during the final stage of a version was an excellent way to boost sales. Many players would be willing to spend a lot of their savings to make themselves stronger. When that happened, the army's sales would rocket, and Han Xiao would harvest a lot of EXP.

However, the Pro League had already been hosted three times. Most normal players were now very aware that they had no chances. A lot of them preferred saving their EXP to use in the next version.

Large scale wars were different; the players would not miss it. It was also a natural opportunity to boost sales, which was very beneficial for him. He would be able to harvest even more EXP near the end of Version 4.0 that would become his inventory during the version update.

"If I remember correctly, the interval between Version 4.0 to Version 5.0 should be about half a century, even longer than the last one…"

The next version was the Calamity of the Supers. The conflict between the Beyond Grade As would break out, and some of the Primordial Ones would return. However, since he had changed a large portion of the storyline, the events in Version 5.0 would certainly be completely different because of the butterfly effect.

This was not a big deal. Han Xiao knew those people who were important, so he was not afraid of changing the original storyline. The biggest version of the next version was actually the players.

In Version 5.0, the maximum level of the players would become level 180, which meant they would become Calamity Grades. The version name 'Calamity of the Supers' was a subtle hint to the players that their impact on the universe in the next version would be tremendous.

"This is good news for me."

By then, the middle level combatants of the explored universe would skyrocket. Although the players would bring chaos, they would also become a crucial force in fighting the World Tree Civilization. In the World Tree War in his previous life, the importance of the players was absolutely irreplicable. If not for the millions of Calamity Grade players, the explored universe would have suffered even heavier damage.

Also, the army would become excessively stronger. All this planning throughout these past versions was for when the players evolved.

There were decades till the next version, so he had more than enough time to prepare. Plus, some of old Manison's words made a lot of sense; foundation was crucial for Mechanics. He planned to spend decades focusing on improving his Mechanic skills while waiting for the effects of [Key of Adeptus Mechanicus] to become stronger.

The effects of this talent would increase once every few days, continuously making him stronger. This meant that more and more of Manison's believers were running into his arms. He could imagine the shift in the Machinery Faith.

All kinds of thoughts flashed through his mind. Han Xiao continued to browse through the forums till the battlefield was cleaned up. He then boarded the spaceship back to Black Star Palace. He had made up his mind on finishing the remaining twenty-seven spars within two months.

…

In a secret Crimson Dynasty military training base, Gaud strolled through the training base, wearing a high-level dynasty officer uniform. He was not in a good mood.

Just now, Gaud had received a message from the dynasty's upper echelons, telling him to postpone the plan indefinitely. The plan referred to using his Esper Ability to try to figure out the core energy of the Evolution Cube.

Back when they came up with this plan, it was totally achievable. However, times were changing too quickly, disrupting the tempo of many hawk faction dynasty upper echelons. At this point, Black Star's position and strength had reached a new height, so this plan became more and more risky. Hence, the upper echelons had no choice but to pause this plan temporarily with resignation, both because they did not want to mess with Black Star as well as to keep Gaud hidden as a trump card.

At the root of it, this was because of Black Star's extremely quick growth that kept changing the situation repeatedly, so often that people could not react fast enough.

This was the source of Gaud's bad mood. Black Star's growth speed was even faster than his even though this was his new account. He could not even see Black Star's taillights. It was tough for him not to feel frustrated.

"Black Star… Black Star…" Gaud mumbled as he walked to a public training facility without realizing.

The sound of intense battles entered his ears. He looked at the source of the sound and saw a low-grade elite class fighting in pairs under the supervision of the drill sergeant. They looked like a group of novices.

At this time, two Grade C Pugilists were fighting in the venue, one having the upper hand and the other barely hanging on. It looked like the latter losing was just a matter of time.

Unsurprisingly, only a few seconds later, this spar ended. The one who was barely holding out got kicked out by a leg swing of his opponent. He slid on the floor and just so happened to stop in front of Gaud.

"Karlot, you lost again." The drill sergeant frowned at the loser. "You're at zero wins and nine losses. It's embarrassing."

"Sorry." Karlot rubbed his chest, stood up, and smiled with resignation.

The drill sergeant looked unhappy as he yelled, "All of your test scores are at the bottom. I really don't know why the people above have put you into my elite class to drag down the entire class' scores. I've allowed you to stay in this class because I can see you're hardworking enough, but if your scores are still at the bottom the next test, I won't give you another chance and will make you leave!"

After he said that, the classmates all looked at Karlot coldly, not hiding their dissatisfaction.

Although these people were students, they were talents the dynasty had selected from the various departments who were being trained in this secret base. Furthermore, this was an elite class. Everyone in it was a talented dynasty soldier, and they were all renowned in their own divisions.

The opportunity to receive this type of training was very rare, so these students treasured it very much. This was exactly why they disliked Karlot—he was too ordinary and not like an elite at all. Logically, he was not qualified to receive such training.

Due to how difficult it was to get this opportunity, these elites all felt it unfair. From their perspectives, the first thing they thought of was the word 'bribe' when they saw a mediocre soldier training with them, making them unavoidably reject Karlot.

Furthermore, as soldiers, they respected the strong above all. Karlot's ability was too low, so they looked down on him from the bottom of their heart. Naturally, they were not going to treat him well.

Noticing the cold eyes of everyone, Karlot sighed in his mind.

He had accepted the fact that he was mediocre long ago. He knew that these people were elites who were much more talented than him from the beginning, so he was not discouraged.

He had gained this opportunity to undergo such advanced training thanks to Black Star. Although he was carefree, he was not someone who would give up an amazing opportunity. However, he was already doing the very best within his capabilities, yet he still could not match up to the growth speed of these elites. There was nothing else he could do.

Gaud quietly observed from the side.

Some time ago, he had heard people say that someone who Black Star once heeded had entered this training base, and that person's name was Karlot. As it was related to Black Star, Gaud kept it in mind. This was the first time he had seen this person.

He sized Karlot up. All he could see from Karlot was the word 'mediocre'.

Gaud considered himself to have sharp eyes, but even he did not find anything special about Karlot. He was confused.

Why was Black Star interested in this guy? He's known for having accurate and sharp eyes. He shouldn't have made a poor judgement…

Gaud could not figure it out at all. He thought about it for a second before waving at the drill sergeant.

The drill sergeant had noticed Gaud long ago. He instantly put on a smile and walked over. Almost everyone in this base knew that Gaud was the person with the highest chances of becoming a Beyond Grade A and had received a lot of resources and training. Gaud's position was quite high.

"What is it, Gaud?"

"That novice called Karlot, whether he passes the tests or not, let him stay in the base," Gaud whispered.

Hearing this, the drill sergeant was puzzled.

Based on his test scores, Karlot was bound to be disqualified and leave the training base. He did not expect Gaud to speak for him.

"I'm not sure. This guy doesn't have much value. Keeping him here is a waste of resources."

"Do what you can then."

Gaud could not see what was special about Karlot either, but because of Black Star, he wanted to keep Karlot and observe him longer.

…

Han Xiao had stayed in Black Star Palace and did not go to the frontlines. One and half a month passed quickly.

On this day, a shocking piece of news suddenly erupted in the Modo Civilization!

The Tri-Race Senate announced the beginning of the impeachment process for the current Modo Three Kings. Throughout history, the impeachment of the highest leaders had occurred very few times, so this instantly shocked the whole society.

As the name suggested, this assembly was formed by the congressmen from all three races. It had extremely high power, including the impeachment right of the highest leaders. The initiators of this impeachment were thirty-three congressmen who proposed the impeachment together. The Tri-Race Senate approved it by voting. The preparations started quickly; it was clearly planned.

Being shocked was one thing, but the Modo citizens supported it to quite a large extent. The chaos in the civilization had already severely affected the daily operations of their society. Although this was caused by enemies, the citizens did not care much and blamed it on the highest leaders, which was much easier.

Marco had gathered more and more supporters, and he found the logical excuse of regaining order and objecting to the war. He used a long and formal report to analyze that Modo's chances of winning this war were extremely low. Using this as evidence, he objected to the Modo Three Kings' decision to continue supporting the expeditionary army, calling it a meaningless sacrifice.

His stand received recognition from quite a number of officials and citizens. Not everyone was willing to sacrifice their present interests for the so-called future potential.

The Modo Three Kings did not expect those who objected to their decisions to suddenly backstab them at such a crucial moment. Their plans were heavily disrupted.

Chapter 1180: Assassination

As soon as the impeachment proceedings started, the political world of the Modo Civilization became boisterous. All the factions were dragged in and forced to pick sides.

Modo had no choice but to shift their focus back to within the nation and deal with the impeachment. The three kings were forced to deploy their men to take part in a political war. Luckily, after so many years, their positions were firm and strong; they would not be overthrown easily.

There were extremely few advanced civilizations that were in a dictatorship. Being in the position as the highest leader did not mean instantly obtaining the highest power. Politics was an art of compromise; power came from obedience. Even as leaders of civilizations, in order to firm their position, they still had to fight for the support of various factions and train loyal followers. Only then would their power be materialized.

Otherwise, no matter what orders they gave, they would be obstructed by their political enemies. Becoming the highest leader did not mean the others would unconditionally obey them. There were many people who had their eyes on the position too.

In the following days, the citizens witnessed the changes in the political world. The Modo Three Kings and the opposing party pulled out one trick after another. The day before yesterday, someone resigned; yesterday, someone got summoned; today, someone was caught in a scandal. God only knew what would happen tomorrow. The citizens had plenty of new stories to follow.

Hearings of the Tri-Race Senate were hosted one after another. The objecting faction brought up a lot of evidence, and even some secrets that the citizens were not supposed to know were displayed, causing uproars among the public.

The Kunde Race incident was one of them. The objecting faction summoned key witnesses and had them provide the signatures of the Modo Three Kings that approved this operation. They then used this as evidence to prove that the Kunde Race incident was the reason Black Star was targeting Modo. Thus, they came to the conclusion that the Modo Three Kings had brought Black Star's hatred to the civilization; they were the culprits that caused Modo to be in this horrible situation. The objecting faction claimed that the Modo Three Kings had made an awful decision and that the Modo Three Kings were not capable enough of remaining as the leaders of the civilization.

There were some more similar pieces of evidence. The objecting faction blamed all the sinful things on the Modo Three Kings, emphasizing to the Tri-Race Senate that the Three Kings were not capable, and suggested changing them.

This was not framing the Modo Three Kings. As the highest leaders, even though some plans were not proposed by the Three Kings, they would only be carried out with the signatures of the three of them, so they could only take the blame.

Endless testimonies caused the situation to gradually worsen for the Modo Three Kings. However, their position would not be shaken so easily. Their connections were very comprehensive. Including the military, many factions were their firm supporters. These factions all had members in the Tri-Race Senate. They worked together to obstruct the impeachment, which was highly effective.

The military was firmly on the side of supporting the war, which brought the support of more important upper echelons. Compared to the supporters of the Modo Three Kings, the objecting faction led by Marco was no match. The investigations hit a wall very soon, so the objecting faction turned their focus to the next batch of Modo Three Kings candidates, hoping to gain their support, which also failed without much suspense.

With the impeachment fermenting, the matter led to political strife. The Modo Three Kings had wasted too much time. They did not want to waste more energy on this matter, so they did not hold back at all.

Therefore, this nonsense did not last too long. In the end, the Tri-Race Senate rejected the objecting faction's impeachment request. The result was basically a loss for both sides.

As the political opposition was dealt with, in order to regain their reputation, the Modo Three Kings decided to give a public speech to give a conclusive response on the impeachment matter.

…

Benid Square was one of the landmarks of the Modo Civilization's capital, a tourist destination with tons of visitors every day. On this day, it was used by the government as the venue for the Modo Three Kings to give a speech. The venue was already set up.

Due to their negative image to the public, the Modo Three Kings did not speak in the political building this time but instead chose to give the speech in front of the public to build an image that they were close to their citizens. The filtered audience filled the square.

A cordon had been set up around the square. Tons of security personnel were stationed around, protecting the perimeter with expressionless faces. At this time, an audience that extended beyond one's sights had gathered outside.

Many people held up banners with words like 'Overthrow the Three Kings'. They were all protestors… Although the objecting faction had lost, they still dealt irreversible damage to the Modo Three Kings' reputation.

The seats of the officials were around the podium, and the objecting faction's seats were all at the edge, clearly arranged deliberately. The others were not willing to even look in their general direction, not wanting to have any connections with the objecting faction that had lost.

"I didn't expect the Three Kings to invite us," a member of the objecting faction mumbled.

"They want to humiliate us in front of the public to enhance the effectiveness of the speech."

Marco was not in a good mood.

He knew full well that at this point, there was absolutely no way the Modo Three Kings had invited them to attend the speech to repair their relationship. They were certainly going to condemn their actions as victors.

Of course, the objecting faction only stepped out to try to impeach the Modo Three Kings because they were confident that they could win. However, they were defeated in the end. The trump cards they had pulled out were resolved one after another, and some witnesses had changed their testimonies. Marco could only admit his loss.

There were actually some others who had the same mindset as him but did not stand out this time because they did not dare take the risk. In order to change the path of the civilization, Marco was willing to take the risk. On the other hand, the people who hid to protect their positions did not take any actions despite the fact they objected to the Modo Three Kings' decisions and watched the armies being sacrificed meaninglessly. Although he had lost, he still despised these cowards.

After a while, the Modo Three Kings approached the podium. The spotlight focused on the three of them.

A loud round of applause instantly started on the square like it was rehearsed, silencing the furious yelling and cussing of countless spectators outside the square. The three of them waved at the same time, looked around at the audience inside the square, and smiled.

While the three of them looked around, their eyes deliberately paused for a moment when looking in the direction of Marco and the objecting faction before turning away. The camera then jumped to focus on the objecting faction, showing their forced smiles or expressionless faces.

"Humph…" Marco snorted softly while clapping with just enough force to make a noticeable sound.

He obviously understood the look the Modo Three Kings gave them. It was a look of winners, a look that said, "Revenge is a dish best served cold."

As the applause gradually stopped, one of the Modo Three Kings then spoke. "My people, Modo is a great civilization. We have stayed united since the exploration era, and generations of Three Kings have led us to create one miracle after another…"

The three of them followed the script they had memorized. They cut to the chase and mentioned the social unrest and the impeachment incident. They admitted that this was because of their decisions, but they emphasized that it was the enemy's conspiracy. They claimed, "Modo is walking on the right path. The enemies want us to back away, so they've used all kinds of plots and conspiracies, hoping to make us afraid."

The three of them also explained why they kept sending soldiers to the Flickering World, saying that it was for the civilization's future. During the long speech, the Three Kings explained and rebutted the matters the objecting faction had brought up during the impeachment, trying to save their reputation and the government's reputation as much as possible.

The Modo Three Kings' words sounded sensible. The people in the square clapped from time to time. The audience outside was gradually convinced too, and the number of protesters gradually decreased.

Other than the reporters, countless spectators were also recording the speech.

In the crowd outside the podium, a tall male held up a multifunctional commutation terminal and recorded the speech. He looked just like an ordinary spectator, but he was actually one of the spies of the Federation of Light responsible for obtaining intelligence. He was sent there to record first-hand footage.

While doing his job, this spy thought, The objecting faction has lost, but the Modo Three Kings have also been heavily hurt. It's good news…

The dust had settled. There was no more shocking news, only the speech from the winners. This spy did not think he would find anything valuable; he was only here because of his duty.

However, at this moment, a flash of light suddenly went past the corners of his eyes. The spy subconsciously turned around.

His eyes penetrated the crowd, and he saw a dim light on the back of a hooded man's hand, as if a mark was lighting up.

The next moment, a sharp golden light abruptly crossed his sights and shot out like a bolt of lightning.

The spy instantly turned and saw this flash of light arrive before the Modo Three Kings, who were giving a speech.

Clank!

An azure magic shield suddenly opened and stopped this flash of light. The Beyond Grade A defense enchantment on the Modo Three Kings activated instantly. It could guard against many kinds of attacks.

The speech suddenly stopped. Only then did the Modo Three Kings realize that the item that had attacked them was shockingly a golden spear. It was indeed Lothaire's weapon, the Deity Assassinator.

"Assassin!" The security personnel around were appalled.

Multiple Calamity Grade bodyguards who had been standing behind the Three Kings were shocked. They hastily activated their abilities to protect the Three Kings.

Although their reactions were quick, it was not quick enough. The outstandingly strong Beyond Grade A defense enchantment only stopped the Deity Assassinator for a moment before it was penetrated. The spear pinned one of the Modo Three Kings right on the ground. Shock and indignation lingered on his face.

The sudden change stunned everyone present.

Someone attempted to assassinate the Three Kings‽

As their minds fully digested what this information meant, horror appeared on countless faces.

"Run!"

"Murder!"

"Call a doctor!"

"Lock down the square immediately… No, lock down the planet!"

The next moment, the entire place went haywire. All the spectators, be it in or outside the square, were panicking and fleeing. While yelling, the security personnel escorted the remaining two kings out of the scene while searching the entire place. The officials were terrified and hastily fled under the protection of their bodyguards. The boisterous venue instantly became a chaotic mess.

"Who sent this killer? This is insane!"

Marco fled as fast as he could, his face filled with horror.

Assassinating the highest leader of a Super Star Cluster civilization right on its mother planet was tantamount to suicide!

God only knew how many years it had been since something like this last happened. Even the three Universal Civilizations would not do this. Nobody could have expected it. The Modo Three Kings were usually in the central political building, but today, they hosted a rare public speech, and it became an opportunity for the assassin.

The most unbelievable part was that the assassin actually succeeded. The Beyond Grade A level defense enchantment on the Three Kings was like a piece of paper.

In the panicking crowd, the spy from the Federation of Light opened his eyes wide, turned, and tried to find the hooded man, but he had disappeared without a trace.

"Who the hell was that guy? This is a completely suicidal attack! There's absolutely no way he can escape the Modo mother planet!"

The spy's face twitched. His eyes were filled with disbelief.

He had never expected to witness something this big today with his own eyes.

In almost an instant, his professional knowledge made him sensitively realize the opportunity to make use of this.

Chapter 1181: What a F*cking Genius You Are

The news that one of the Modo Civilization Three Kings had been assassinated quickly spread across galactic society. The king who was attacked was announced to be deceased. This sudden incident shocked the entire universe!

Be it the officials of advanced civilizations or ordinary people of the galactic society, the first response they had when they heard about this could be concluded with three words.

What the f*ck!

This was the leader of a Super Star Cluster civilization who died, not some nobody, someone whose position was only inferior to the leaders of the three Universal Civilizations. To the galactic residents, something like this seemed to only have happened centuries ago. Such shocking news had never happened in the past god knew how many years.

To ordinary people, the leaders of advanced civilizations would never die from assassinations. This was exactly why it was unbelievable when it actually happened. This proved one thing—everyone was equal in the face of death, and no one could not be killed.

Right after the assassination happened, the entire Modo mother planet entered the highest state of alert. Countless soldiers searched everywhere thoroughly for the culprit.

The spies of many other civilizations were dragged into this too. Quite a number of these people were monitored by the Modo Civilization; Modo just never did anything to them, hoping to catch a bigger fish. Now, however, these things were no longer a concern. All of these people were captured and interrogated.

The Modo Civilization instantly restricted the leaking of the footage and very quickly made an announcement using extremely harsh words, emphasizing the fact that assassinating the leader of the Modo Civilization was an act of provocation and humiliation to the entire civilization. They would be investigating this with all of their forces and claimed that it was most likely done by an external enemy. They also said that they would certainly not let things go once they found out who the culprit was.

The assassination made the public both shocked and lost. In this situation, the announcement the Modo Civilization made instantly guided the thoughts of the public, triggering their collective anger, hoping to redirect their emotions toward the enemy.

Usually, this was the right thing to do.

However, the various organizations the three Universal Civilizations had hidden in the Modo Civilization's territory would not watch this happen. They kept stirring up fires everywhere. They published all kinds of opinions to affect the impact of the Modo Civilization's announcement, changing the mindset of the public and confusing the situation.

The methods they used were not flashy at all. All they did was state all kinds of new speculations regarding the assassination, mainly in two directions. One was to claim that the objecting faction had a motive to take the risk and assassinate the Three Kings because their attempt to gain power had just failed. The made-up story was structured so well it almost felt real.

The other was spreading rumors claiming that the assassin was actually an extremist of the other two races created by the racism lately, hoping to incite the racism issues.

Both of these theories had flaws, but conspiracy theories always had listeners. While the quantum network provided convenience to the galactic society, it also became an important platform for guiding public opinion. All kinds of information was available in the quantum network, weakening the judgmental skills of the public. Plus, the assassination made it difficult for the majority of the public to remain sensible. Hence, these two theories surprisingly received recognition by quite a lot of people.

At the same time, there were also dozens of terrorist organizations claiming to be responsible for this incident, fighting for it as if this was an opportunity to firm their positions in the gray world.

The number of people who supported the racist thoughts and believed the political assassination theory was growing rapidly. The seed of chaos gradually matured. One could never know what kind of strange opinions people might have till something big happened. It was complete anarchy.

The Modo Civilization was beleaguered because of this assassination and had no time to slowly deal with the public opinion at all. They had no choice but to take tough measures, forbidding the public from discussing these two conspiracy theories. Although the upper echelons clearly knew that this would only make things worse in the future, they had to first restrain the spread of these rumors.

This incident received immense attention. Countless organizations paid close attention to it. A storm was brewing under the noses of the public.

Han Xiao, who was far in the Flickering World, received the news too.

…

"What the hell, someone assassinated the Modo Three Kings? Whose cutie did that‽"

Han Xiao's eyes opened wide. He was surprised too.

He had once had similar thoughts, but he had never taken action, nor did he order his subordinates to carry out the assassination.

The main reason was because of the restrictions of his identity. He was now a hero of the lawful world. No way could he attempt to assassinate the leader of an advanced civilization.

However, if someone else did it, Han Xiao was glad to see it happen.

He could roughly guess what impact this would have afterward. Whether the Modo Civilization could capture the culprit or not, their investigation had to achieve results. Even if they could not find out the truth, they had to find someone to blame it on to redirect the nation's internal social conflicts, giving the public a target to vent their emotions.

This depended on what Modo chose to do. If they decided to make this matter smaller, blaming it on the terrorist organizations outside their territory was most convenient. If they wanted to make this matter even more severe, they could both put the blame on the three Universal Civilizations or him. This way, Modo would have found a new motive for the Flickering War and would keep sending more armies over while keeping the moral high ground.

As for the truth… who knew? The Modo Civilization forbade the video from leaking, so he could not watch the footage of the assassination. However, he felt that the three Universal Civilizations were definitely not the culprits. There was absolutely no need for them to do this.

Could it really be an extremist?

Han Xiao was very curious.

"Whose man is this? This is such an honorable sacrifice!"

While he was wondering, his communicator suddenly rang.

He took it out and glanced at it, it was an encrypted communication request from Lothaire.

Han Xiao's expression became stiff, he suddenly had a bad feeling.

"Calling me at this time, don't tell me…"

After hesitating for two seconds, he picked up the communication and heard the steady breathing in the channel.

"Lothaire." Han Xiao subconsciously lowered his voice.

"Hmm."

"Please don't tell me that you did this…"

"I did."

Hearing this answer, Han Xiao's vision went dark for a moment.

What the hell, after making these guesses, turns out it's my man!

This is too much. I'm not sure my tiny heart can take it…

"Are you insane? I didn't order you to do this!"

"You told me to disrupt the order of Modo's society. I understood what your goals are." Lothaire's tone was serious.

Han Xiao felt like his chest was stuffed. "So, you decided on your own to assassinate the Modo Three Kings‽"

"I've fulfilled my duty."

What a f*cking genius you are!

Han Xiao's face began contorting.

No wonder you dared attack EsGod!

For such a steady and firm man like me, why do I have such an impulsive and head-strong subordinate‽

Han Xiao took a few deep breaths and calmed his emotions.

At this point, the only thing he could do was accept reality and clean up the mess.

"… Where are you? Have you escaped the Modo mother planet?"

"Yes, or I wouldn't have contacted you."

Lothaire briefly explained what had happened.

He was not completely reckless. He had already infiltrated the Modo mother planet more than a month ago and come up with many ways of getting out, only acting after the plan was fully complete. He had been waiting for the opportunity. As he could not come into contact with the Three Kings, he had been waiting patiently all along till a few days ago. When he saw the Three Kings' announcement to give a speech, he knew that this was the opportunity, so he struck after making enough preparations.

With one assassination after another, Lothaire had gained enough experience and become an expert. From the assassination succeeding till the Modo Civilization excuted the lockdown, there would be a reaction process in between, and he used this bit of time to successfully escape. The entire process was well planned and organized. However, he was only temporarily safe now. He still had to face the Modo Civilization's search afterward.

After hearing Lothaire's description, Han Xiao sighed and said, "It won't be that easy to escape from someone else's territory. Pause all your assassination missions. Killing one leader is effective enough. You don't have to continue targeting them. Focus on escaping first. I'll see if I can bring you back."

What was done was done; he could not let Lothaire fall into Modo's hands.

Things like this could be done but not shared, or there would be much more cons than pros. As long as Modo did not capture Lothaire, there would be no solid evidence, and he would never admit it.

To say that Han Xiao did not blame Lothaire for making this decision on his own would be a lie. He was originally peacefully watching things develop all according to his plan, but now there were risks. Assassinating the Three Kings was not in his plan.

However, from another perspective, there were pros to this too.

Since the assassin was his man, this meant that the damage this incident caused to the Modo Civilization would also be counted toward the mission progress of [Kunde Race Leader's Last Wish]. He might complete this mission earlier than expected.

…

Bang!

A team of soldiers charged into the office, looked around, and coldly said, "Marco, come with us for investigation."

Marco stood up slowly with a bitter smile.

All objecting factions were key targets of the investigations, since they had motive. They were all dragged down by this. No matter how wrongly accused they felt, they had no choice but to obediently accept the investigation.

The sudden assassination affected the objecting faction negatively too.

At this point of time, Marco only had one thought.

F*ck!

Chapter 1182: You Are Only at the First Layer, But I Am Already at the Fifth Layer

In the conference room that now had triple the guards compared to before. The remaining two kings of Modo and the various upper echelons were hosting an emergency meeting. Everyone there was experienced. They quickly passed the shocked and panicked state to being filled with rage.

"Have we found out who did this?" The two kings of Modo were furious.

Every time they thought of what happened, they felt exceedingly uneasy—if the one who was giving the speech at that time was not their unlucky colleague, they might have been the one who died!

Daring to assassinate them, the leaders of the civilization, was an insult to the entire Modo Civilization. The two of them were overwhelmingly enraged.

"Not yet, but the intelligence department has submitted the analysis of the recording and found matches in the database…"

An intelligence official operated on the table with a solemn expression. The next moment, a green virtual screen rose up from the table in front of every official. On it was the same file.

"The weapon the culprit used is a golden spear. According to the data, the master of this weapon is a highly dangerous wanted criminal with the code name [Mystery]. The earliest record of this man was during the Kunde Race incident. This man committed multiple assassinations at that time and then disappeared for more than a decade. Recently, he started to act again in our territory, killing the heads of all kinds of industries…

"According to the analysis, [Mystery] has top notch Calamity Grade strength, possibility at the level of a Beyond Grade A seed. The golden spear weapon he uses is a powerful enchanted weapon. However, due to the little observation records we have, we were unable to obtain too much information. Nonetheless, from this assassination incident, we can speculate that [Mystery]'s weapon possesses an extremely strong ability to penetrate energy and also deals extra damage to strong targets. Also, [Mystery] might be acting with a group. The assassinations committed by many others seem to be related to him too. We suspect he might have formed an organization in the ten or so years he disappeared…"

The frequent assassinations targeted at the Modo Civilization lately were not all done by the Assassin's Society. There were also other active organizations. Advanced civilizations did not have a shortage of enemies. Seeing that Modo was in chaos, some enemies had added salt to their wounds. Some of these were assassination organizations from the black market, some were from the terrorist organizations outside Modo's territory, and there were also some racial extremists and criminals who disguised themselves as assassins to commit crimes. The society was extremely unstable, and the police forces were beleaguered.

The two kings of Modo finished reading the report. One of them yelled, "What I'm more concerned about is whose orders this killer follows? Whose organization does he belong to‽"

"[Mystery]'s appearance is clearly related to the Kunde Race incident. Back then, the main participants were the Crimson Dynasty and their allies. Although we don't know which organization this killer belongs to exactly, he certainly is related to the Crimson Dynasty. He might be a secret soldier of the dynasty, or he could be an officer of one of the dynasty's Beyond Grade A allies…"

"So, the Crimson Dynasty very likely approved this‽" the two kings of Modo asked.

"This… isn't certain." The intelligence official thought about it for a moment. "The situation now is not the same as before. More than ten years ago, the Beyond Grade A Association was not yet founded, and the dynasty still had enough control over their Beyond Grade A allies, so the assassinations back then were indeed related to the dynasty. However, the situation has changed now. We can't rule out the possibility that this incident was a private operation of one of their Beyond Grade A allies."

Hearing this, everyone's expression changed, and a name subconsciously appeared in their minds.

"Could it be… Black Star‽" The two kings of Modo were furious.

Although the Crimson Dynasty was scum, taking the risk of assassinating the leader of an advanced civilization had many more cons than pros for them. They basically had no reason to do this.

It seemed like only Black Star who had exceptional hatred toward them had motive.

"Black Star! He got the upper hand in the Flickering War and cost us a lot, but did that make him feel he can do whatever he wants‽ How dare he do this? This is outrageous! Modo will never forgive him!"

The two kings of Modo were burning with rage.

They now had another goal to participate in the Flickering War, not just for the future of the civilization but also to make Black Star pay with blood. The two of them believed that after this, the entire civilization could become united against an exterior enemy. There would no longer be any objecting faction.

However, at this time, an upper echelon hesitated for a moment before objecting. "But I don't feel that makes sense. What's Black Star's goal in doing this? Just to feel good? There's no reason! He's a man who prioritizes profit over everything. He's already gained the upper hand in the Flickering World… To be completely frank, he can slowly make us suffer and incur even more losses. There's no need to assassinate our leader at all. In fact, doing so would even bring him risks.

"If he gets exposed, the heroic image the three Universal Civilizations have built for him will be severely damaged. He'll lose the advantages he obtained. Black Star doesn't feel like someone who'd make such a reckless decision…"

After hearing this theory, the various upper echelons present also frowned in doubt.

"That does make sense. Black Star wouldn't do meaningless things. If the assassination was ordered by him, it's definitely to achieve some kind of goal…"

"And what goal would that be?"

The room went silent. The people present worked brainstormed as much as they could.

More than ten seconds later, an intelligence official's eyes suddenly gleamed. He stood up and said, "I think I figured out Black Star's plan!"

"Oh? Quickly tell us about it." Everyone's eyes focused on him.

This intelligence official said with a firm tone, "Black Star did this to prevent us from surrendering!"

"Huh?"

Everyone tilted their head. Big question marks appeared above their heads.

"Erm… explain." The two kings of Modo frowned.

"This is my speculation. Black Star knows Modo has no chance of turning the table, so he's worried we might give up the Flickering War and withdraw the expeditionary army. If that happens, he won't be able to continue damaging us. Therefore, in order to prevent us from backing out, he secretly ordered his assassin to do this, openly provoking and insulting the entire Modo Civilization. He predicted our reaction—whether the culprit is his man or not, we'll definitely suspect him.

"Then, due to our hostile relationship, he feels that we'll likely claim that he's the mastermind to damage his reputation, which will go exactly according to his plan. Once we claim Black Star is the mastermind, under the eyes of the entire universe, we'll have to show we're not going to let him off easily, so we won't be able to easily pull out the expeditionary army. Instead, we'll have to keep sending in more troops, or we'll be seen as a wimp to the outside world. As an advanced civilization whose leader has been assassinated, we must never compromise. This way, Black Star will have successfully maintained the situation and forced us to keep fighting. He will then continue eating up our troops."

The others trembled and hastily went through their own thoughts. When they realized that this was exactly what they were thinking of, they felt a chill running down their spine.

I knew it. Black Star has calculated even our responses… Luckily, we predicted his predictions.

The two kings of Modo shook their heads and said, "No, no, Black Star knows we'll accuse him. Why isn't he afraid of his reputation being damaged?"

"I think he really isn't afraid…" an official said. "If we don't catch the culprit, we'll have no solid evidence. With the heroic image Black Star already has, which side will the outside world believe? Even if there is evidence, Black Star can still refuse to admit it and accuse us of framing him. Plus, the heroic image he has now was built by the three Universal Civilizations. Although he's enjoyed the benefits of it, he's restrained by his reputation. If he can get rid of this restriction, it won't be all bad for him. In fact, the three Universal Civilizations might be more worried than him in that case…"

Many people nodded and felt this made sense.

The two kings of Modo suppressed their wrath and said, "If this is really Black Star's doing, are we not only going to hold him responsible for it but even cover it up for him? Absolutely impossible! Don't even think about it!"

The two of them admitted that this speculation made sense, but in order to not fall into Black Star's trap, how could they, an advanced civilization, not hold him responsible but instead cover it up for him?

This is ridiculous. Does he think we're shameless?

As a powerful Super Star Cluster civilization, how can we be intimidated by this kind of trick? We will not compromise in any form!

The intelligence official who made this speculation hesitated for a moment before speaking again. "Actually, there's another possibility."

"Go on!"

"Ahem, I just thought about it. If there's a third party that predicted Black Star's and our responses judging from our hatred of each other, what if they sent someone to disguise as or bribed [Mystery] to do this, purposely carrying out the assassination in public to start a storm all to frame Black Star and increase the hatred between us… Is that possible?"

Hearing this, the others were perplexed.

This kind of plot was not rare in history, so the theory was completely possible.

"Who would do that?"

"Who else? Our enemy or Black Star's enemy, of course. They might want to watch us fight each other in the dark…"

"If this is the case, should we still pull out the expeditionary army so that we won't fall into the enemy's trap?"

The two kings of Modo were lost in the layers of speculation.

They were not at fault for overthinking. Smart people would always make all kinds of speculations for things, guessing the reason behind it, deriving the matter to the fourth or fifth layer. Never would they guess how simple the truth actually was—it was nothing but the sole actions of a reckless man.

"Your Excellencies, we're just speculating. We can't confirm that Black Star is the culprit yet. Catching the assassin is our priority now!" an upper echelon reminded.

The two kings of Modo nodded heavily and shouted, "That's right! No matter what, we have to track the killer. We must catch him and find out the mastermind. Even if this is really Black Star's trap, Modo will never compromise!"

After saying that, the two of them were filled with frustration. They felt like no matter what choice they made, it would still be within Black Star's plan.

It's terrifying to have an enemy like this!

The people present exchanged looks. Many people wanted to say something, but no one did in the end.

If this was really Black Star's trap, the decision the two kings of Modo made would have fallen right into it. To some people, the two kings were losing their cool.

The objecting faction was being investigated, but there were still some with the same thoughts who did not expose themselves, and they were feeling even more shaken now.

Maybe Marco and the others were right. It's really time for new leaders.

In the corner, seeing that no one was paying attention to him anymore, the intelligence official who made the speculation sat down looking still unsatisfied. He only had one thought in his mind.

Get me a drink. I can still brainstorm!

…

If Modo was only suspecting Black Star, the Crimson Dynasty would be completely certain.

In the Ruler's office of the Crimson Dynasty, Urranrell held her chin with her hands and said, "… So, Black Star might have done this to prevent the Modo Civilization from backing away?"

Modo had forbidden the sharing of the recordings, so the process of the assassination could not be found through normal channels. Of course, the three Universal Civilizations had ways to get the recording, not through Virtual Technology but totally because they had accumulated enough information channels.

In this respect, the accumulation of advanced civilizations was far superior compared to Beyond Grade As. For example, Han Xiao's forces were limited in the Primeval Star River. Although his Virtual Technology could get him the recordings easily, it still required a process of going there from the Flickering World and activating Virtual Intrusion. Not doing anything personally but still getting the information belonged to the territory of having information sources.

Back during the Kunde Race incident, Black Star had worked with the dynasty on assassinations. Since she had seen it before, although she did not know who the user of the golden spear was, she was certain that this man was Black Star's subordinate. Hence, she immediately thought that assassinating the Modo Three Kings was Black Star's plan.

Looking at the report on the screen, Urranrell thought, Hehe, Black Star is more daring than I imagined, even assassinating a leader of an advanced civilization… Although that breaks the rules a little, it seems quite effective.

Not long after receiving the news, she had also figured out Black Star's 'goal'.

The three Universal Civilizations did not want the Modo Civilization to retreat this soon. Causing as much damage as possible to these Super Star Cluster civilizations was the three Universal Civilizations' goal. Black Star's 'actions' matched the interest of the three Universal Civilizations.

Wonderful, wonderful… Nonetheless, this does cross the line a bit. Urranrell wiped off the smile on her face.

A Beyond Grade A assassinating the leader of an advanced civilization was a very sensitive matter. It would alert all the advanced civilizations including the three Universal Civilizations.

Just thinking about what this meant would explain why the leaders of the advanced civilizations were so concerned about this.

Because this was the oldest profession of Beyond Grade As when they first appeared!

Using individuals who possessed strength above the limits for assassinations was much more valuable and effective than putting them in large battles. One could easily imagine how much destruction an expert Beyond Grade A assassin could bring.

Back during the exploration era, Beyond Grade A assassins who specifically targeted leaders of civilizations were nightmares of the civilizations that survived. The main reason the three Universal Civilizations built the Psionic Seal Rings around their mother planets was to guard against sudden attacks from other civilization but also to guard against assassination attempts from Beyond Grade A assassins.

This assassination incident reminded Urranrell of many tragic examples in the exploration era. Once someone opened this box, it might cause prolonged negative effects to advanced civilizations.

After pondering silently for quite some time, Urranrell sighed.

Times had changed. No matter what, Black Star was an important ally recognized by the dynasty, a National Pillar.

She had no choice but to help to clean up his mess. Be it because of morals or logic, there was no way she could 'betray her ally'.

"I don't know if Black Star's subordinate will be able to escape… I shall have our people in the Modo Civilization's territory provide some help secretly just in case…"

Chapter 1183: Disqualified

You have triggered the urgent mission [Escape]!

Mission Introduction: Your friend Lothaire has successfully assassinated the Modo Civilization leader. He is being pursued and is trying to escape the Modo Civilization's territory. He needs help.

Mission Requirements: Help Lothaire escape the Modo Civilization territory.

Reward: 8 Billion EXP, 2 Random Rewards, draw 1 ability/talent from Lothaire, [Civilization Leader Slayer] milestone.

Remarks: By accepting this mission, -3,000 Modo Civilization Favorability.

"Hmm, the mission only appeared now?"

In Black Star Palace, a notification popped up on Han Xiao's interface. He was both surprised and speechless.

Briefly looking at the mission introduction, Han Xiao accepted it without hesitation. There was already no room for his Modo Civilization Favorability to decrease any further.

Helping Lothaire was something he had to do, so getting rewarded for it was just a cherry on top. He only found it weird that the mission did not pop up when he chatted with Lothaire but only appeared after he had made the arrangements.

"The arrangements have been made. I wonder if I can get Lothaire out."

Han Xiao shook his head.

He was not very confident. On the low side, the odds of success were only ninety-five percent.

Ever since he became the three Universal Civilizations' consultant, building subdivisions for the Black Star Army had become much easier. There were subdivisions in the Primeval Star River too. Although he could not build an intelligence network there, the armed forces stationed there were quite strong. Han Xiao had also left quite a lot of mechanical soldiers there, including a King mechanical suit just in case.

After receiving the news from Lothaire, he had instantly ordered his men to infiltrate Modo's territory with a King. As long as they could rendezvous, Lothaire would be able to immediately escape using the King suit. The others in the Assassin's Society would have to figure something out themselves, but since they were not the main target and did not know Black Star was their boss, there was not much intelligence they could leak.

The King mechanical suit was the Universal Treasure that Han Xiao had built the most times. Although it was extremely expensive to build, ever since he obtained [Billion Mechanic Empire—Manison], his success rate of building Gold equipment had increased tremendously, saving him a lot of money. He had to admit that Manison's Exclusive Talent was incredible.

Of course, the main reason he could build so many of them was that he was rich.

Thinking back to when he just entered the galaxy, he had to carefully plan how to spend every Ena, but now he was too lazy to even look at deals that would earn him less than fifty million Enas profit.

"Maybe this is what growth is…"

Although rescuing Lothaire was important, he did not plan to go there himself. It was very far away, and having the local subdivision's mechanical troops take his Lord's Avatar along was more than enough. He had already done everything he could; there was not much more he could do to help Lothaire.

At this time, Black Star was on the rooftop of Black Star Palace, hovering five meters off the floor.

Dozens of different-sized, ring-shaped mechanical devices hovered around him. From Han Xiao's perspective, each of the rings was wrapped around hundreds of stars. Silk-like beams of light crisscrossed inside the rings like an energy filtering net, picking out tiny dots of light from nothing that landed on Han Xiao's body and dissolved, absorbed by his skin.

He was training Ames' [Dragon Emperor Star Energy Extraction Technique]. The ring devices were the assistive tools he had built called Star Energy Collectors. They could enhance the effects of the Dragon Emperor Star Energy Extraction Technique.

Han Xiao let out a breath of air that consisted of star energy and felt the energy flow inside his body. It was as if his cells were shrouded in a fuzzy layer of star light. He tutted with satisfaction.

"Tsk, the effects of this energy training technique are even better than Heber's Stellar Furnace Cultivation. Ames is quite creative. What a nice surprise this is."

Not a single Super would be unhappy about having too much energy. Even Beyond Grade As who could infinitely regain energy would never stop training their energy. Every slight increase in their maximum energy was an increase in their limits, and Han Xiao was no exception. He had always taken energy training very seriously and frequently searched for all kinds of energy training techniques.

Originally, among all the energy training techniques he had, [Heber Stellar Furnace Cultivation] had the best effects. It gave him a total of 16,750 increase in his maximum energy. Now, its position was replaced by [Dragon Emperor Star Energy Extraction Technique].

This energy training technique gave him 800 base energy, but the training time limit was 800. Each period of training it would give him up to 30 energy. In the most ideal situation, this could increase his maximum energy by close to 25,000.

Such an amazing effect could totally increase his Energy Rank by a whole new level, giving him a new layer of attribute bonuses. The impact would be tremendous!

Even though he had [Radiation Absorption], which would make him stronger without him having to do anything at all, it only gave him about 16,000 energy over close to thirty years, still less than [Dragon Emperor Star Energy Extraction Technique].

Nonetheless, [Radiation Absorption] gave him quite a lot of attribute bonuses in Strength, Dexterity, and Endurance.

Old Man Manison had once said that the strength of Mechanics came from their foundation. The longer they lived, the stronger they were. This ability was the perfect proof of that.

The training for this time ended. Han Xiao put the Star Energy Collector away and headed down back to the office while browsing the forums.

There were still some days till the date of the guild alliance war. Almost all the guild alliances responded to it; the influence was clearly visible. The sales of the army's faction store rocketed through the roof. The army players finally stopped saving money and spent like crazy. The EXP Han Xiao received in the past few days was massive.

On the other hand, the preparation for the fourth season of the Pro League had also started long ago, receiving quite the attention, indirectly increasing the players' shopping desire, helping him once again before the version ended.

"At this speed, when Version 4.0 ends, not only will I have enough EXP to level up to 340, but I'll even have quite a lot to spare."

Han Xiao was quite satisfied.

A blonde female walked out from the corner ahead. When she saw Han Xiao, she was stunned for a full second. She then trotted and sprinted into Han Xiao's arms.

"Uncle!" Aurora hugged Han Xiao tightly.

"How old are you now, still acting like a kid?" Han Xiao rubbed Aurora's hair, pressed on her head, and pushed her away.

"I'll always be a kid in front of you." Aurora giggled.

She was indeed qualified to say this. Her overflowing vital energy had kept her looking like a teenager.

Han Xiao placed his hand on her head and asked, "How is your strength progressing?"

"Quite fast." Aurora raised her hand and released a cluster of vital energy. It seemed to be brighter than before.

"Let me take a look."

Nanoparticles flowed at the tip of Han Xiao's finger and formed a metal needle. He stabbed Aurora's arm and triggered the combat information, seeing her full attributes.

Han Xiao looked at it and nodded with satisfaction.

Ever since Aurora became the master of the Holy Light Particle, Han Xiao had hired a ton of employees to specifically cultivate the Holy Light Seeds, helping Aurora become stronger. The effect of that was spectacular.

The Vital Energy Esper Ability was unique, so Aurora would never hit a wall. As long as she accumulated enough, her Grade would smoothly increase. Therefore, the method of harvesting leeks using the Holy Light Particle was perfect for her, making her grow at an incredible speed, much quicker than growing naturally. With her current growth speed, it would not take hundreds of years for Aurora to become a Beyond Grade A. The time would be reduced by roughly seventy to ninety percent.

Han Xiao smiled and said, "Not bad, not bad, I'm satisfied with your progress. Keep it up. Now go play,"

"Humph, I've been doing a lot of things in the army, not just playing. Don't always see me as a kid!" Aurora puffed her cheeks, turned, and ran away.

You just said you'll always be a kid, and now you're unhappy about me seeing you as a kid. What in the world…

Women are so unpredictable, even harder to understand than old man Manison's Felon technology.

Han Xiao shook his head and did not chase after Aurora, instead returning to his office.

As soon as he walked in, his communicator rang. He looked at it, and to his surprise, it was a call from Kasuyi.

Han Xiao casually sat on the Throne, lay back, and picked it up.

"Yo, Old Kasuyi, you rarely ever contact me. What's this about?"

"Are you free?"

"What, you want to ask me out?"

"Something like that. I'm planning to explore a special secondary dimension and hope to team up with a Mechanic. It'd be best if you're free."

Han Xiao's eyes flickered. He sat up straight slightly and asked, "Why didn't you go to Manison? Aren't the two of you quite close?"

"He's not in a good situation at the moment, so it's not wise to look for him. Comparatively, you're my top choice. You're more suited for this mission than him."

"Oh? Why?"

"Because that place is dangerous. I need a tank to stand in front, so… you know what I'm saying." Kasuyi coughed.

Han Xiao tutted.

No wonder you came to me. Turns out it's because of my tankiness.

Why hide something like this? You can just tell me you want my body.

"How dangerous is that secondary dimension?"

"I've never done field research, so I don't know the details either. However, it's definitely very dangerous. Even Beyond Grade As' lives can be threatened."

"Who else is going?"

"Just you and me. I don't want too many people to take part in this operation."

Hearing this, Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

He felt that this was most certainly not just a simple exploration. He wondered what secret goal Kasuyi had.

"That's about it. Black Star, when are you free?"

"Erm… in a few months. You know what's happening between Modo and me. I don't have time to do something else for the time being. Are you in a hurry?"

"Not really. I can wait for you, but don't make me wait too long."

"That's easy. You can deal with Modo together with me, then I'll be free sooner, right?" Han Xiao teased.

"Hehe, go trick someone else." Kasuyi smiled faintly.

"I can surely go with you, but you'll at least have to show some sincerity, you know," Han Xiao said.

"What reward do you want? As long as it's a not too excessive request, I will agree."

"Now that you suddenly say that, I really don't know what I want… What about more requests?"

"No, just one." Kasuyi's expression remained the same.

"Then I've not decided yet."

Han Xiao shrugged. This was a favor from Kasuyi, so he did not want to waste it.

"It's still early anyway. Take your time to think about it. Tell me when you've made up your mind."

After the agreement was made, Kasuyi did not waste much time. They chatted for a little bit before hanging up.

Han Xiao put the communicator down and pondered.

"Fascinating. Even Kasuyi needs a teammate to bear the risk together. What's going on in that secondary dimension? Is it really that dangerous?"

Sadly, no mission was triggered yet, so he had no clue.

After pondering for a while longer and still having no idea, he put this matter in the back of his mind.

…

In the next ten or so days, the Modo Civilization searched everywhere for Lothaire. However, it was not going smoothly at all, and accidents occurred frequently. The forces the Crimson Dynasty planted in Modo's territory kept stirring trouble, obstructing the investigation in all ways possible, but they also lost quite a number of men who were captured and interrogated by Modo.

In this situation, the assassins inside Modo's territory all stopped acting and went into hiding, afraid of being suspected. They were all shocked by how daring this assassin who killed the Modo Civilization's leader was.

During the thorough investigation, Lothaire's experience proved to be a huge help. He continuously hid, shifted locations, and covered his tracks, avoiding the soldiers time after time.

He had multiple stealth abilities to begin with and the bonus of the Medium Luck Glow, so he was able to rendezvous with the mechanical army Han Xiao had sent into Modo's territory without getting caught in any battles.

The mechanical army successfully handed the King over to Lothaire. With it, he teleported away directly and finally escaped. He would never be found by Modo.

The Modo Civilization did not know about this. They were still searching everywhere. However, just a few days later, a sudden change happened in the Modo Civilization's leading level again.

As one of Modo's leaders had passed away, one of the Three Kings was missing. The race this position represented was very unhappy, and they did not want this situation to carry on. Therefore, a candidate quickly replaced this hole for the time being, and the Three Kings were complete again.

However, this new leader's political stand seemed to be different from the other two kings—he did not support sending more soldiers to the Flickering World.

Due to all kinds of factors, the objecting faction seemed to have grown stronger once again. Those objecting faction upper echelons, including Marco, were all released after they were proved innocent. Under the protection of some kind of political power, not only were they not cleansed, but they were even firmer about objecting to the decision to continue participating in the Flickering War.

A storm started in the Modo Civilization's leading level again, but this time was different from the public impeachment. Instead, it was all going on in private. The public did not know the truth; they only noticed that the shifting of officials seemed to be more frequent.

No outsiders knew what kind of political strife and compromising the Modo upper echelons had made. They only knew that more than half a month after the assassination incident, the Modo Civilization publicly announced the progress of the investigation.

The report did not mention the names of the three Universal Civilizations and the Black Star Army at all. They only stated that many suspects had been caught, and they had made some progress, but the details of the progress were not stated at all.

At the end of the report, the Modo Civilization stated that they would be attacking all the terrorist organizations outside the territory that had claimed responsibility for the assassination. They expressed that this was an insult to Modo's face, and these organizations were key suspects.

Under the operations of the Modo Civilization, the public opinion of the nation was directed at these terrorist organizations. The hatred was shifted.

The spies and mechanical armies that Han Xiao had left in the Modo expeditionary army's territory discovered their sudden movements—expeditionary army fleets disappeared in the territory one after another.

Very soon, not just the Black Star Army, but the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance also noticed this.

Although it was not clearly stated, everyone could guess what the Modo Civilization was doing—the Modo expeditionary army was retreating!

The objecting faction rose, the nation's internal state was in chaos, and there were many possible traps behind the assassination. In the end, the objecting faction got the upper hand. The two old kings of Modo were forced to compromise. The order to pull out the expeditionary army was made. They had decided to give up on participating in the Flickering War.

A simpler conclusion for this would be…

The Modo Civilization was now disqualified by Black Star!

Chapter 1184: A Wise Assassin Is Not a Good Assassin

In the army commander's office of Black Star Palace, Lothaire's remote projection stood in the middle of the room. Han Xiao circled him, sized him up, and sighed from time to time.

"Kid, although you've successfully escaped this time, don't feel glad. I need to properly talk to you about this."

"What orders do you have?" Lothaire calmly accepted the scolding.

"Although the plan worked, you made the decision on yourself, and I had to clean up for you. I'm your boss, not the other way around. For something as big as this, you should ask me before you carry the plan out, got it?" Han Xiao stood in front of Lothaire with arms behind his back and reprimanded him.

"Won't happen again." Lothaire's response was short and simple.

Han Xiao grunted, paused, and said, "The impact of this assassination was extremely severe. The Modo Civilization has given up on the Flickering War and is focusing on internal affairs. They definitely will not let this go easily. Therefore, all activities of the Assassin's Society will cease for the time being. Hide and wait for this to be over. Only then will I allow you guys to be active again."

"How long?"

"A few decades. You have to make use of this time properly to train," Han Xiao said.

"Okay." Lothaire did not complain and calmly obeyed.

He had acquired some new experience from this assassination. He was just thinking about digesting them too.

Assassinating the leader of an advanced civilization was undoubtedly a legendary accomplishment. It had brought him subtle changes. It was like some kind of ability that increased his possibility of reaching Beyond Grade A. However, since Lothaire did not have the interface, he could not fully understand all that. He only got a blurry feel of it.

After giving him advice for a bit longer, Han Xiao ended the communication. His deliberately serious expression relaxed, and a smile appeared on his face.

This assassination that Lothaire had never informed him till it was done really startled him, but the results turned out to be extremely good. As the Modo Civilization had withdrawn its army, the second requirement of [Kunde Race Leader's Last Wish] was now complete.

If not for Lothaire's assassination, the Modo upper echelons would not have shifted this drastically. In that case, he would have had to spend more time and pay a heftier price in order to force Modo to retreat. Furthermore, the chain of chaotic reactions caused by Modo's leader being assassinated were also counted in the mission progress.

Although Lothaire made this decision without consulting him, the results turned out to be reliable. Han Xiao always had high hopes for Lothaire. In his eyes, Lothaire had the potential to become a Beyond Grade A. His potential was much higher than lazy Beyond Grade A seeds like Hadavy.

One reason he froze the activity of the Assassin's Society was to wait till this was over, but another was to give Lothaire more time to find the opportunity for Promotion.

Han Xiao put these things in the back of his mind, opened the mission list on the interface, and looked at the two bright gold missions.

Both [Escape] and [Kunde Race Leader's Last Wish]'s rewards could now be obtained. One of the two requirements of the latter was already complete. He could acquire [The Enemy], [Proof of Leadership], and [Kunde Rage] if he wanted.

Han Xiao thought about it and suppressed his temptation to complete [Kunde Race Leader's Last Wish], as the first mission requirement was to 'provide protection when the Kunde Race is being culturally modified', which was not complete yet.

This Grade S mission was a single mission, not a chain mission. Therefore, once he clicked on completing it and accepted the reward, it would mean that he would not be able to obtain the reward for the first requirement. He wanted the four Political Assets rewarded by the first requirement. Anyway, he could decide when to conclude the mission. He could obtain the three abilities anytime he wanted, so he was in no hurry.

"I shall conclude Lothaire's mission and get the reward first."

Han Xiao headed out, turned left into the officer lounge to get some luck, returned, and quickly opened the interface.

[Escape] Completed!

-3,000 Modo Civilization Favorability.

Current Relationship: [Archenemy]

You have received 8 Billion EXP, 2 Random Rewards, and the [Civilization Leader Slayer] milestone.

[Civilization Leader Slayer]: All civilization leader Favorability -10. Your words will be more heeded by the various civilizations. At the same time, when you, your organization, or your allies fight any fleets or Supers of your opposing civilization, their defense and various resistances will be reduced by 3% – 7%.

"This Milestone is definitely for the wanted criminals of the evil factions." Han Xiao's eyes twitched.

To wanted criminals, the Favorability of civilization leaders is complete trash, but since I'm someone with a high position and identity, the Favorability of civilization leaders is not useless.

However, he did not care about it too much. The only advanced civilization leader who had a good relationship with him was Urranrell. His Favorability with the federation's president and the church's pope were both negative, yet they were still working together. As long as there were enough profits, the personal Favorability of the leaders was barely impactful.

Furthermore, the value of that -10 Favorability of the civilization leaders was completely meaningless compared to the other effects of the milestone. Although the numbers were not high, the influence it had was extremely absurd. It worked against entire civilizations, reducing the various resistance and defense of all members of the opposing civilization.

Han Xiao instantly knew that when fighting the World Tree Civilization, this ability would give the entire explored universe a natural edge!

Comparatively, that slight reduction in Favorability was negligible.

"I sacrificed my Favorability for the entire universe. What a great man I am."

Han Xiao was almost touched by himself.

He focused and continued looking at the ability/talent drawing interface.

You have received the reward: draw one of Lothaire's skills (Ability/Talent).

Note: Lothaire is a Pugilist. Parts of the abilities/talents are adjusted according to your class.

Randomizing… Complete!

Please select one from the five options below as the reward:

[Stealth Master] Talent: Drastically reduce your presence to others, drastically reduce the chance of the enemies discovering you, and drastically reduce the clues you leave behind. You can easily find all the factors in a certain area that might lead to you being discovered, including but not limited to all kinds of surveillance devices and detection spells.

[Assassination Mark] Ability: Mark a target, increase the damage of your next attack to the target by 75%–100%, Critical Rate by 45%, and Critical Damage by 100%. Energy Cost: 150. Cooldown: 48s.

[One-Hit KO] Ability: When your next attack hits the target successfully, instantly carry out Lethal Judgement once. The base of the Judgement is the target's Health, END, Lethal Resistance, LUK, and the level difference between you and the target. If the Judgement succeeds, the target will die instantly. If the Judgement fails, the attack will deal an extra 280% damage. Energy Cost: 500. Cooldown: 1,200s.

[The Way of an Assassin] Ability: Charge energy into the next attack, accumulating extra damage bonuses. Energy to damage bonus Conversion Rate: 10:1%. Maximum damage bonus: 300%. Cooldown: 150s.

[Fearless Heart] Talent: When fighting a strong enemy, you will receive extra attack bonuses. When the enemy is below Grade B, this ability will not be triggered; when the enemy is Grade B, you will receive a 5% base attack bonus; when the enemy is Grade A, you will receive a 15% base attack bonus; when the enemy is Grade S, you will receive a 25% base attack bonus; when the enemy is Grade S+, you will receive a 35% base attack bonus; when the enemy is Grade SS, you will receive a 45% base attack bonus.

Woah! This kid! Han Xiao's eyes gleamed. What's a master assassin? This is a master assassin!

Lothaire had not been around for many years. It had been a very long time since Han Xiao last looked at his interface. He could recall that of these five options, other than the second option, Lothaire did not have any others back then.

Looks like this kid has been busy the past twenty years, he's got many new skills.

Han Xiao was overjoyed.

Such an excellent learning ability could almost match up to Nero. He had found a treasure.

He browsed through the options. No way he was going to pick the second or the third options. Although the Lethal Judgement of [One-Hit KO] was quite tempting, as soon as Han Xiao saw that Luck was one of the things considered for the Judgement, he instantly eliminated this option.

The fourth option, [The Way of an Assassin], was quite powerful, but Han Xiao also eliminated it after some pondering. This ability could only provide bonuses for one attack, but attack frequency was what Mechanics focused on. Although the [Charge—Endless Potential] he had obtained from Silver Shadow could work together with this ability, it was too situational. There would not be many chances to use it.

Han Xiao mainly hesitated between the first and the fifth option. [Stealth Master] was a functional talent that would dramatically enhance his stealth ability. It would be tremendously useful for spy operations, infiltration, stealing intelligence, and so on. Although it would not directly increase his strength, it would provide him with other forms of support.

However, [Fearless Heart]'s bonuses were way too good!

This did not just enhance one attack, but it was a passive bonus. Every single attack from him and his mechanical army could enjoy the bonus!

Furthermore, the bonus was on top of base attacks, meaning the percentage increase could be seen as the increase in the actual damage dealt!

"The only ones who are qualified to fight me now are all peak Beyond Grade As. This talent is perfect for people like me!"

Han Xiao felt exhilarated.

To Lothaire, the bonuses of [Fearless Heart] beyond the third level were all useless, since there was no way he could defeat a Beyond Grade A now. Only Beyond Grade As could fully utilize the power of this talent.

After pondering for about ten seconds, the desire to deal more damage won in the end. Han Xiao had made his choice.

You have received the talent [Fearless Heart]!

"Nice." Han Xiao took a deep breath. He felt a wave of heat that released from his brain that quickly flowed through his body.

After sensing it for a while, his expression became strange. He suddenly connected all the dots.

This talent was faithful to its name, it gave him a strong sense of confidence. Han Xiao noticed that more than half of his fear toward the strong had disappeared, replaced by disdain.

Manison? Fragile little sh*t, fight him!

The three Universal Civilizations? Piece of cake, fight them!

The World Tree Civilization? What is that? Fight them!

Anyone that appeared in his mind, he wanted to fight. His heart was filled with an indomitable sense of fearlessness, an illusion as if he could just beat up everything in the world.

He hastily suppressed this emotion, took a few deep breaths, and finally calmed himself down. It all made sense now.

"No wonder Lothaire dared assassinate the Modo Three Kings. Turns out it's the side effect of this talent. The mystery is now solved…"

Han Xiao rolled his eyes.

What Fearless Heart? Bullsh*t, this is clearly Reckless Heart!

Chapter 1185: National War

[Fearless Heart] was undoubtedly a semi-Molding Talent level talent. This was a surprise for Han Xiao.

He turned off the interface and contemplated what to do next.

"Modo is already disqualified. The second requirement of the Kunde Race mission is complete. As long as Modo doesn't come to mess with me, I won't need to fight them in the future… Once they retreat, I won't have an excuse to take part in the Flickering War anymore. I'll have to temporarily exit this stage. The army players might have problems with that… but luckily, now is already the final stage of the version. The impact won't be too huge."

Without Modo as an opponent, the Black Star Army no longer had a reason to continue participating in the Flickering World. This way, the army players would have to exit this main storyline too. If this had happened in the middle or even early stage of the version, the army players would have been in an uproar. Some of the newbies would most likely have changed factions to join the first World Server war.

However, Modo retreated at just the right time. It was now near the end of the version, meaning there was not much time left for the players to do things. Most of their energy was focused on preparing for the fourth season of the Pro League and the World Server War that was about to happen. These were the last two big things they could do near the end of the Version 4.0.

Losing the Flickering War main storyline in this situation would minimize the players' dissatisfaction. Furthermore, Han Xiao had faked a main storyline mission, which the players would receive reward from, making up for the loss of the players not being able to participate in the real main storyline mission to a certain extent.

Due to the existence of the Black Star Army, the state and territory distribution of the various guild alliances in the Flickering World was completely different from Han Xiao's previous life. Furthermore, this difference would extend all the way to the versions in the future. Even Han Xiao could not really predict what would become of these guild alliances in the future.

Han Xiao pondered for a while. When he realized that there were no more big things he had to do at the end of the version, he breathed a sigh of relief.

"What needs to be done has been done. What's left is to watch things develop like the other Beyond Grade As and wait for the Flickering War to come to a result…"

Han Xiao decided to lie low for some time and develop his technology, spending the remaining time of Version 4.0 peacefully. Furthermore, the army had attracted way too much attention recently. Nothing was good in excess, so it was a good time to cool down and temporarily stay out of the public eye.

"Now I just have to wait for the World Server War and the Pro League to suck out the players' savings for me to have enough EXP for Promotion."

Han Xiao smiled. He did not even have to come up with any promotional events. These two events were like automatic harvesting machines, convenient and effortless.

…

The Modo Civilization did not openly announce their retreat. They focused on promoting their plan to attack the terrorist organizations while quietly withdrawing the expeditionary army bit by bit.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance was an organization with shared interests, after all. Although Modo gave up on the Flickering War, they could not just walk away. As the Modo expeditionary army retreated, the other Super Star Cluster civilizations sent out some of their troops to form mixed fleets and took over this line of defense.

The Super Star Cluster Alliance was glad to see Modo exit. This way, their nightmare Black Star would be gone too. This was a completely beneficial trade in their eyes. Although the other Super Star Cluster civilizations were harsh in the things they said, they were still in the same alliance. They achieved some kind of deal with Modo and signed some agreements as compensation for Modo's exit.

As the main enemy fled, the Black Star Army's troops stopped attacking the Super Star Cluster Alliance's line of defense and left the Ferdinand Battle Zone in batches. The forged mission [Black Star Army Expedition Order] concluded, giving the army players a wave of rich rewards.

Although the rewards were set by Han Xiao and slightly worse than the real main storyline, it had its pros. The players would only be able to conclude the real Flickering War main storyline mission after the war ended, meaning only in the next version. On the other hand, the fake main storyline mission Han Xiao had made could be concluded now, meaning the players would receive the reward before the version ended.

These rewards gave the army players more resources to level up abilities, purchase equipment, and so on to increase their strength. The most direct benefit was that this would help players in the World Server War and the Pro League that was about to come.

Just as Han Xiao expected, exiting the main storyline in advance did not trouble the players. If the war against Modo was still carrying on, this would cause ordering the players very difficult for the army. Now that he had basically given the players a holiday, they could fully focus on the World Server War.

Planet Milton was a desolate planet located in the exterior parts of the Emerald Star Cluster. Over the past few months, batches of fleets with symbols of different guild alliances had been arriving there, building bases, fortresses, and lines of defenses on this planet.

Many of these guild alliances were enemies with each other, but all of them silently agreed on ignoring each other and constructed their strongholds peacefully.

The reason that this happened was one of the rules stated inside the invitation letter that before the designated date to start the war arrived, all professional guilds and player alliances that had arrived on Planet Milton could construct as many strongholds as they wanted, but attacking each other was not allowed. Anyone who disobeyed the rules would be kicked out of this war.

This was like a 'protected period', basically the preparation stage for all the guild alliances that were participating, as well the time given to all the players to get there.

Therefore, in the past few months, these guilds had been sending one batch of spaceships there after another, transporting tons of resources and constructing many temporary strongholds. The locations they chose to build strongholds were anything but random; some guild alliances had teamed up with others, and their strongholds had to be built close to one another so that they could help each other.

Since fighting before the official date was not allowed, fighting for the locations to build their strongholds was also forbidden. It worked on a first come first served basis. Therefore, the invisible war started during the preparation stage when they were constructing the strongholds. Choosing the location of the strongholds was like playing chess; not only did they have to be close to their allies' strongholds, but they also had to disrupt the enemy guild alliances' stronghold formations.

As of now, about seventy percent of all the players in Galaxy had arrived. The unpopulated Planet Milton became exceptionally boisterous.

…

In Golden Alliance Base No.1, the upper echelons of the four biggest Chinese guilds and various top tier Chinese guilds gathered in one place.

In the middle of the room was a 3D projection of Planet Milton. The surface was divided into areas with different colors, representing the territories of different guild alliances.

The Golden Alliance was the guild alliance the Chinese profession clubs took the lead in founding. It basically included all the top tier Chinese guilds. The Golden Alliance could be seen as the representatives of the Chinese players; almost all the members were army players.

The term 'army players' was just a general term. It was not an official guild alliance and also had different factions. Some foreign players who only joined the army in Version 4.0 formed different guild alliances. Being in the same faction was a link that made these guild alliances natural allies.

Usually, these guild alliances could be seen as a whole, generally called the 'army players'. However, when it comes to the national war, they still need to be classified separately.

The various guild alliances that gathered on Planet Milton could be roughly split into four Factions—the Black Star Army Faction led by the Golden Alliance, the Anti-Black Star Faction led by the Galactic Business Alliance, the Three Universal Civilizations Faction led by the September Conference, and the remaining scattered forces mainly consisting of the guilds from other Beyond Grade A organizations and neutral organizations. They fought for their own and had no leader.

Morning Snow Twilight Frost stood beside the projection, gestured with his hands, and said casually, "… As everyone can see, the Galactic Business Alliance, Northern Battlefront, 5C Alliance, and so on have always targeted us. They've set up their strongholds around every one of our strongholds, preventing us from expanding the base, clearly planning to surround us as soon as the war starts."

He was the president of the Dynasty Club's official guild, also the first president of the Golden Alliance.

The president of the Temple of God, Jupiter, crossed his legs and said with disdain, "Ha, are these Europeans playing chess? Don't they know who invented chess?"

"Our allies are responding too. Some arrived at the locations in advance, so the enemies won't be able to surround us. Some built strongholds at important strategic locations. It won't be that easy for the enemies to mess with us," the president of the Jade Green Sky said slowly.

The guild alliances of the Black Star Army Faction had made an agreement to follow the lead of the Golden Alliance and fight together. Other than the guild alliances of the Black Star Army Faction, the Golden Alliance also received help from elsewhere, the enemies of their enemies. The enemy's enemy might not be their friend, but at least there was room for them to work together.

"In terms of supplies, fleets, and weapons, we have the upper hand. The bulk purchased Evolutionary Badges are also given out, forming close to two hundred demolition divisions of eight hundred members each. In attacking strongholds, they'll destroy the enemies with the aid of airstrikes very quickly," a guild president said excitedly.

Fleets and all kinds of war machines were allowed in this war, but no Planetary Obliteration level weapons were permitted. However, the weapons used had to be bought. This war was a pure battle between the players; getting help from NPCs was clearly forbidden.

The various large guild alliances hosted this battle mainly to create exposure. The national war aligned with the various clubs' interests. As long as they could achieve outstanding results in the war or even become the final winners, their guilds would be able to attract more ordinary players, gain more fame, and earn through traffic. This was the goal of professional clubs.

As for the winning condition, it was very simple. There were mainly two ways. One was to destroy all of the enemy's strongholds on Planet Milton. After the battle started, the guild alliances would still be able to continue building more strongholds, but the others would be allowed to attack them.

Another way was to deplete the opposing guild members' revival times in the week. The players could revive ten times in six days at most on one account, and in such a highly intense war with hundreds of millions of players participating, the frequency of the players dying would become strikingly high.

Morning Snow Twilight Frost nodded, turned to the many professional players who were listening on the side, and asked, "How's the challenge going?"

King Admiral said lazily, "More wins than losses. I forgot the exact numbers."

Bun-Hit-Dog instantly gave a thumbs up with a grin. "No worries, I remember. We're now at 3,488 wins, 1,142 losses. The win rate is about 75%. It's glorious!"

The rules stated that the guilds could not fight each other, but since so many players had gathered there, clearly some would get too bored. Duels were not forbidden, so PVP matches could be seen everywhere.

Due to this, the various large guild alliances sent out many PVP experts to challenge players of the other guilds. If they won, the other guild's morale would be affected.

The results of these duels needed to be promoted to increase the popularity of the guild, so professional reports were needed. Hence, Bun-Hit-Dog, who was a celebrity, was hired by the Golden Alliance as the chief reporter to lead the entire battlefield reporters group, personally in charge of writing the battle reports of the Golden Alliance.

Such a large-scale national war had players in all kinds of industries participating such as PVP experts, logistics players, management personnel, reporters, and so on. They all had their own job to do. It was a festival.

…

As the date for the start of the war approached, the atmosphere on Planet Milton became more and more heavy. A storm was coming.

The players were not the only ones who paid attention to this war. Even the other organizations paid attention to this war between the Immortals.

The three Universal Civilizations, Super Star Cluster civilizations, and the other organizations got some information from the players. Although they were surprised by the special hostility between the Immortals, they all did not disrupt them, only observed them, quietly recording the specialties of Immortals.

If the Black Star Army Faction won his war, Han Xiao would benefit from it too. His faction would be more appealing to the new players. However, he did not plan to interfere. He did not want to ruin this signature event that would certainly be written into the Galaxy Chronicles. He only wanted to stay at home and watch the show while eating some popcorn.

Time passed. Under the eyes of countless people, the day of the national war finally arrived!

Chapter 1186: The Tears Pugilists Are Shedding Are All the Water Damage Their Brains Suffered When They Choose Their Class

Despite constructing many strongholds on Planet Milton, all the big guild alliances had a main base, usually the first stronghold they built. It had no difference from the other strongholds in terms of rules, but to the players, it was a symbol, like the main city.

Dragon Hill was a large hill that surrounded the Golden Alliance's main base. It originally had no name. The name Dragon Hill was given by the Golden Alliance after they occupied this place.

On the day of the beginning of the war, hundreds of battlefields of varying sizes appeared on Planet Milton. Most were between strongholds. Among all these battlefields, Dragon Hill attracted the most attention. This was because the Anti-Black Star Faction had placed their main forces there, planning to get rid of the Golden Alliance's main base on the first day of the war. The Golden Alliance, too, placed their main forces there and prepared for it. They had decided to fight head-on.

Almost ten million players from both factions gathered on Dragon Hill, looking forward to the battle. The countless troops turned this hill into a colorful sea. Teams of players kept shifting locations like tides on the sea.

The mixed colors came from the troops of the Anti-Black Star Faction, as they wore very different equipment. As for the Golden Alliance, they were wearing the army's standard mechanical suits, which were black and silver. It was very neat. The Golden Alliance looked like a huge official army, unlike the Anti-Black Star Faction, which looked like a mere mix of small forces.

The people of the Galactic Business Alliance and other guilds were stationed at the south, east, and west sides, planning to attack from all three directions. The Golden Alliance troops' formation was circular, wrapped around the main base. The formations of two sides were separated by a wide belt area.

Inside the strategy surveillance room, the 3D satellite map hovered in the middle.

Morning Snow Twilight Frost, who took the position as the main commander of the battle, stared closely at the map, giving out orders one after another. The dozen military strategists around him occasionally gave suggestions, while the group of assistants sent the orders down.

For such a large battle, fighting without an overall strategy would spell certain defeat, so the commanding system was very crucial.

To prevent electromagnetic or virtual technology disruptions that might prevent the frontlines from receiving orders, both sides chose to use the chat system in the interface as the channel to give out orders.

The main commander looked over the entire battle and analyzed the situation with the military strategists. The orders would then be passed down by the messengers in the command room to the various high commanders. The high commanders would then swiftly adjust the detailed strategy based on the orders and the situation of the frontlines before giving orders to the intermediate commanders under them. The intermediate commanders would then pass the order down to the team captains at the frontlines, who would then communicate with their team members in the team channel and execute the orders.

On both sides, there were as many as more than a hundred thousand commanders, the majority being the team captains.

This procedure looked complicated, but because the chat system was not restricted by distance and everyone did their job properly, it was very efficient.

If all the players made up a body, the main commanders and the high commanders would be the brain giving the orders, and the intermediate commanders and the team captains would be the nervous system responsible for controlling the body based on the orders the brain gave.

Morning Snow Twilight Frost gave a round of orders. Seeing that the troops on his side were all almost in place, he exhaled softly, turned to Jade Green Sky, who was one of the military strategists and asked, "… The setup is about complete. How much time till the war starts?"

"Six minutes and eleven seconds."

"It's about time. Tell all teams to preheat their weapons. Activate the shields of the base and the frontlines too. At the three-minute mark, have the enchantment Mages start applying buffs and the rest start consuming whatever combat capability enhancement potions they have."

The order was quickly passed down. A thick, light-blue energy shield rose around the main base and shrouded it.

The defense Mage teams at the frontlines started to apply shields and enchanting spells on the other teams around very soon. The Pugilist teams who would be leading the charge also started to inject enhancement potions. These bonuses all had a time limit, so using it right before the start of the war would maximize the effects.

The Anti-Black Star Faction's men were doing the same thing. Colorful lights appeared on both sides like a fireworks competition.

Seconds felt like years in the last three minutes. All the players present were exhilarated and nervous. They held their breath, focused, and waited for the war to start. The atmosphere of the battlefield was silent and intense.

As the countdown continued, it finally reached zero.

"Go!"

At that instant, the earth started trembling!

The battlefield that was silent just seconds ago was suddenly filled with roars and battle cries. The battle erupted instantly!

The two stationary seas suddenly turned into raging tsunamis, charging at each other!

Countless energy beams formed an enormous net on the empty area between the two sides. Tons of players fell during the charge from the opponent's long ranged attacks. The black and the mixed colored tides quickly closed in on each other and clashed!

Boom boom boom boom!

Chains of explosions left cracks and pits on the ground. Dragon Hill swiftly became a mess.

The charging teams of both sides collapsed in large areas. In just an instant, countless mechanical soldiers, Pugilists, and melee-ranged Esper players died on the spot. It was a bloodbath!

This was not a stage for any one person. No matter how strong a player was, once they got out of the main formation, they would be killed in an instant. Carrying out their individual duties in groups was the only choice.

"Area C5 and D2, target their Psychic teams! Their AOE is too strong. The shield durability is almost at the warning line!"

"Defense Mages, keep giving the Pugilists enhancing spells. Throw fire or poison spells or whatever you have toward the enemies! Trap experts, stop f*cking throwing spells and keep planting traps! Summoners, get your babies out quicker… Where's the attack Mage team of Area B2? Don't fall out of formation!"

"Area A1, A4, B2, B6, C1, and D1 Mechanics, quickly disassemble the traps. D9's artillery is broken. Go repair it. Army Style and Mechanical Pugilists, keep advancing. Cannon Masters, don't stop attacking. Target their Psychics and Mages. Virtual Mechanics, handle their fleets. Armed and Energy Mechanics, bring out your heavy weapons and continue to fire. Target their Pugilists!"

"Psychics, focus on their Mechanics. Remember to save your mana… Nice! Someone landed a Super Critical Hit! A ton of enemies have just died!"

"Espers who are not melee types, don't rush forward. Stay behind, and step back to recover your mana when you're out… Didn't I f*cking tell you not to rush forward? That's the job of Pugilists! Why the f*ck are you fighting for it‽"

"Area C2 Pugilists, try to die slower! Get back to the frontlines after reviving. What are you waiting for‽"

The battle entered the climax instantly. The chat channels were filled with energy, and the commanders were yelling at the top of their lungs.

The players of the five classes all had their job to do. Psychics were responsible for AOE attacks and applying debuffs. Espers and Mages were responsible for whatever their ability was or what they excelled at.

The Pugilists were the most tragic, they could only lay down their bodies at the frontlines for the rest to advance. The Pugilists were strong and incredible in the early versions, now they were weak and helpless. How the tables turn.

After all, Pugilist was a civilian class, the pros of it were that it was easy to play, the fighting style was cool, and it was not bad in duels.

However, in large battlefields like this, everyone was targeting Pugilists, hoping to deplete their revival times so that their opponent would lose the teams who were leading the charge. In situations like this, the Pugilists' death rate was far higher than the other four classes. Even the term 'cool' was lost on them. They were basically competing on who could die in a flashier way.

Furthermore, Pugilists did not have any other choices. No one would want them even if they wanted to do construction work in the logistics department; their efficiency was far lower than all kinds of mechanical devices.

At this time, the thoughts in the various Pugilist players' minds were shockingly similar.

F*cking hell, how am I supposed to play this class‽

Comparatively, Mechanics who were weak in the early stages were shining brightly in battles. They were the busiest in the battlefield. They could fight, manage logistics, charge forward, deal both single target and AOE damage, repair, and produce. They were irreplaceable.

Due to how strategically crucial the Mechanics were, the Golden Alliance had an edge. Because of their faction, the most elite Mechanics among the players were all in the Black Star Army. Basically all of them were members of the Golden Alliance.

As the battle carried on, the situation started shifting—the Golden Alliance gained the upper hand, and it was expanding.

The top tier professional players all had the privilege of getting resources poured onto them by their clubs, so the difference between them was not too obvious. However, in terms of overall strength of the players, the Golden Alliance surpassed the Anti-Black Star Faction.

The Black Star Army had united the Chinese players long ago, saving the players the cost of continuously changing factions. Furthermore, there were all kinds of faction privileges from time to time. Their growth was much more organized than the 'wild' players who had been in many different factions in the past versions.

After close to four versions, the Golden Alliance players were clearly superior in terms of abilities and equipment overall.

Furthermore, the fake main storyline Han Xiao concluded in advance gave the army players another wave of funds and EXP. One or two players receiving it would not make a difference, but tens of millions of players all received the reward. When that materialized in this battlefield, it increased their edge even further.

"The casualty count statistics are out!"

Inside the main base's command room, Morning Snow Twilight Frost was giving out orders when he received a set of smart statistics. His eyes gleamed.

"The enemies died 0.742 times on average. For our side, it's 0.631 times. Wonderful!"

The people present were overjoyed.

This data represented the average deaths per player on both sides. Though the difference was only 0.111, in this battle of tens of millions of players, this meant that the players on their side died about five hundred thousand times less than the opponents!

"The revive limit is only ten every six days. Finishing those revives means you're out. Today is the first day of the war, so their bottom line is probably between 1.8 to 2.2. Their charging team has died more times than the average at almost 1.2. They'll soon be unable to hold on!"

Morning Snow Twilight Frost narrowed his eyes and said, "Send in fifty demolition divisions. Advance at my command!"

As they were not fighting NPCs, both sides did not use large-scale suicidal attacks. Everyone could revive multiple times, and if used wrongly, they might lose more than they had to gain instead.

The Golden Alliance had piled up a ton of Evolution Badges when preparing for the war. Fifty demolition divisions meant forty thousand players, which was about a 0.01 increase in the overall average death count after conversion. They now had an enormous edge, so they could totally take the risk. The goal was not to kill more enemies but to make use of the tankiness and the high melee damage bonus of the Aberrations to break the opponent's formation.

As the order was passed down, a special team was escorted into the frontlines. With countless flashes of light, their bodies expanded into Aberrations one after another and charged into the enemy formation, unstoppable like a hot knife cutting through butter!

A total of forty thousand monsters with multiple buffs charged into the enemy's formation, instantly creating areas of enemy Pugilist players that were separated from the rest. The attacks from the Golden Alliance followed right after and wiped them out on the spot.

The violence of the Evolution Badge was recognized by all the players. The advance of forty thousand Aberrations messed up the Anti-Black Star Faction's command system for a while.

They spent quite a lot of time before killing all these Aberrations. The chaos had caused the Anti-Black Star Faction's average death count to increase by 0.018, meaning about a hundred thousand players died. The difference between two sides was getting bigger, especially among the Pugilist teams.

"We can win!"

The morale of the Golden Alliance players in the frontlines rocketed. The players of the Galactic Business Alliance were clearly not as energetic.

Battles between large armies would not be turned around easily. As soon as one side had the upper hand, the remaining battle would just be the process of snowballing.

The situation continuously became better for the Golden Alliance and worse for the other side. The results of the battle were gradually growing certain.

…

While the battle on Dragon Hill was going on fiercely, Han Xiao, who was far away in Black Star Palace, was holding a bag of popcorn in his one hand and a drink in the other, watching the broadcast from Bun-Hit-Dog on the forums.

However, his focus was not the situation of the battle…

"Nice, nice, using forty thousand Evolution Badges at once. Charging these Evolution Badges is going to get me a wave of EXP again. Keep using them."

"Haha, hundreds more mechanical teams are destroyed. More repair fees."

Han Xiao was joyous. He did not feel heartache about the battle damage the Golden Alliance was suffering at all. He was practically laughing.

In his eyes, every batch of resources the Golden Alliance lost meant a new round of sales for him. If not because the faction benefits could not be given out randomly, he would even sell to the Anti-Black Star Faction.

"War is still the most profitable!" Han Xiao grinned.

At this point, he felt like he was a shameless strategist reclaiming the resources he gave out from the players in all kinds of ways.

After all, the players would only be motivated to create more value when their hard-earned resources were emptied.

Chapter 1187: Black Star, I Have Mastered Your Ways!

The Dragon Hill battle was like a signal. Flames of war erupted everywhere on Planet Milton in the next two days. The bloodshed of the guild alliance players was never-ending. Battles happened on hundreds of battlefields across many strongholds every moment. It was as if Planet Milton was being bombarded continuously for two days. The surface was completely wrecked by the hundreds of millions of players.

The forums were basically filled with only two types of posts, the ones that kindly greeted the families of the opposing players and the battle reports of the various battlefield reporters.

As there were way too many battles going on across the various battlefields at the same time, even Han Xiao could not follow all of them. He only watched the Golden Alliance's performance on the first day, saw that the Golden Alliance had emerged victorious in the Dragon Hill battle, and stopped paying close attention. He only looked at Bun-Hit-Dog and the Galaxy Times' reports once every few hours to get an idea of the overall situation of the World Server War.

In general, the Golden Alliance had the biggest advantage. The guild alliances such as the Galactic Business Alliance suffered large losses on the first day, so they clearly became much more cautious.

As for the Three Universal Civilizations Faction led by the Golden Alliance and the September Conference, they did not organize any large-scale battles, only smaller partial battles. Instead, the scattered neutral factions were the ones that had fought most intensely so far.

The scattered neutral factions had the most players. Many smaller guilds formed small alliances. Not only were they fiercely fighting each other, but some daring players even formed teams and attacked the strongholds of the big factions such as the Black Star Army Factions. Most of them were defeated, but a small percentage of them managed to take over some strongholds from the three mainstream factions.

In similar events, cleaning up the scattered players was normally the first thing that needed to be done. However, that was not the case here. The war was extremely brutal, and the revival count that basically no players cared about usually now became the most crucial resource.

The three mainstream factions had the ability to eliminate any scattered factions they wanted, but doing that without taking at least some damage was impossible. The players were fearless and would never give up resisting. Even the three mainstream factions would certainly incur some losses. To them, using the crucial revival counts on these scattered players was an utter waste.

Furthermore, attempting to cleanse the scattered players on a large scale would most likely cause them to unite and fight back. By then, they would have shot themselves in the foot and gotten trounced by the scattered players.

Although the rules did not state a time limit, everyone had an unspoken agreement to decide the results of the war in six days. Otherwise, their revival count would refresh again by then, which would be extremely costly for the guild alliances.

Although the players could revive again, their resources would undoubtedly deplete as time went on. If they were to fight another round, the inventory of the guild alliances would suffer tremendously. Furthermore, normal players would not be willing to go through the death penalty too many times.

In his exclusive workshop in Black Star Palace, Han Xiao stored away a newly built King mechanical suit, casually opened the forums, and browsed through the battle reports for today.

'Golden Alliance 8 Hours Report: Continued Increase in Win Probability' - By Bun-Hit-Dog: "The Golden Alliance has carried out forty-one battles in the past eight hours, four are million level battles, eleven are five hundred thousand level partial battles, twenty-two are a hundred thousand level partial battles, and four small group battles. No ten million level battles. Of them, the Golden Alliance won twenty-nine and lost twelve, winning 70.73% of the battles, a 3.16% increase compared to yesterday. The overall average death count increased from 2.375 to 2.814, maintaining at the top of the average survival leaderboards, further increasing their lead over the second in place. The difference now has already reached 0.703!"

'Flying Stone Cliff Quick Report' - By Galaxy Times (Chinese Zone): "Today, the Galactic Business Alliance and the Northern Battlefront's stronghold in Haywood Valley was assaulted by the September Council and Denland. As their teleportation arrays were disrupted, the Galactic Business Alliance and the Northern Battlefront dispatched the closest forces to travel to the Haywood Valley stronghold as reinforcements. However, when they passed by Flying Stone Cliff, they fell into the Golden Alliance's ambush and suffered heavy losses. According to reliable sources, the Golden Alliance secretly dispatched a team there and had them log off. By logging in at the Flying Stone Cliff, they took the enemies by complete surprise, achieving a huge victory!"

There were many similar reports, Han Xiao scanned through them with a smile to see which guild alliances were eliminated for about half an hour before exiting the forums.

Beep beep beep!

At this time, his communicator rang. It was surprisingly the dynasty exploration army's Marshal, Brother Tarrokov.

Han Xiao accepted the communication and asked with a smile, "Yoho, Old Tar, what's up?"

"Have you been paying attention to the war between the Immortals?" Tarrokov's tone was serious.

"Hehe, I have a ton of Immortals under my command. How can I not pay attention? Come on, do you have to test me like this? Did the dynasty upper echelons send you?"

Han Xiao had a rough guess of what Tarrokov's intentions were.

"Hmm…" Tarrokov did not deny it and slowly said, "What I want to ask is, how much do you really know about the Immortals?"

"Be more specific."

"Alright… the Intelligence Department and the Dynasty Science Institute have never stopped observing the Immortals. One of the earliest batches of Immortals appeared on Planet Aquamarine, which were almost all recruited by you. You seem to have a very deep understanding of them. We'd like to know, why do the Immortals disappear every so often? Why does all of their strength increase after appearing again after they disappear? Does this strength increase of theirs have a limit? Can they really be fully controlled?"

A chain of questions was thrown at Han Xiao. He did not immediately respond. He felt the attitude change of the Crimson Dynasty.

The three Universal Civilizations had always been studying the Immortals, and now they finally came to him, who was an 'expert' in this matter on the surface. This was clearly because of the World Server War. It had made them take the Immortals even more seriously!

The nickname 'Cancer of the Universe' had existed for more than half of the version. The players had always been active in different events everywhere. Even though there was the Black Star Cup not long ago, that was just a competition. This time, however, was the first time the various organizations finally witnessed a large-scale battle only Immortals took part in.

The weapons and fleets they used were nothing extraordinary, nor was the scale as marvelous as the galactic battles. The only thing that was shocking was how fiercely the Supers fought. The Immortals from different factions had fought before too, but this time, it was much bloodier and more brutal.

The advanced civilizations were only shocked, but those smaller organizations were almost spooked!

So, this is what a war between the Cancers of the Universe is like. We still underestimated the violence of these people!

Thinking about the specialties the Immortals had shown in the past, the dynasty no longer had the leisure to slowly carry out their studies, so they approached Han Xiao, hoping to obtain more detailed information.

"I don't know them that well. You guys probably already know what I know…"

Of course, Han Xiao was not going to tell the entire truth. He casually said some things. Most was information the others could also obtain, nothing rare or new.

"Is that all you know?" Tarrokov was not convinced yet.

"What else? I was only able to find some patterns before others. I'm not an Immortal. How can I know everything?" Han Xiao joked.

"You're right…" Tarrokov nodded.

Actually, the Crimson Dynasty had suspected that Black Star was an Immortal decades ago.

However, no one had been able to kill him, so there was no way to know the truth.

Then, since Black Star did not disappear periodically like the Immortals, the dynasty had let go of this suspicion.

After Tarrokov was gone, Han Xiao wiped off the smile on his face and looked serious.

He opened the interface, looked at the EXP gauge, and made an estimate.

"At this rate of harvesting EXP, when this fight is over, I'll have more than enough EXP to complete the level 340 Promotion before the Pro League starts… Hmm, I can use the Evolution Cube again this time."

Han Xiao frowned slightly.

As the strength of the players increased, the state of the universe would become more and more chaotic. He would only be able to deal with all kinds of changes by becoming stronger as quickly as possible. By then, no matter how the advanced civilizations responded, he would be able to deal with it.

…

The players of the Limitless Financial Group were also part of the World Server War. They were one of the large forces among the scattered factions.

Sorokin was also paying attention to this battle, but not just to observe it—he had other plans.

"This seems like a good opportunity to attract Immortals…" Sorokin's eyes flickered.

He had always been passionate about recruiting the Immortals. Although he did not know the truth about the players, the path Han Xiao had taken gave him some ideas.

Sorokin had carefully studied the Black Star Army's history, especially the methods the Black Star Army used to attract the Immortals. By concluding what had happened in the past, he had found quite a lot of patterns.

By now, Sorokin felt like he had already mastered Black Star's methods.

"This war between so many Immortals is a good opportunity for the Limitless Financial Group to make a name for itself among the Immortals. If the Immortals of the Limitless Financial Group win in the end, it should attract more Immortals…"

Usually, the Limitless Financial Group Immortals did not have an edge. In order for them to win, he had to interfere. Anyway, he was not restrained by his reputation like the other Beyond Grade As. Even if word of him, a Beyond Grade A, shamelessly interfering with a war between Grade B supers got out, his reputation would not be affected because he never had one to begin with.

As a Beyond Grade A, even without using his full strength, he would be able to decide the results of battles at this level. Furthermore, his methods were extremely sneaky. He believed that these Grade B Immortals would not be able to discover them.

"Looks like this is worth a try. I shall do it…" Sorokin made up his mind.

His speculation actually made sense. However, he could not see the forums, so he lacked the most crucial piece of information… He had no idea the players were fighting, and more importantly, he was completely clueless about the fact that the rules forbade NPCs from interfering!

The players of the Limitless Financial Group did not dare break the rules. They had invested a ton of resources and worked hard trying to maintain the good results they had achieved.

What they would never have expected was that their own faction leader was preparing to get them instantly disqualified.

Chapter 1188: That's Not How the Script Was Written!

Within Mount Gold, a large base was embedded in the mountain, with the sky around it hovering with battleships and a team of mechanical guards, tightly guarding the area.

This was the main base of the Apocalypse Foundation, the largest guild alliance belonging to the Limitless Financial Group. Sixty to seventy percent of the mountain itself had been transformed into mechanical defense facilities, and relying on this main base, they had also cleaned up the surrounding small areas to continuously expand.

In the middle of the third day of battle, the Mount Gold stronghold sent three ace troops to conquer the Hex Armed Forces of the Wind Hunting Valley. This was another large guild alliance that occupied the area. The two of them had been fighting for regional supremacy.

The Hex Armed Forces had long detected that their enemies would attack and thus pulled out their troops. Both sides fought fiercely outside Wind Hunting Valley, neither side willing to extricate themselves.

Just as the fierce battle between the two were raging, another guild alliance called the Reverse Crusade launched a raid on the Mount Gold stronghold.

They had planned this for a long time and stationed their troops to hide and ambush the area a day and a half in advance. They had even erected a secret resurrection point in the area. Using the opportunity when the main forces of both sides were in battle, they attacked the relatively empty base camp of the Apocalypse Foundation, intending to steal the other's base.

The Apocalypse Foundation was at the disadvantage of fighting on two fronts. They actually intended to withdraw the troops attempting to conquer Wind Hunting Valley. However, the Hex Armed Forces seemed to have anticipated the emergence of the Reverse Crusade and entangled the main force of the Apocalypse Foundation, not allowing it to separate from them.

At this moment, the stronghold at Mount Gold had turned into another fierce battlefield. A large number of artillery battleship and combat machinery were fighting in the air, fireworks constantly dotting the sky, and the ground was full of players fighting in the hills and plains.

The Apocalypse Foundation had basically dispatched all their trump cards at this point and did not have many of their elites to guard their base. Most of the members in the base were their periphery members, and faced with the attack of the elites in the Reverse Crusade, they could only steadily retreat from the base.

A flood of unfavorable battle reports was sent back to the main command room of the stronghold, causing the leader of the Apocalypse Foundation, Sisyphus, to feel beleaguered.

"No wonder the Hex Armed Forces suddenly provoked us. It was all to lure us into falling into their trap! They're indeed devils!"

Sisyphus hurriedly contacted his Vice President, who had led the team to attack the Hex Armed Forces, through the guild channel.

"Quickly come back to reinforce us. This old man here can't hold them back for long!"

"Boss, we can't withdraw at all. The Hex Armed Forces are chasing us too closely. Unless we all die, there's no way for us to return. The average number of deaths in our main force has reached 5.14. If we go up by one more point, we'll be even more passive. Right now, even if we manage to go back, our ships and weapons will also be captured by the enemy!"

"We're already at this stage. If we lose a bit, it can't be helped. It's more important to protect our base!"

"We can't! The enemy has already made preparations in advance. If we all try to return via dying, then they'll definitely push the momentum to attack our home base, joining hands with the Reverse Crusade!"

Hearing this, Sisyphus frantically scratched his head.

As they had been caught off guard, the situation now was two against one, and the Apocalypse Foundation alone could not handle it. He could only ask for help from the other guild alliances that were on the Limitless Financial Group's front.

"I hope that our reinforcements can arrive in time. This time, I really suffered a huge loss…"

With a heavy heart, he refocused his eyes back to the real-time battlefield projection, but he froze on the spot.

"W-what is this situation?"

Turning to look at his members and commanders, he found that everyone had the same expression of shock, as though they had come across a ghost.

In the monitoring screen showing the frontal battlefield outside the Mount Gold stronghold, one of the squads of the Reverse Crusade had broken through the defense line and slammed into their troops.

"Instagib[1] them!"

The death squad prepared all their abilities, ready to collectively blast the whole lot of them.

At this moment, all their movement stopped, as the light on their bodies disappeared due to being interrupted.

Not only did it apply to the death squad, but all the Reverse Crusade players had the same reaction, as though the freeze button was pressed simultaneously for them. All their actions were halted, causing the troops to be instantly disconnected and the lineup torn.

On the interface of these players, the same notification appeared.

Sorokin (Manifestation) has used [Mind Shock] on you!

Judgment is in progress… Judgement successful. You cannot control your body for the time being.

Your skills are forcibly interrupted, and you have been afflicted with the [Stiffness] status.

In that instant, the situation went through a plot twist. The Reverse Crusade, which was originally beginning to see the light of victory, suddenly plummeted into the abyss, their psychological states suffering a great shock.

At this moment, there were only curses echoing in their heads.

You even called out a Beyond Grade A‽

This is cheating!

Are the guilds of the Limitless Financial Group such sore losers‽

The short [Stiffness] status condition turned the tides in an instant. The Apocalypse Foundation players did not stop, setting off a burst of explosions to take out a large portion of the players from the Reverse Crusade, reclaiming their battlefront.

The Apocalypse Foundation players were also in shock, not because of the sudden stop of the Reverse Crusade players, but rather because of a notification that they received on their interfaces.

Sorokin (Manifestation) has used [Spiritual Inspiration] on you!

You have entered the [Inspired] state. +10% all Attributes.

Sorokin (Manifestation) has used [Combat Excitement] on you!

+18% to Damage, +12% to Defense

"What's happening‽"

"Where did the bonuses come from? Did someone use a Character Summon Card?"

"That's not right. Even if the Character Summon Card is used, the name of the user won't be changed!"

The troops at the frontline could not understand it, but this was not the time to think. They hurriedly struck to kill the enemy instead.

Before long, most of the troops from Reverse Crusade had died. Everyone thought that this was a desperate situation but did not expect to solve the threat in such a manner.

Sisyphus had yet to recover his wits. At this time, a call came from his Vice President, his tone one of surprise.

"President! We beat the Hex Armed Forces! I don't know why, but their movements suddenly halted!"

"It can't be, right‽" Sisyphus hurriedly asked the various commanders, only then figuring out what had happened. He was bewildered.

What situation is this? Did Sorokin arrive? But we didn't call him! Why did he come to join in the fun?

Could it be that he saw us in danger and took the initiative to help?

Sisyphus' eyes widened. There was nothing on his face that represented the joy of making a successful counterattack.

In normal times, they might have been touched, but right now…

What business is it of yours? Your excessive worrying will be the death of us all!

…

The next day…

"Look at the iron hooves,

"Trampling across the myriad mountains and rivers,

"I'm standing on the edge of the wind,

"Holding tightly the rotation of the sun and moon."

Han Xiao hummed[2] while walking out the bathroom.

With only a towel wrapped around his waist, his toned, sturdy upper body was exposed, with the magic circuit on his chest akin to a glowing dark blue tattoo, flickering with each breath.

A pinnacle Beyond Grade A could basically forego rest, but Han Xiao had always attached importance to a combination of work and rest. In the past few days, he had created seven to eight sets of King mechanical suits, so he decided that he would not be doing any assembly today.

Without adjusting his body temperature to evaporate the water, he simply wiped his body dry before kicking back to swipe the forums.

The moment he entered the forum section, his expression turned weird.

"Apocalypse Foundation violated the rules, inviting Beyond Grade A helpers? Aren't they part of the Limitless Financial Group's guild alliances?"

Han Xiao entered the post and saw that the replies had gone into the tens of millions.

The content of the post was basically the Hex Armed Forces and the Reverse Crusade condemning the Apocalypse Foundation. After a day of fermenting, this incident had resulted in a storm within the player community. Countless players were filled with indignation and accused the Apocalypse Foundation of violating their rules.

"It's too much. We were actually going to win. I didn't expect that the Apocalypse Foundation would be such sore losers, hiring a faction leader and using this method to make a comeback. This is simply cheating!"

"There's a whole stack of videos and screenshots as evidence. Let's see how you explain this!"

"That's right! Yesterday, someone even tried to clean up the mess, saying that this was the effect of a Character Summon Card. My @ss! Since when was the Character Summon Card able to change the name of the person utilizing it?"

"Such acts that undermine fairness must be severely punished. I propose we cancel the qualification of the Apocalypse Foundation in participating in the war. Since you can't afford to lose, don't play!"

The forum was basically full of posts of annoyance. Han Xiao swept through it, seeing the announcement made by the Apocalypse Foundation as well.

"I'm the President of the Apocalypse Foundation Guild Alliance. Things are not what they seem. We did not ask Sorokin for help; he did it himself. This has nothing to do with us. Think about it, guys. We're clearly aware of the consequences of breaking the rules, so why would we purposely go against them!"

Sisyphus' post, in the face of the enraged group of players, was like a drop of water in a bucket. Not only was it not convincing, he was even ridiculed in return.

"Hehe, continue crafting this story."

"So, as it turns out, you can invite the Beyond Grade A to help first, then apologize later and absolve yourself of all blame. I've learned something today."

"What, do you think only your side has a Beyond Grade A? Who are you looking down on!"

"You wanna play this game? Men, someone go invite Ancestor Black Star over!"

Many of the players did not accept this statement, but the players on the side of the Limitless Financial Group sort of believed this to some extent. Suddenly, there was a mix of responses.

"It can't be, right? Sorokin, that old dog, was actually so nosy?"

"This is akin to a time bomb! When it comes to us, then wouldn't our qualifications to participate be cancelled too?"

"I'll meekly ask now. Is it still possible to change factions…"

"Level 180 Psychic, my core class skills are all lv.7 and above. Begging for a guild to accept me!"

Sorokin's actions completely scared off all the players from the Limitless Financial Group. In order to continue participating in the war, the players even wished to switch camps. They did not dare stay any longer in this organization that could backfire on them at any time.

After reading the post, Han Xiao finally figured out what was going on.

"The guilds shouldn't be lying, so this was likely done of Sorokin's own initiative. As for his goal… well, he has always been keen on recruiting players, so he probably summarized some rules from watching me and thought of how to increase the attractiveness of his faction."

After realizing the whole picture, Han Xiao guessed Sorokin's logic before bursting into laughter.

"So, it's like this… The idiot actually thought that his actions were completely concealed, just using some auxiliary mental abilities to make others think that this was an explosive ability of the Limitless Financial Group players or that they utilized some special spiritual weapon. Normally, they would not be able to link it to him… but the combat information has already betrayed you, you little cheater."

Han Xiao laughed.

Little Soro, ah, Little Soro, you shot yourself in the foot. When you use the wrong method, instead of lifting the prestige of your faction, you will cause a countereffect, giving you a bad reputation among the players.

The worst part about this was, the poor bloke could not even access the forums, so he was still in the dark, unaware that he had been scolded thoroughly by the players.

This is the advantage of information…

Sorokin's manipulation would no doubt result in some of the players of the Limitless Financial Group leaving. At that time, when the players were cold and lonely, he would use his warm chest to hug them, welcoming them into his faction.

Little So, it's not me who's snatching your leeks this time. You handed them to me yourself…

Han Xiao chuckled.

This feeling of earning something while sitting at home was pretty comfortable.

…

Since his intervention yesterday, Sorokin had been paying attention to the subsequent development, but he could not help but feel puzzled when he did not see the situation he expected.

Based on his reasoning, the Apocalypse Foundation had launched a successful counterattack with his help. The other Immortals would now be amazed by the strength of the Limitless Financial Group, so why did they not show any response?

It was not until the next day that he saw the Apocalypse Foundation reacting. It was not the pursuit of their victory as he expected but them abandoning their base and leaving the planet on a battleship.

"Strange, what's this reaction?"

In his office, Sorokin gazed at the live broadcast of the news media covering the front lines, and he frowned.

Just as he was feeling puzzled, Sorokin received a pop-up from his own artificial intelligence. One glance caused his heart to skip a beat.

He saw that the pop-up report was full of resignation notices from the Immortals, and this number was rapidly increasing.

"What's happening? Why are they resigning from the Limitless Financial group‽"

Sorokin had a stunned expression, and as if he had thought of something, he quickly turned back to the live broadcast.

He saw batches of Immortals belonging to the Limitless Financial Group flying out of the stronghold, scattering. Some went to the neutral factions, while others ran to the three mainstream factions, including the Black Star Army. There was no restriction on the operation of players to switch factions on the spot, so one could be beating someone up one day and turn into teammates the next day. This was all allowed in the rules.

The Limitless Financial Group, being a galactic consortium, did not pursue faction cohesion in the first place. Those who joined did so because of the high welfare provided, so there was no reluctance for them to switch factions. Now that the first World Server War was destined to be recorded in the Galaxy Chronicles, if they missed this opportunity, there would not be any reward left for them. In order to not be disqualified, the Limitless Financial Group did not hesitate to betray their faction.

"This…"

Seeing this, Sorokin was a little dizzy.

My methods were obviously the same as those of Black Star, so why did I get the opposite effect?

That's not right. That's not how the script was written!

[1] [Annotation text missing] Back

[2] [Annotation text missing] Back

Chapter 1189: Thanks, Little Soro, for the Assist!

The change in the Limitless Financial Group was just a small episode in the entire national war. After some players changed factions, the heat of this episode quickly subsided, and the various guild alliances redirected their attention to competing against each other.

The battlefield developed day by day, with a large number of players being eliminated. Because the number of resurrections decreased, the surviving guild alliances had become more cautious, not daring to be so aggressive. In addition, because many of the guilds had been eliminated, the battle was not as intense.

Because the Golden Alliance was constantly ranked first on the list, their lead kept on snowballing, and their current advantage was too huge. They were ambushed by the anti-Black Star troops, those from the three Universal Civilizations, and a bunch of loose guild alliances. This was one of their most tragic battles since the beginning of the war.

While the Golden Alliance had an advantage in terms of strength and number of resurrections, they also suffered from a loss in numbers and could not continue to maintain an excellent battle loss ratio. Their average number of deaths jumped from 5.89 to 7.38.

However, the advantages accumulated by the Golden Alliance were too solid, allowing them to maintain their position at the top despite the losses they sustained in this battle. The Golden Alliance's average deaths did not exceed 6 before this battle, while the averages for the other guild alliances were too high. For example, in second place, the September Council belonging to the three Universal Civilizations saw their average deaths rising from 6.71 to 7.68 after the battle, which was a net win for them, but overall did not allow them to beat the Golden Alliance.

According to the forums, the analysis of average death ratio was at 9 points. Any value higher than that meant that the troops had lost their combat capabilities, and right now, many of the major guild alliances were approaching this number.

Thus, on the sixth day, those who had yet to be eliminated did not wish to rashly start a war. They seemed to tacitly agree to refresh their number of resurrections on the day. Thus, Planet Milton suddenly became quite deserted, with only sporadic battles taking place.

However, when it came to nighttime, the scene suddenly got lively. The various guild alliances began to fight wildly, exploiting the loophole in time.

Because a player that ran out of resurrections within the six days would count as being permanently eliminated, even after the refresh time of six days, they would still be ineligible to continue the battle. Thus, the guilds planned to use troops that still had enough resurrection times to eliminate the 'seriously wounded' guilds with an average rate of 9.0 on the sixth night, weakening their opponents' troops. In this manner, after the resurrection count refreshed in the morning, it would be basically equivalent to having no battle losses.

Thus, the night of the sixth day gave rise to a huge battle royale, where those who wished to live past the night fled in all directions, whereas the 'healthier' ones turned into hunters, chasing after the 'wounded' with a smile.

Of course, the hunted and the hunter roles were easily swapped, and from time to time, there were hunters who turned into prey and joined the fleeing team. Compared with the tragic and bloody battles the previous few days, the sixth night seemed to be reminiscent of a horror comedy.

But this very night displayed the largest wave of elimination since the start of the war. A full seventy percent of players were sent off that night. On the morning of the seventh day, when the number of resurrections was refreshed, the guild alliances of the three mainstream factions had less than half of their troops left. The other scattered organizations were worse off, leaving only a quarter or even a fifth of their total population.

The plan to solve all battles within six days went through, but the scale of the troops for every guild were also reduced, so the resources that needed to be invested were also reduced. The major guild alliances could only fight with their remaining troops for another six days before they ran out of ammunition and food.

And when it came to the third cycle, that was, the morning of the thirteenth day, there were only six guild alliances left on Planet Milton. The Golden Alliance was one of them, and it was, relatively speaking, the best-preserved power. None of the eliminated players left, instead remaining to watch the battle from above Milton in their spaceships, betting on who would be the final winner.

Because the margin of error had become even lower, everyone started to behave more cautiously. In this situation, it would be difficult to clear out every single one of their opponents, so the six guild alliances unanimously decided to attack each other's strongholds and remove them to win.

After the first two weeks of war, the number of troops had decreased, resulting in a far less intense battle compared to at the beginning. At this time, another advantage of the Golden Alliance was greatly magnified—the Evolution Badge!

The Aberrations had strength far beyond a player's current level, but the flaws were also obvious; they were restricted to melee battles, and most of their skills would be frozen. This had led to the inability to fully utilize the superiority of the biological Aberrations in ultra large scale group operations due to the high concentration of firearms.

However, this was a different case in the small and medium scale battles where the enemy would have less firepower.

At the current stage of the war, the Golden Alliance no longer deliberately pursued the advantage of having lower damage, and using the powerful attack capabilities of the aberrations, they traded their resurrection times to invade the strongholds. By the fifteenth day, two other guild alliances had already been eliminated by them.

By the seventeenth day, only two alliances were left—the Golden Alliance and the Galactic Business Alliance. Both sides reached an agreement to not attack strongholds but rather settle the war in a decisive battle without regrets.

Having decided to end with a bang, both sides chose the battlefield to be Dragon Hill, which had already been renamed to Dragon Grand Canyon. They fought from morning till night, and in the end, the Golden Alliance won with a weak advantage, having less than two thousand players on the battlefield when the last member of the Galactic Business Alliance was killed.

The national war thus came to an end with such a result. Once it was over, the forums became the carnival grounds for the Chinese players. Even those who were eliminated politely sent congratulatory messages, acknowledging the win of the Golden Alliance for the first national war. The Galaxy Times as well as various reporter groups also released reports and articles, especially the group led by Bun-Hit-Dog. They were full of flowery praises, so cringy to the point that even the Chinese players that saw it felt their scalps tingle in discomfort.

The 'Galaxy Chronicles' was also updated, classifying the first national war as the 'Milton Battle', recording all the wars that took place, large or small. Because the Chronicle was one where players could add in their own input, everyone just had to upload the battles they had experienced to completely restore the entire process of the national war.

Even after the national war ended, the players did not leave but rather reluctantly returned to Planet Milton, treating the environment and using their engineering machines to transform their strongholds into cities.

Because it was a rare occurrence for people of all factions to gather, some players set up stalls, and soon, many more joined in, turning the place into a trading area. PVP players also felt an itch to look for people to spar, and thus, Planet Milton became lively again, as though it had turned into a new Main City for the players.

…

In the office of Black Star Palace, Han Xiao closed the forums with a smile on his face.

"It's finally over, after more than half a month. The time taken was much longer than in my past life."

He did not provide any help throughout the whole process and thus was very happy to see that the Golden Alliance had won. The Chinese players had achieved good results, showcasing his fruitful efforts in the past four versions toward them.

The first national war in his previous life had a far-reaching impact, being marked as one of the major landmark events in the 'Galaxy Chronicles'. The rules of the battlefield were passed down from then and eventually became a tradition recognized by the players. If they chose to fight again in the future, the same set of rules would have to be observed. The victory of the Golden Alliance would inevitably increase the attractiveness of their faction. As new players in the future considered which factions to join, with the older players blowing their own trumpets, the former would definitely choose the Black Star Army over the rest, due to its potential benefits.

The most important thing was that with the length taken to fight the national war, it had brought him far more benefits than expected!

Han Xiao opened the interface, glancing at the value of his EXP gauge as he smiled.

"It's about two months before the Pro League. I didn't expect this wave of experience to give me what I needed…"

Based on his calculations, he had enough to upgrade from level 331 to 340. This was much earlier compared to his initial estimations!

Within this wave of experience, there was a huge portion that was contributed by the former Limitless Financial Group players who switched factions midway.

"Little Soro, Little Soro. I must sincerely thank you for your help. Half of the labor belongs to you."

Han Xiao was extremely satisfied.

With enough wealth and foundation on his hands, there was no need to hesitate. He directly invested all his experience into his levels.

_____________________

Divine Throne Mechanic leveled up to Lv.32. +500 Energy, +5 STR, +5 DEX, +18 END, +25 INT. You have received 20 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

…

Divine Throne Mechanic leveled up to Lv.40. +500 Energy, +5 STR, +5 DEX, +18 END, +25 INT. You have received 20 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

You have received the Promotion Mission for Lv.340!

Lv.340 Promotion Mission: Raise one of your [God's Trait Transformation] skills to at least the 10th level.

_____________________

"Hmm?" Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

His [God's Trait Transformation—Machinery] had already reached the ninth level. Constructing another Universal Treasure would allow him to reach the tenth level.

The upper limit of his Divine Throne Mechanic Class was capped at sixty. Thus, there was no mission for a change in class at 340, only the Promotion mission.

"This seems quite easy this time round…" Han Xiao mumbled, but then he laughed to himself.

It's not that the mission is easy, but rather, I'm too good.

He was originally intending to use a Mission Completion Card for his Promotion, but he now dispelled the thought. Regardless, he had to increase his God's Trait Transformation skill, so there was no need to waste a Mission Completion Card on it. After the Intelligent Plague disaster, the dynasty had opened up a Gold Grade blueprint exchange channel for him. As long as he had enough faction Contribution Points, he could redeem a blueprint and craft it. He had the patience to wait for a while.

Furthermore, the effect of his Evolution Cube depended on his Energy Level. Now that he had the Dragon Emperor Star Energy Extraction Technique on hand, Han Xiao intended to raise his Energy Level to the next tier, obtaining an extra stack of bonuses from the Evolution Cube. This would also require some time before he reached his target.

Han Xiao directly took out his communicator to contact the Crimson Dynasty. After expressing his needs, he soon received a list of blueprints to choose from.

After scanning it carefully, he selected one of them, sending out a redemption application.

The next step would be to await the approval of the dynasty's senior officials to obtain his blueprint.

While the Gold Grade blueprints were precious to mechanics, to the point that having money alone could not buy it, with the fame and influence of the Great Mechanic Han, this was not an issue. Having authority in one's hands really made things a lot better.

Han Xiao was in a joyous mood, playing with his communicator whilst waiting for the dynasty to reply. Casually looking at the lively scene that was taking place in Planet Milton, he suddenly had an idea.

In his past life, the location of the first national war was also on Planet Milton, so it was regarded by the players as a commemorative Main City. However, after the version update, the planet was requisitioned and no longer opened to the public, thus becoming a regret for many of the players.

"When the fight between the three Universal Civilizations and the Super Star Cluster Alliance is over, officially concluding the fourth exploration phase, I'll buy Planet Milton and the several surrounding planets to give them to the Golden Alliance…"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

This move would not only deepen the army's presence among players but also reward the Golden Alliance.

The excellent results of the Golden Alliance have brought us huge benefits. Though it's an internal matter of the players, I should not be too stingy and make a statement to deepen the sense of belonging for the army players.

Isn't it just a few planets? Just this paltry sum, I can buy it directly!

Chapter 1190: Promotion!

Half a month passed by in a flash. Because the battle of Planet Milton had been settled, the preparations for the Pro League began to rapidly heat up. Players liked the new and fresh concepts, so analytical posts about the strength of professional players began to be posted on the forums, and various teams had also begun to promote and mobilize themselves.

But Han Xiao did not pay attention to all of this. As soon as he obtained the Gold Grade blueprint, he threw all his affairs to Sylvia, concentrating on production.

Because it was his first time creating this blueprint, Han Xiao worked for half a month, experiencing many failures and accumulating a lot of proficiency before he obtained a Gold Grade end product, obtaining his God's Trait Transformation point.

"It's done!"

In the machinery modification room, Han Xiao could not hide the joy on his face, casually throwing aside the Gold Grade equipment he had just created to open his interface and use up the point.

_____________________

God's Trait Transformation—Machinery] has reached the 10th Stage.

There are now unknown changes in your Life Hierarchy.

You have obtained a new understanding of Machinery. +15% chance of forming a new exclusive expertise. The skill [Universal Simulation] has obtained a sublimation.

You have begun to perceive part of the power of the transformation route - [Talent Unknown].

You have received [The First Sanctum] Ability Fragment x 1.

_____________________

"Oh, that's right. Every fifth increment indicates a new realm." Han Xiao nodded to himself.

When he reached the fifth stage for his God's Trait Transformation, the same notification had appeared. This time, he had obtained a fragment of the First Sanctum.

He glanced at the effect of the tenth stage. It increased the level of all Mechanic skills from the [Apostle Mechanic] to the [Divine Throne Mechanic] Classes by three, along with a 1.2 times bonus to Machinery Affinity, a forty percent bonus to skill effect, and a 1.3 times bonus to damage and shield durability… It was basically a replica of the fifth stage's effect, with an increase in the bonus range provided.

"This is similar to the fifth stage in that it provides an increase in combat abilities, not bad… eh? What's this?"

Han Xiao suddenly realized that the progress bar behind the ability name had changed. The expected (10/?) had become (10/15).

"The unknown question marks are now revealed… Is the highest level of God's Trait Transformation capped at fifteen? And it seems like you can only see this limit when you reach a certain level…"

Scanning it carefully, he found that the change was more than just these factors. From the 10th to the 11th stage, the number of points required to level up the skill had inflated to 6 points. At the same time, there was also a surprising notification.

_____________________

Your [God's Trait Transformation—Machinery] has reached the 10th Stage.

You have triggered the transformation requirement. For each requirement completed, you can reduce the cost of upgrading by one God's Trait Transformation point.

Reach level 345

Comprehend a Unique Talent

Create a Gold Grade blueprint

_____________________

"Going above the tenth stage not only requires points but also missions to be completed. This is a little like the advancement missions… Will the Mission Completion Card be effective here?"

While he was surprised by the changes in the God's Trait Transformation skill, he had no intention to experiment with it now. He turned his head, letting his mechanical assistant clean up the workshop while he directly teleported to a barren planet where he had previously placed a Throne beforehand.

Whoosh!

His vision spun, and he found himself now in the middle of a desolate gorge. Looking up, the walls on both sides stretched up all the way, forming a straight vision toward the sky.

This was a planet located in the hinterlands of the Black Star Army. He had chosen to advance here because he did not wish to make such a big commotion.

Han Xiao stowed the Throne away that he had his machinery place there beforehand before taking out the Evolution Cube and activating it.

Buzz!

The dark strands of Evolutionary Energy seeped out, and Han Xiao guided it into his body. A wave of pain burst out, as a black cocoon was formed outside his body.

On his interface, the notification of the effect of the Evolution Cube used swept through his screen like a waterfall.

_____________________

You have utilized the Evolution Cube (Gold Grade)!

You have received a permanent special benefit—[Gene Optimization: Evolution Cube]!

Identifying species… Identification complete.

Your current species is: Void Star Pursuer

Your genetic structure is being optimized…

The first optimization has succeeded. Your potential qualities have increased. It is detected that you have received this level of optimization before. You have received +0 STR, +0 DEX, +1 END, +2 INT, +0 MYS, +0 CHA, and +3 Energy.

Your Energy Level is above Level 0. The second optimization has automatically succeeded. It is detected that you have received this level of optimization before. Your potential qualities have increased, and you have received +1 STR, +1 DEX, +2 END, +3 INT, +0 MYS, +0 CHA, and +4 Energy.

…

Because your Energy Level is above Level 24, the 26th optimization has succeeded. Your potential qualities have increased, and you have received +85 STR, +90 DEX, +113 END, +148 INT, +76 MYS, +60 CHA, and +560 Energy.

_____________________

During this period, he had taken the time to learn the Dragon Emperor Star Energy Extraction Technique, and just yesterday, he had broken into the twenty-fourth level for his Energy Realm.

The first time he used the Evolution Cube, his Energy Level was only at fourteen. Thus, the first sixteen levels of the gene optimization had been triggered previously, and the effect of repeated use was far worse than before. But the effects from the seventeenth to twenty-sixth optimizations were normal because it was being triggered for the first time.

In total, his Strength and Dexterity had increased about 700 points, Endurance by almost 900, and Intellect over 1,100. Mystery and Charm had also increased by around 500, giving him a total of almost 4,500 Attribute Points. His energy had also gone up by around 4,000 points.

"The effect is pretty good, with a greater increase than when was used for the first time. This is probably because of the higher-level bonuses."

Han Xiao scrolled to the back of the notifications and was startled.

_____________________

You have obtained 26 rounds of gene optimization. +40% Experience needed to level up. Lasts for 26 months.

You have fulfilled a special condition: Possess a Racial Talent and obtain more than 20 levels in gene optimization.

You have triggered a Special effect.

The next time you undergo a Race Evolution, you will receive +30% to your attribute balancing, and your Racial Talent will also be additionally strengthened,

Gene Optimization has ended.

_____________________

With a cracking sound, the black cocoon shattered, and the evolutionary energy returned to the Evolution Cube.

The pain caused by genetic optimization slowly faded. Han Xiao's nerves were now extremely tough, and this sort of pain could not even distract him. He only stared at the notification on the interface with joy.

He only thought that the Evolution Cube would give a bonus for the first ten energy levels. The additional effect for the twentieth was something he did not expect. No player had ever reached this level back in his previous life.

"The last time provided me an additional opportunity for Race Evolution, and this time, it will increase my attributes in Race Evolution. Wonderful."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

At his level 300 Race Evolution, there had already appeared the option of [Void Archangel]. This meant that during his level 340 Evolution, he could reach the pinnacle of his Void Genes, which would likely give him a path that would lift his gene limiter!

Because the Race Evolution for one that lifted the gene limiter would give a lot more attributes compared to a general evolution, he was even more overjoyed.

"Good things come in pairs! It was worthwhile spending all my free time with Feidin!"

Han Xiao was ecstatic.

Taking a deep breath, he calmed down his emotions, keeping the Evolution Cube.

Looking at the indication of 'Completed' on his level 340 Promotion Mission, he solemnly chose to complete the mission.

Boom!

The ground quaked!

Surging Mechanical Force exploded out from him, rising to the sky!

_____________________

Lv.340 Promotion Mission completed!

Promotion succeeded!

+120 END Bonus! 1 END = 690 Health = 700 Stamina

On the road of Evolution, you have taken yet another step forward.

Race Detected: Black Star Race (Specialty race, unchangeable)

Randomly selecting five suitable evolutionary directions… Extraction complete!

Please select two from the five Race Evolution choices below and receive one talent from each:

[1]

[2]

[3]

[4]

[5]

_____________________

"What the hell are those two options?"

Enduring the drastic changes in his body, Han Xiao looked on with doubt.

Of the five options, he had never heard of the names of the [Saint—Carmel Race] or [Innate Star Body]. Even after checking his database, there was still no record.

"At this current level of evolution, things that I've never seen before have finally appeared."

While Han Xiao was curious, since he had already walked on his void evolutionary pathway to this point, there would naturally be no meaning in changing it. The two options provided unknown abilities, so he did not wish to take the risk.

As for the Void World Worm, he was aware that it was a symbiotic life born within the Void Dimension, forming an important part of the natural cycle in the Void Dimension. It fed on void energy and the chaotic space stream to form materialized excrement, which was one of the sources that made up the Void Dimension.

Both the Void Deity and Ancestor of the Void were the pinnacle form of the Void Evolutionary route, and both had the effect of lifting the gene limiter. Han Xiao did not hesitate, choosing these two races directly.

_____________________

You have received the talent [Gene Limiter Removal]!

You have received the talent [Void Control]!

Gene Limiter Removal: Your physical strength breaks through the limit of your species, greatly liberating your potential. You will obtain a huge number of attribute points and have a chance to raise related attributes when you perform your daily activities.

Void Control: You can control the Void Dimension to a certain extent (including but not limited to borrowing void energy to strengthen yourself, high-speed absorption within the void dimension, transform void energy into energy, summoning the void dimension to descend at your location…)

_____________________

"Void Control… Kasuyi definitely has a similar ability, or else his recovery speed would not be so terrifying…"

Han Xiao nodded secretly to himself. This ability was the most valuable talent, equivalent to obtaining permissions to operate a part of the Void Dimension.

Scrolling down, he noticed that the talent of the Black Star Race had also been strengthened.

_____________________

Your Black Star Race talent [Mechanical Genius] has been upgraded.

Mechanical Genius: Your Machinery Affinity bonus has increased from x1.28 to x1.38, Machinery Creation Performance increased from 44% to 54%, and +1 to all Mechanic Class skills' levels.

[Gene Optimization—Evolution Cube]'s effect has been triggered!

Your Black Star Race talent [Mechanical Genius] has been upgraded.

[Mechanical Genius: Your Machinery Affinity bonus has increased from x1.38 to x1.48, Machinery Creation Performance increased from 54% to 64%, and +2 to all Mechanic Class skills' levels.

Molecular structure is improved, organ structure strengthened, metabolism changed…

Black Star Race potential upgraded. You have received bonus attributes: +410 STR, +384 DEX, +561 END, +901 INT, +659 MYS, +347 CHA, and +10,000 Energy. Energy Level bonus attributes have been changed!

Gene Limiter Removal has taken effect. According to your current life level, race potential, and current attributes, you will obtain additional attributes. You have received +1,876 STR, +1,670 DEX, +2,348 END, +3,971 INT, +1,350 MYS, +966 CHA, and +23,400 Energy.

[Gene Optimization—Evolution Cube]'s effect has been triggered!

Your attribute replenishment effect is increased by 30%. +685 STR, +616 DEX, +872 END, +1,491 INT, +602 MYS, +393 CHA, +10,020 Energy.

_____________________

"What the‽"

Han Xiao's eyes grew wide.

This attribute point replenishment was by far the greatest he had seen. Including the bonus of Evolution Cube, the attribute points awarded totaled more than 20,000!

At this moment, the continuous surging energy within his body became more and more unstable, Han Xiao's body exuded a dazzling light as though it had become a planet core.

The energy rushed around his body, as though looking for an exit.

The next moment, his entire body shook as the energy was released to his surroundings.

Boom!

With Han Xiao's energy as the epicenter, oppressive energy burst out.

The earth shattered and melted instantly, turning into an ocean of magma.

This barren planet was akin to an egg, exploding into pieces as though it had been smashed on the floor!

Han Xiao only had a single thought in his mind at this moment.

"Thank goodness I didn't advance in the base, or else this daddy would have lost his home…"

[1] [Annotation text missing]

[2] [Annotation text missing]

[3] [Annotation text missing]

[4] [Annotation text missing]

[5] [Annotation text missing]

Chapter 1191: Skyrocketing Attributes

"Warning! Warning! The fourth sector is showing a high-energy response! The specific coordinates…"

An alarm sounded in the C0075D space monitoring system within the Fenrir Star System, and the staff hurried over to the radar screens. All of their uniforms carried the emblem of the Black Star Army.

The army had built a large number of space stations in the territory under their jurisdiction, which would monitor the situation within. They were mostly handled by artificial intelligence and supplemented by a small number of staff as insurance.

At this moment, a dazzling spot of light suddenly lit up on the real-time monitoring star map. The staff hurriedly operated the ultra-long-distance astronomical observation device, enlarging the field of view for the location of the energy burst.

The barren planet originally in this position had vanished, replaced by a cloud of golden energy that was constantly expanding, as though a dying fixed star was turning into a Red Giant. Brilliant arcs of lightning surged around it constantly.

Seeing this, the staff in the room all displayed confused expressions.

"What sort of phenomenon is this?"

"Looks like stellar delay… but there's only one barren planet here. Where did the Fixed Star come from?"

"Energy fluctuations are high. It feels more like that of a Beyond Grade A energy rank. It couldn't be a Beyond Grade A that sneaked in, right?"

Everyone spoke before unanimously deciding to conduct a field survey in accordance with the provisions of the operation manual.

An unmanned spaceship flew out of the space station, soon arriving at the planet's location. They saw that the golden energy was still expanding, its volume overwhelming at this point. The unmanned spaceship could not approach but only cruise around to collect data.

This continued for a period of time before the golden energy stopped expanding, shrinking hundreds to thousands of times smaller before suddenly exploding out in a shock wave. The observation screen turned blank from the shock wave.

The shield of the unmanned spaceship flickered, and the durability plummeted. Fortunately, it was far enough that even though it was damaged, it was not destroyed. When the spaceship finally stabilized, the staff far away in the space station hurriedly looked at the location of the explosion. The area was completely empty, with all matter of the barren planet annihilated.

Even after surveying for one round, they could not find the shadow of a person.

"Observation complete, source of outbreak not found. Requesting to return."

Hearing the emotionless reply from the artificial intelligence, everyone present shared a glance.

"This matter is too strange. It's not at our level. Report to our superiors."

At the same time, Han Xiao, who had swapped into another King mechanical suit, was now situated on another barren planet.

"Hu, I almost got caught."

Taking off his mechanical suit and collecting the Throne he had placed here, he let out a breath filled with gold lightning.

This time, his promotion had brought about a huge improvement. The energy in his body was nigh uncontrollable, his cells constantly producing energy that had blown up the planet when released. In order to not be seen, the moment he completed his promotion, he put on the spare King suit and teleported away.

He had chosen this position within the depths of his own turf to keep it a secret. His current strength had already made the various major organizations jealous, so if the outside world learned that he had improved yet again in such a short period of time, they would not show jealousy but fear. This might backfire on him, so he chose to keep it a secret, not wanting others to know about it for the moment.

"Master, hum… The command center of the Fenrir Star System has reported the high-energy response you triggered. They do not know the reason. How do I reply, hum?" Phillip's voice sounded in his mind.

"So fast? Not bad, you can reply as usual. Send some exploration troops there for a symbolic stroll."

Han Xiao shook his head and chuckled.

Looking past this small episode, Han Xiao reopened his interface. The notification of the completion of his promotion had popped up. Rubbing his hands in excitement, he observed the changes.

Total Level: 324

Main Class: Mechanic

Race: Black Star Race

Attributes: 15,914 STR, 15,423 DEX, 27,010 END, 56,460 INT, 13,107 MYS, 6,430 CHA, 0 LUK

Free Attribute Points: 135

Awakening Point: 9

Health: 41,039,094

Stamina: 31,662,700

Energy: 293,475

Lv.25 Energy bonus stat: +6,620 STR, +7,745 DEX, +10,308 END, +14,187 INT, +6,060 MYS, +4,382,600 Stamina Limit, +9,806% Machinery Affinity

Energy Rank: 98,510

Grade: SS

Grade SS Bonuses: +150 END, +45% All Resistances. +40% to Highest Attribute , +25% Other Attributes, awarded additional 750 Free Attribute Points and 50 Potential Points

Remark: The door to an even higher realm is slowly being opened for you…

"Hiss…" Han Xiao took a deep breath.

The effect of his promotion this time was astounding! All his attributes had increased tremendously, by almost a third compared to before his advancement… except his luck. It had fallen back to zero when his attributes were washed during the creation of his last Universal Treasure, and he had yet to place it back.

Compared to his current attributes, they were much stronger compared to when he first entered the Beyond Grade A realm. In particular, energy would showcase its strength in the later stages, each level giving a stronger increase. The bonus provided by the level 25 energy was much higher compared to when it was level 15. Sure enough, suppressing his energy was the best way to boost himself!

The increase in his attributes brought about by his Race Evolution was equivalent to getting the bonus from level 21 to 25 for his energy. The increase was huge.

Especially with his current HP. Let alone the enemy, Han Xiao's own tankiness made him wish to vomit when he saw it. He had an impulse to imitate Wei Yan from the Three Kingdoms, screaming out loud, "Who can kill me!"

"Even if I don't use machinery, and just rely on my body to fight Beyond Grade As below the Energy Rank of 52,000, I could probably still defeat them! And with my current Intellect attributes, plus the various bonuses, the state of my machinery is now terrifying."

Han Xiao clenched his fists, feeling the explosive power surging in his body. He could not hold back his smile.

With his current strength, even without his skill [Virtual Purification—Restore], he would not be scared of Manison bringing out the Felons. As long as he dared to appear using his true body, Han Xiao would use him as training. Right now, within this era of pinnacle Beyond Grade As, the only one that could threaten him would probably be [God's Chosen] Wuornos, who was unfathomable.

The more one's Energy Rank increased, the greater the span between each point. To be unable to achieve 100,000 this time made Han Xiao feel a bit of a pity. After all, this was like a threshold, so he had thought that maybe something would have been triggered.

However, considering that the entry to Beyond Grade A was not a whole number, the value of 100,000 did not carry any meaning at all.

His Grade did not change, and Han Xiao thought that Grade SS should be the peak of the Beyond Grade A realm. The next tier should be the realm that the EsGod was always searching for, which would give one a qualitative change in their life form, just like from the Calamity Grade to the Beyond Grade A.

The Free Attribute Points given from level 331 to 340 had been left untouched. Han Xiao threw a point into Luck before assigning the rest to Intellect.

Taking a look at the experience needed to upgrade, the amount had once again skyrocketed. It was such an astronomical figure that it even made a leek expert like himself speechless.

After admiring his new attributes for a few more moments, Han Xiao finally dragged his gaze away, pulling up the Ability section.

Because he was busy with his promotions before, he did not have the time to observe the changes in his God's Trait Transformation. This time, his promotion met all five conditions of the God's Trait Transformation, and he obtained five points.

However, [God's Trait Transformation—Machinery] required six points to reach the eleventh stage, more than what he currently had. He decided to see if the Mission Completion Card could work on the skill as well to reduce the cost.

"Theoretically speaking, the Mission Completion Card should work since it is usable for promotion missions."

Muttering to himself, Han Xiao took out the Mission Completion Card, selecting the requirement of 'self developing a Gold Grade blueprint' before looking at the interface.

You have used a Mission Completion Card!

Mission Completion Card has taken effect.

You have completed one of the upgrade requirements of God's Trait Transformation—Machinery. Points required to upgrade have been reduced by one. You currently need: 5 points.

"Oh, it works." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Over the years, he had obtained many Random Reward draw chances and had accumulated quite a few Mission Completion Cards. They now had another purpose—being used for his God's Trait Transformation skill.

"Although this is good news, I don't know if the requirements for each upgrade will increase. It's better to still save them and try to complete the upgrade requirements on my own. There's no harm in raising my strength anyways."

However, he still decided to prioritize his upgrade of [God's Trait Transformation—Machinery]. If the limit was still ???, he might have switched to the [God's Trait Transformation—Void] route, but now that the upper limit was not far away, he intended to try to complete the God's Trait Transformation—Machinery first, to find out what would happen if one of the routes was maxed out.

Right at this moment, his communicator rang.

"Beep beep beep!"

Kasuyi's washbasin-sized face appeared on his screen.

"Black Star, are you done with your stuff? When shall we depart?"

Han Xiao had previously agreed to Kasuyi's request to team up, but he had been delayed by the affairs of the Modo Civilization. After the Modo Civilization was dealt with, Kasuyi would send out a request every few days, but Han Xiao had replied to ask him to wait due to his promotion mission.

"Alright, alright, such a coincidence. My business has just finished. Let me know when you want to go," Han Xiao helplessly said.

Kasuyi finally revealed a smile. "Right now."

"Such a hurry?" Han Xiao was surprised.

"That's right. Do you have time?"

"I do have time, but I don't know where to go. What sort of preparations are needed?"

"There's no problem. We can meet up in the Void Dimension first before I brief you."

Kasuyi did not even wait for Han Xiao to reply before hanging up.

Han Xiao toyed with the communicator, his curiosity increasing.

He had agreed to Kasuyi's invite initially purely out of their friendship, but now he was getting more interested about this matter. What sort of event would make Kasuyi so desperate?

It was not known how long he would be gone this time round. Han Xiao thought about it before sending word to Sylvia.

"I'll be going to the secondary dimension world. It's unknown when I'll come back, so I'll leave you in charge for the time being."

Han Xiao quickly got back a reply.

"You might as well not come back."

Han Xiao felt helpless.

It seemed like Sylvia had been working overtime endlessly all this while, and thus, she was a little resentful. He would not argue with someone whose hairline was in danger of receding.

Han Xiao was about to summon the Mysterious Energy Host to bring him into the secondary dimension before he suddenly paused.

"Oh, that's right. I have the ability of Void Control and should be able to enter the secondary dimension at will without using the Primal Chaos Mysterious Energy."

He closed his eyes, activating the talent and communicating with the Void Dimension.

His consciousness seemed to sink into a colorful world, and bubbles quickly passed through his field of vision. Soon, a large gray-blue bubble appeared in his line of sight, growing larger.

With a thought, he inserted his consciousness into the Void Control from his macroscopic perspective.

Puff!

There seemed to be a sound going off in his mind as his consciousness was inserted into the Void Dimension without any hindrance. It was smooth as though the entry had been greased, leaving his own mark in the core of the Void Dimension.

Boom!

The next moment, Han Xiao felt that his consciousness seemed to have expanded, covering the entire Void Dimension. The energy within was like an extension of his body, and he could ignore the distance to absorb the energy of the Void Dimension, like an invisible energy transmission pipeline.

"Turns out, this is the same feeling as described by Hila…"

Han Xiao was astounded.

Those who could connect to secondary dimensions were few. Kasuyi was connected to the Void Dimension and Hila to her Underworld Dimension. Traveler had connected with the Evil Convergence secondary dimension through his own efforts, and now Han Xiao had joined their ranks. Having a secondary dimension that would provide a constant flow of energy to nourish the body was indeed different.

At this moment, he recalled something.

"That's right, Kasuyi is also connected to the Void Dimension. I'm not sure if he will find out…"

While waiting for Black Star in the Void Dimension, Kasuyi sat in his palace, absorbing the Void Energy to adjust his state.

He suddenly jerked and raised his head in shock.

"Someone else has connected to the Void Dimension?"

Kasuyi did not mind others connecting to the Void Dimension, as the energy was endless. He was not like Traveler, who treated the secondary dimension like his wife.

However, this was not something that could be done overnight. Only the Void species had the qualification to connect, but even so, they had to use their mental strength to slowly remove layers of obstacles in order to reach the core and establish a connection. At the beginning, Kasuyi had tried countless times before he finally established a connection.

But this unknown newcomer did not even make a commotion, reaching the core on their first try. This was inconceivable.

"Who could this guy be‽"

Kasuyi was secretly shocked, at the same time feeling a little sour.

"Even I could not do it so quickly. Just what qualifications does this person have…"

The more Kasuyi thought about it, the more unpleasant it was. The void energy he took in no longer felt as good as before.

Chapter 1192: God's Trait Transformation's Secrets, an Extreme Mission

Somewhere in the Void Dimension, a light flashed, revealing Han Xiao's figure, which was transmitted via Void Control.

"Kasuyi should have arrived. I'll go look for him."

With his Void Control, a small map of the Void Dimension conveniently appeared in his mind. Han Xiao found his position, moving toward the middle area of the Void Dimension, which was the territory of Kasuyi.

The effect of Void Travel was greatly increased, and each usage brought him a great distance. It did not take long for Han Xiao to reach the outskirts of Kasuyi's territory. After thinking about it, he stopped in an area that served as a border post, releasing his aura.

Boom!

The surrounding Void Energy blew up in a storm, alerting the guards. A huge army flew over quickly, led by a Void Duke.

"Who dares to intrude in Lord Kasuyi's… Oh, it's Lord Black Star!"

This Void Duke did not finish speaking before he saw Han Xiao, and he immediately dropped the hostility.

Han Xiao's reputation in the Void Dimension was not insignificant, since the deeds he had left there the last time had spread all around. Most of the strong people at the top of the Void Dimension knew about this void species that was at the same life form level as Kasuyi, and the milestone [Void Dimension Conqueror] helped too.

"Kasuyi and I have an appointment. Where is he?"

"Lord Kasuyi is already waiting for you in the main hall. Please follow me."

The Void Duke dispersed the troops, leading Han Xiao into the outpost and approaching the platform with mysterious lines on it. He then took out a deep blue crystal, whose insides were swirling with void energy. The next moment, the surrounding Void Energy surged, forming a gray-blue spatial vortex on the ground of the platform.

"A transportation door made from Void Technology?" Han Xiao sized it up.

Because the rules of the Void Dimension were different, they had their own system in place. This was a method based on utilizing the Void Energy and its characteristics, which could only be used in the Void Dimension.

Stepping in, Void Energy flooded his body. The next moment, he instantly appeared before a magnificent and luxurious palace, made out of crystals of various colors.

"Black Star, you're here."

A familiar voice came from behind him. Han Xiao turned around to see a small table, with Kasuyi seated by it.

Just as he was about to continue speaking, Kasuyi sensed something, and he showed a look of surprise.

He suddenly sensed the aura of a similar life form on Han Xiao—not the aura of the same species but one of a high-level bloodline.

"You've… evolved again?" Kasuyi revealed a look of shock.

"No, no, it's just a trivial increase." Han Xiao put on a humble expression.

As void creatures, his own Race Evolution could not be hidden from Kasuyi, but the other party was also unable to ascertain his exact growth.

"Every time I see you, I get more surprised…" Kasuyi narrowed his eyes. "Just now, the one who intruded… cough, who formed a connection with the Void Dimension couldn't be you, right?"

"Oh, you indeed discovered it." Han Xiao waved his hands. "I was just trying it but didn't expect it to be so simple. I succeeded in a try. I remember you mentioning that you do not mind others linking to the Void Dimension as well, correct?"

"That's alright. I was just curious…"

Kasuyi's eyes twitched, and he put on a nonchalant expression. However, his inner self was twisting in agony.

Simple? I'll be d*mned if it's simple!

To pass off your connection with the Void Dimension as a simple test, then what about my effort!

As he was internally scolding Han Xiao, the latter suddenly stepped forward, stretching out a hand to pinch his face.

Kasuyi paused, staring up at Han Xiao.

"You, what are you doing?"

"Checking to see if it's your main body or your clone." Han Xiao was curious.

"… I'm in my main body!" Kasuyi angrily slapped off Han Xiao's offending hand.

Han Xiao asked with suspicion, "Didn't you say that exploring the dimensions would be dangerous? I thought you would send a doppelganger and not come over with your main body… With just your health, you dare to do this?"

Kasuyi felt his face cramping up.

What sort of words are you saying? You think I'm so paper-like?

… Alright, I'm more like paper than you, but I'm still a pinnacle Beyond Grade A. There will be a limit to my paperness!

Kasuyi was speechless for a long time before pointing to the seat opposite him in resignation. "Have a seat and eat something. I'll explain our objective."

A few void creatures holding trays appeared as he spoke, carrying plates of food and wine and putting them on the table. The plates were made out of colorful translucent crystals, sparkling beautifully.

However, Han Xiao's mouth twitched upon looking at the food.

If he was not wrong, this thing on the plate seemed to be the excrement of the Void World Worm and was even the most concentrated part of it…

"What's wrong? Eat some."

"It's alright. I don't have such heavy tastes."

Han Xiao hurriedly waved his hand.

This could be considered the local cuisine of the Void Dimension, containing pure Void Energy. But Han Xiao had acquired this species and thus had no habits of eating such stuff.

Seeing this, Kasuyi did not force him, raising his glass to take a gulp of wine before beginning his explanation.

"At our level, the God's Trait Transformation is indispensable for us to go further. You must also have touched on this, but you might not know that as the degree of God's Trait Transformation gets higher, there will be some sort of intuition for you to perceive certain opportunities to obtain objects or complete some illusory things to reduce the difficulty of promoting to the next stage.

"And this time, I sensed an opportunity that guided me to the secondary dimension that we're going to explore later. There seems to be something in it that's attracting me, which might help in my God's Trait Transformation…"

"Oh?" Han Xiao suddenly had a thought.

Opportunity for transformation? This is similar to the prerequisites that appeared when my God's Trait Transformation reached the tenth level.

So, it turns out, this is how the prerequisites are reflected in the NPCs… Kasuyi must have a type of God's Trait Transformation that has gone above level ten.

To a Beyond Grade A, information about God's Trait Transformation was precious knowledge, so Kasuyi did not hesitate to share more about it at this point. Han Xiao also listened for a while and learned more about it.

It seemed vague, but Kasuyi gave a few real examples, such as his senses telling him that if he became the most powerful overlord of the Void Dimension, it would be conducive to his God's Trait Transformation. This was the same as Manison, who had a gut feel to become the leader of the Machinery Faith, which was what the Old Man had told him in private.

As for why this would happen, Kasuyi also had a few hypotheses.

In his opinion, the God's Trait Transformation was not only the evolution of the individual but also the entanglement of one's fate line with countless external factors. Only through assuming and integrating the luck of every group could the final God's Trait Transformation then be completed, as though it was a fate that the strong had to bear.

"There's actually such a thing?" Han Xiao was secretly surprised.

But thinking about it from another point, since there were the two words 'God's Trait' within the God's Trait Transformation, one could not rule out such a possibility. However, it was still unknown as to what would happen after the transformation was complete.

It was no wonder Kasuyi was so impatient. It turned out that he saw another possibility for further improvement.

It was just that from Han Xiao's perspective, this matter could actually be explained simply using an interface. It was probably that what the God's Trait Transformation was looking for was no longer just limited to levels, attributes, or energy. Rather, like the Class Advancement, he needed to complete a certain mission to earn his promotion. To a normal person, it would seem like they had received the call of destiny.

Because he had already seen the Mission Completion Card work on the God's Trait Transformation mission, Han Xiao did not find it too difficult to believe. In fact, he got happier.

It doesn't matter how a normal Beyond Grade A should train because we don't follow the same system at all. I just need to rush through all of these.

At this moment, Han Xiao suddenly realized a problem.

"I'm also a void creature, so my transformation route should be the same as yours. Will we then become competitors?"

Kasuyi shook his head. "Even if it's the same transformation route, the things we feel are different. While I don't have much information, my intuition tells me that everyone's path will be unique… at least within the same generation."

"Then your intuition must be really good," Han Xiao said. "I understand the goal now. It's to help you find an opportunity for your God's Trait Transformation in the secondary dimension, right? How's the situation there now?"

Hearing this, Kasuyi's expression became more serious, and he frowned.

"I've already sent two doppelgangers over. This area is within the deepest parts of the secondary dimension, and the space there is very chaotic, the environment dangerous. This is not the main issue, however. There's a group of powerful creatures guarding that area, and my doppelgangers have been repelled twice!"

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

To be able to repel Kasuyi's clones meant that the total combat power of these creatures could be compared to a pinnacle Beyond Grade A. This was undoubtedly the most dangerous place in the secondary dimensions. A Beyond Grade A would likely not be able to survive.

"Have you tried talking to them?"

"Their memories were empty, having no valuable information, and they seemed to also have no self-awareness. They did not respond to me, and I didn't recognize what species they were either. There's no record of them in the database."

"Let me look at it."

Han Xiao's brows furrowed. He was afraid that Kasuyi would have encountered those from the World Tree Civilization. That would be bad.

However, after seeing the image Kasuyi shared, Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief. He also did not recognize this creature, so it was likely not to have any relation with the World Tree Civilization.

"Just the guardian of this secondary dimension has such strength. I'm not sure what it will be like inside… Have you managed to get in?"

"Nope, I cannot break through the blockade of these creatures."

"If the outside is so dangerous, it's definitely not any better inside. Maybe it's the nest of these creatures…" Han Xiao's expression was strange. "You really want your main body to set off?"

"The only way for me to discover the opportunity is for my main body to go over. With your help this time, there should not be any problems. The Mechanic class is the most proficient in large scale battles. This should be your forte." Kasuyi laughed and spoke honestly. "Furthermore, my intention of inviting you was not just based on your strength but also to borrow your mechanical suit, the King. If the situation becomes too bad, then only you will have such mobility."

"I see." Han Xiao nodded.

"Then I'll accompany you with my main body. The machinery is too weak and might not be able to guarantee your safety."

Hearing this, Kasuyi did not know what expression to make.

Of the entire Universe's mechanics, probably only you can say such words…

Ding.

At this moment, Han Xiao heard the notification from his interface, indicating the acceptance of the mission.

_____________________

You have triggered the mission [Kasuyi's Invitation].

Mission Introduction: In order to find an opportunity for his God's Trait Transformation, Kasuyi has decided to explore a dangerous and mysterious unknown secondary dimension. Because he acknowledges your abilities, he has asked for your help.

Mission Requirements: Help Kasuyi find the goal of his trip.

Reward: 450 billion Experience, 6 Random Rewards, 3 Character Summon Cards, +30 Favorability for Kasuyi, 1 God's Trait Transformation, Milestone - Unknown

Remark: This mission is extremely risky. It is recommended that you proceed with caution.

_____________________

450 billion experience‽ Han Xiao almost doubted his eyes.

The experience reward was often linked to the difficulty of the task, but he only obtained ten billion for fighting against Old Man Manison. The highest experience reward he had ever seen was the one for the mission [Ending the Darkness], which was basically impossible to complete[1] appeared at chapter 1064, with a requirement of ending the slave trade in throughout Galaxy.].

And this experience reward was set at 450 billion, with a further remark warning about the difficulty of the mission‽

At this moment, Han Xiao could tell for sure that the mysterious secondary dimension was hiding a huge secret!

In the past, he did not exist, so Kasuyi's closest friend would probably have been Manison. Since both of them had come out unscathed, this meant that while the danger was high, it would not surpass that of a pinnacle Beyond Grade A.

Furthermore, since he had just undergone his promotion, his strength had greatly increased. It should not be a problem to do something that Manison and Kasuyi could manage.

I'm taking Manison's spot, which means that if there's anything good in the secondary dimension, Manison will be deprived of it…

Thinking about it, was this not him robbing another opportunity of Manison's?

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

His greatest hobby now was causing trouble for that old man.

…

In a certain corner of the Primeval Star River…

"Achoo!"

Manison, who was studying his blueprints, suddenly sneezed, and his expression turned gloomy.

With his experience, he did not need to think to realize that it must be that b*stard Black Star who was cursing him!

[1] [Annotation text missing] Back

Chapter 1193: A Strange Dimension

In the chaotic space that resembled a thunderstorm, a silver prismatic spaceship cut through the waves at a high speed, like a small boat traversing the open seas, experiencing endless turbulence.

Han Xiao and Kasuyi were inside the cockpit, observing the map model of the secondary dimension.

"We're going deeper…" Han Xiao looked at the jumping coordinates, smacking his lips. "Are you sure we didn't go the wrong way?"

"The direction my senses are telling me has not changed. Based on my experience, we should be almost there." Kasuyi nodded.

Because Kasuyi had never managed to enter the secondary dimension of his target, he did not have any anchored coordinates, so he could only travel through the known secondary dimensions first to shorten the distance as much as possible before they barged through the chaotic space stream.

The duo had been in flight for a few days and had left the area of control of the three Universal Civilizations far behind, delving deeper into the secondary dimension and passing through many bizarre planes.

The world of secondary dimensions was just like the main universe, constantly expanding. With every passing second, countless worlds would be born or would die. The three Universal Civilizations had only explored a portion of the relatively stable areas and called this explored area the 'Shallow Layer', whilst the unexplored areas were known as the 'Deep Layer'. However, there was actually no essential difference between the shallow and deep layers in the secondary dimensions.

Because it was difficult to move forward without proper coordinates, the only thing the duo could do was rely on Kasuyi's senses as their only navigator. Fortunately, because he had been there twice, there was proof that this method was feasible.

At this time, an almost invisible crack suddenly appeared in the turbulent space ahead.

Kasuyi's eyes brightened. "It's there!"

The moment he heard it, Han Xiao turned the spaceship in a sharp arc, dashing straight into the crack.

Boom!

By theory, encountering cracks in a space storm meant that one could directly enter a secondary dimension, but this time was different. Both of them only felt the hull slightly shake, but the world outside their porthole still showed an empty space. In front of them, an endless honeycomb-shaped space wall appeared, glowing in a mysterious bluish purple. This was the external barrier of a secondary dimension world.

And outside the space wall, there was a large group of weird creatures, the monsters mentioned by Kasuyi.

"It's here?"

"Yes, be careful. These creatures are not only aggressive but very resilient to attacks, having amazing resistance to both mental and energy attacks as well as being able to release a sort of energy similar to dimensional lightning. They can resonate with each other, forming a huge shield to isolate the outside world, which cannot be broken without killing the creatures. This was why I could not rush in," Kasuyi replied.

Han Xiao studied the creatures carefully. They were all quite large, and while he lacked a reference, he estimated that they were three hundred kilometers in length. They had the characteristics of a beetle, with a milky white exoskeleton all over their body and segmented body parts. At first glance, they resembled a centipede without feet. However, along the gaps between the carapace, they possessed light blue membranous wings instead.

Every section of the membrane wing had a limb-like joint, with a hollow bone tube attached at the end, as though serving as a breathing organ. On their abdomen, there were two rows of symmetrical nubs for feet, extending all the way to the tail. Their head had no visual organs nor mouthparts, only a huge pointed cone with rows of holes densely packed around it.

"What a look. Just because no one can see them, they chose to grow in any manner they wish?" Han Xiao secretly insulted them.

As they chatted, the wandering creatures spotted their spaceship, immediately attacking. They saw one of them inhaling a large amount of space turbulence before black and purple lightning appeared around it, shooting out to attack the spaceship.

Buzz!

Kasuyi's eyes lit up, and a huge Psychic shield popped up to protect the spaceship. All the black purple lightning bolts landed on it, exploding into fireworks, but he continued to inject power to ensure that the psychic shield was stable. With a huge amount of MP as his support, Kasuyi was totally not afraid of his consumption.

"They have very thick skin and good Psychological Resistance. My efficiency in damaging them is very low… I'll leave it to you, Black Star."

"You can defend. Leave the attacking to me."

Han Xiao opened his secondary dimensional army box, and mechanical soldiers rushed out and bombarded the creatures with fierce firepower.

Army-Style Mechanics were the best at such large-scale team battles. While Kasuyi was also good at area of effect damage, his class leaned toward mental damage. As long as he encountered targets with high Psychological Resistance, his damage efficiency would decrease.

The Psionic energy bombarded the monster, blasting a charred gap in his exoskeleton. The resistance of this group of monsters was indeed amazing, but Han Xiao was not his past self. After his promotion, his attributes had sharply increased, improving his attack power and Mechanical Force bonuses. Under the large-scale Mechanical Force concentration, the monsters were easily bombarded into scattered pieces.

At this moment, more of the creatures rushed over. Their numbers seemed to be endless, and they came up to fight with the mechanical troops without the slightest fear.

Their energies constantly resonated and connected with each other, forming an extremely thick black-purple shield that covered each individual body, slowing down the rate of casualties. As more of them arrived, the strength of their attacks and defense also rose.

Despite the fierce fighting, the two remained in the spaceship without moving.

Observing the battlefield outside the porthole, Kasuyi seemed surprised.

"Black Star, why is your machinery lethality so high now?"

Having crossed arms against these creatures, he was clear of their defenses. In his opinion, even if Black Star could handle the enemy, it should not have been as easy as this.

Kasuyi had also known Manison for many years and was knowledgeable. This time, the combat power of Black Star's Mechanical army was beyond his expectations. Compared to the last time he personally experienced Han Xiao's strength during the attack on Hila, Black Star had improved too much.

"My standard is just average."

Han Xiao smiled and waved his hand, not intending to reveal anything.

Seeing Han Xiao's reluctance to speak, Kasuyi also did not ask further, moving away from the topic. He exclaimed, "A Mechanic is truly a convenient class, able to solve such a trouble just by sitting in the spaceship."

"It's an advantage of our class. While we Mechanics have many weapons and underlings, are able to adapt to any situation, and especially for me, have the recovery abilities of a pugilist… I will never have Psychic abilities," Han Xiao joked.

"… This is not exactly consoling me either."

As they continued to talk, Han Xiao was glancing at the interface's combat information. While Kasuyi did not know about the origins of these creatures, he could find out just by looking at the interface.

The interface had named this creature 'Space Louse', with an average level of 240 to 260. It was a special biological life form with extreme racial talents. Just judging by their attributes and skills, it seems that the strength of a single Space Louse was already slightly higher than a normal Calamity Grade Super but far from reaching the Beyond Grade A realm. It was mainly because of their amazing resistance obtained from living in the chaotic space stream. Those Interstellar Beasts he had met before this all paled in comparison to them.

The Space Louse also had the ability to share energy. The more of their race within a certain distance, the higher their boost would be. They could share damage and transfer attributes, but there was a limit. However, at this limit, they could even resist the attacks of a pinnacle Beyond Grade A.

"This sort of creature is quite powerful. As long as their numbers are large enough, they can be compared to a pinnacle Beyond Grade A. I'd like to get a bunch of them to breed, but I don't know their habits or if they could survive in the main universe…" Han Xiao stroked his chin.

"I don't care about that right now." Kasuyi waved his hand. He only wanted to enter this secondary dimension to obtain an opportunity for his God's Trait Transformation.

"That's right. Let's finish our business first."

Han Xiao nodded and was about to command his machinery to fire and blow up a portion of the Space Louse group to create a channel into the secondary dimension.

At this moment…

Boom!

A tyrannical energy wave erupted in the distance, quickly approaching.

Sensing the fluctuations, Han Xiao and Kasuyi's expressions changed.

"This energy…" Kasuyi had a solemn expression.

"This is a real pinnacle Beyond Grade A. His realm is probably no lower than you or me!" Han Xiao frowned.

In their perception range, the source of this energy was fast approaching them, bringing about a strong sense of threat.

Both of their figures flashed as they finally left the spaceship. They also revealed their auras, gazing at the distance where the fluctuations were coming from.

Not long after, a comet shot over, stopping in front of them and revealing itself to be a three-meter-tall figure, with weird armor covering their entire body and only leaving two blue light dots where the eyes of the helmet were.

Han Xiao and Kasuyi sized up the visitor, quietly exchanging a glance before communicating mentally.

"Did you see this person the last two times?"

"Nope, his aura is foreign to me."

"Could this person be someone who hid in the secondary dimension his whole life, cultivating until he reached the pinnacle Beyond Grade A realm?"

"It's possible."

"I'll try conversing with him."

The two quickly reached a consensus. Kasuyi immediately released friendly mental signals, sending a spiritual message to attempt to communicate.

Han Xiao did not intervene in the exchange between them, but after a few seconds, he saw Kasuyi's expression turning ugly.

"What did he say?"

"No matter what I say, his replies were exactly the same, asking us to leave, otherwise they will kill us invaders."

"He called us invaders?" Han Xiao was full of surprise. "Could this secondary dimension be his territory?"

Considering the difficulty of the mission, Han Xiao had known that the mission would not be easy from the beginning, but he had only thought that this secondary dimension was a nest of the Space Lice. Now it seemed like they were wrong. Furthermore, the Space Lice around did not attack the mysterious newcomer, as though they were bred, so the truth was not so simple anymore.

"How would I know? It seems like there's nothing to talk about anymore. Get ready to do it." Kasuyi narrowed his eyes. He had to obtain his opportunity for his God's Trait Transformation, and it was impossible to compromise.

"Alright, but there's no need to fight him. We just need him to retreat, and we can directly enter the secondary dimension to see what's going on inside," Han Xiao suggested.

Kasuyi nodded, and without warning, a sudden violent mental attack burst out from him, shattering the surrounding chaotic space stream.

The mysterious person instantly attacked, surging blue energy gushing out to collide against Kasuyi's psychic energies.

Boom!

The violent energies exploded, clearing the entire area of the machinery and Space Lice.

Kasuyi's MP was nigh infinite, so his style was aggressive. However, his opponent was not stingy with their energy either. Both of their energies clashed to a stalemate in midair, radiating outward as shockwaves.

However, the strength of the mysterious person was actually as impressive as Kasuyi's!

Seeing this, Han Xiao immediately joined the battle, fighting two against one as his Mechanical Force dragged the countless soldiers toward him.

The next moment, a small-scale Mechanical Deity descended on him, throwing out a slash from his blade.

Because the other party's combat power has undoubtedly reached the SS rank, the effect of [Fearless Heart] was immediately activated!

Swoosh!

The Celestial Punishment Edge cut through like a hot knife through butter, slashing away the energy that the mysterious person was using as a shield and striking him backward so quickly that he turned into a comet, disappearing in their field of vision.

Kasuyi's psychic energy suddenly had no resistance left, and he could hardly react in time. He spoke in a stunned tone.

"You… knocked him flying? Isn't that too quick‽"

Kasuyi was in a delicate mood. He felt that Black Star seemed to be far stronger than he expected. There was a huge error in his impression on the strength that Black Star had.

"Alright, cut the extra talk. I only knocked him away. If he returns, we'll have to continue fighting him. Let's just enter and check the place out."

Han Xiao personally took action, manipulating his Mechanical Deity to lead the way using his blade and smashing open a route through the Space Lice. He exploded the shield formed by the energy resonance of the Space Lice, exposing the space wall of the secondary dimension.

Seeing this, Kasuyi did not have time to question Han Xiao's strength. He hurriedly followed him as they rushed into the secondary dimension with a large wave of machinery.

At this moment, the mysterious person finally flew back. Looking at the gradually closing space wall, the blue light spots at the position of his eyes flickered rapidly, suddenly turning red.

"Intruders succeeded in breaking through the second line of defense. Immediately adopting the third set of response plans. Changing operation mode… Change completed. Current mode: Pursue and Kill!"

…

Han Xiao had just entered the space wall, and seeing the chaotic space stream of blue and purple colors, along with the feeling of suffocation, he got a big surprise.

"This feeling seems to be different from when I've entered other secondary dimensions…"

Before he could even sense the scene carefully, his sight took an abrupt change.

Seeing the new scene, he paused in astonishment.

He was situated high above the sky, with an extremely prosperous galactic city facing him. The city had tall buildings and bright lights, along with countless flying vehicles and an endless flow of people on the street, all of which were a race he had never seen before.

"This… what's the situation here?"

By the side, Kasuyi was also shocked. He did not expect the inside to look like this.

Han Xiao now remembered that the combat information about the mysterious person was termed 'Supreme Guardian'. So, the object of the person's protection was this civilization?

Looking behind them, they got a shock once again. What appeared was not the space wall of the secondary dimension but rather a sky full of galaxies like the main universe.

Just as the two were puzzled, a sudden change occurred!

"Wu wu wu wu! Emergency evacuation! Emergency evacuation!"

A harsh alarm suddenly sounded in the entire city, and the ground shook, with the steel surfaces sliding away to reveal various refuge entrances. The countless pedestrians and flying vehicles seemed to have practiced this thousands of times, hurriedly flying into the shelters.

At the same time, turrets with weird forms protruded from the ground, aiming at the two.

"Hey, we're being treated as invaders now… What is this‽" Before Han Xiao could finish, he sensed the aura fluctuations of six Beyond Grade As, and his eyes widened.

In the distance, six figures rose into the sky from all directions of the city, rushing toward the duo.

Seeing this, Han Xiao and Kasuyi shared a glance, their eyes brimming with surprise.

In addition to the previous pinnacle Beyond Grade A outside, there were now at least seven Beyond Grade As in this secondary dimension!

What the hell is this place‽

"Luckily, the six of them are only at the Beyond Grade A level. We should be able to handle them… huh?"

Kasuyi suddenly stopped mid-sentence, his expression turning unsightly.

"What's wrong?"

"My connection with the Void Dimension… seems to be disconnected?" Kasuyi's eyes got wider as he spoke.

Han Xiao frowned, secretly feeling it before realizing that he too could no longer connect to the Void Dimension.

Opening his interface, he checked if he was suffering from any abnormal state, but his status was as usual, not affected by any space interference device.

But as he scrolled down, he found something strange.

Not only did his talents related to the Void Dimension turn gray, but even his secondary dimensional army box and Dimension Factory were frozen, unable to be activated.

"What's going on?"

Han Xiao was confused, feeling that this secondary dimension was revealing an indescribable weirdness.

Chapter 1194: Mobile War System

Just as the duo were caught unawares, the six Beyond Grade As had already arrived and encircled them.

The one who seemed to be the leader spoke loudly, but neither Han Xiao nor Kasuyi understood the other party. They were using an unfamiliar language, and it was not in the general translator's database.

Kasuyi squinted before releasing his psychic waves to communicate, pulling Han Xiao into the chat channel.

Seeing this scene, the leader was stunned for a moment before he received the mental connection. The moment he connected, he immediately asked, "You guys, where did you come from? Why do you not understand the common language?"

"Where is this place?" Kasuyi replied with a question.

"Tudor Province Capital, a colonial planet under the Caliste civilization. I'm the Captain of the Protectorate Team, Farlite. I request you to explain your origins and identity immediately as to why you appeared out of thin air over the city. Please answer!"

Hearing this, both Kasuyi and Han Xiao shared a glance, sensing each other's doubts through the mental link.

Caliste Civilization? They had never heard of it before. Looking from the history of the exploration era up till now, there were no records of such a civilization. Could it be that this was a civilization borne in the secondary dimension that had never appeared in the main universe? While they did not know their level of technology, just the six Beyond Grade As could already occupy a place in the main universe.

Seeing that the two of them did not respond, Farlite intensified his tone and shouted, "This is the period of martial law in the entire universe. You've violated the ban set by the Celestial Star Alliance, visiting the colonial planets of other civilizations without permission and showing your power at will. According to the relevant laws and regulations, you have to immediately disarm yourselves and give up resistance, sealing your own Source and accepting our investigation. Otherwise, we will take coercive measures!"

These words could be understood separately, but linked together, they only gave the duo more confusion.

Universal martial law? Celestial Star Alliance? Source? What's that‽

While they did not understand the nuances, the overall meaning was clear. It was nothing more than asking them to give up any resistance. However, in such an unfamiliar environment, it was naturally impossible for the two to give up self-protection and allow themselves to be apprehended.

Kasuyi wanted to ask more, but upon seeing that the two of them remained indifferent, Farlite's expression sank, and he moved without speaking further.

Boom!

His aura exploded suddenly, and in a flash of rainbow light, Farlite charged in front of Kasuyi as though he had teleported, lashing out with a punch. The shock waves from the compressed air sounded out as a sonic boom.

"You dare move against me?"

Kasuyi frowned, and with a speed even quicker than Farlite's, he reached out and placed his hand on the side of Farlite's fist. He slightly tilted his body, pushing against Farlite's fist. The majestic Pugilist aura was cast aside, turning into a beam of light as it disappeared into the galaxy.

His movements then shifted lightly, and an elbow shot forward, hitting Farlite's chest. The highly concentrated psychic energy was akin to acupuncture, pouring into the opponent's body through the point of contact without a single bit leaked.

Boom!

The energy erupted internally, and Farlite could no longer control his body, flying back at a speed that was several times faster. He crashed through the skyscrapers, leaving behind large holes that were totally see through as he disappeared into the distance.

Han Xiao could not help but comment, "Oh, looks like you can do hand to hand combat with a Pugilist as well."

"Don't look down on others. I killed my way out from the Void Dimension, so melee is also my forte." Kasuyi shook his arm casually.

While he was used to squandering the limitless mana provided by the Void Dimension, he had been a very precise fighter before, causing the greatest damage using the least energy. As a void creature that lived in the Void Dimension since his childhood, melee would not be his weakness.

Furthermore, he was still a pinnacle Beyond Grade A, and just his raw attributes would already be able to allow him to compete with a Beyond Grade A Pugilist, let alone with his dual abilities of spiritual and psychic powers.

The other five Beyond Grade As seemed to have received a shock, letting out exclamations of surprise. Han Xiao did not know what they talked about, but in the next instant, the five of them rushed over, besieging them.

The various weapons on the city's ground level also opened fire toward them, filling the sky with explosions like fireworks.

"Sigh, these people are so irritable. They dare to fight above the city. Aren't they afraid that we'll just blow up their planet?" Han Xiao sarcastically remarked before a wave of his hand brought up the concentrated firepower of his machinery, whilst some of them entangled with the five Beyond Grade As.

The mechanical units that were fighting against the Space Lice outside the secondary dimension had been brought in together by Han Xiao. While his secondary dimensional army box and Dimension Factory could not be opened at this time, leading to a lack of troops that could be summoned, the Great Mechanic Han was not worried at all.

A Mechanic's weapons were all crafted by themself. If he could not use his inventory, he could just pick whatever materials he had on the spot and make something!

The stronger his hands-on abilities, the more assurance he had!

The six opponents consisted of two Pugilists, a Mage, and three Psychics, all of which were ordinary Beyond Grade As with Energy Ranks below 52,000 Ona. As soon as both sides clashed, the five Beyond Grade As fell into a disadvantage, only being able to resist with difficulty. Even if Farlite managed to return to the battlefield, he would not be able to reverse their predicament, only holding on bitterly.

With the advanced attribute bonus brought about by the Promotion to level 340, coupled with the explosive output brought by his [Legendary Battle Technique] and [Fearless Heart] skills, an ordinary Beyond Grade A wanting to go against him was simply deciding that they wanted to cut their lives short. Furthermore, there was yet another pinnacle Beyond Grade A, Kasuyi, beside him. Against these normal biological life forms, the latter's Psychic skills could finally exert their full lethality. Together, it was a simple task to beat the ordinary Beyond Grade As.

However, even if the six were not opponents of Kasuyi and Han Xiao, it was still possible to contain them for a period of time. This was even more achievable given that the duo were unaware of the situation and thus did not wish to unnecessarily kill.

While using his Psychic Acupuncture technique to cause hemorrhage to his opponent's brains, Kasuyi communicated to Han Xiao through the mental channel.

"Black Star, we're not in our strongest states now. There's also another pinnacle Beyond Grade A outside the secondary dimension. If he joins in, the situation will be unfavorable to us. We don't need to continue this battle and instead should leave this place to obtain more intelligence as a long-term plan."

"My sentiments, let's shake them off."

Han Xiao nodded. He was very concerned about the information these people revealed, wanting to figure out his current environment as soon as possible.

With a thought, he pulled all his mechanical soldiers together, gathering them.

Clank!

The Mechanical Deity descended once again, stretching out a hand to grab Kasuyi and integrate him within before igniting all its thrusters and rising into outer space.

Farlite shouted, as though telling them not to run, while leading the other five along in pursuit. Pugilist flames, Psychic impacts, and Magic spells continued to blast toward the Mechanical Deity, all of which were shielded by the honeycomb structure of its Emperor's Cape.

"Still want to chase? This group really do not know how to count their blessings. They must have suffered from a lack of 'love[1]'."

Han Xiao helplessly raised his Celestial Punishment Edge, and the surging psionic energy formed on the blade. Following the pathway of the Getta Hadoken, it condensed before slashing out in a solid arc of light.

Weng!

The faint blue light blade shredded the space around it, leaving cracks as it flew forward.

The strength behind this blade caused the expressions of the six to drastically change, and they hurriedly utilized their strongest defensive skills to go against it.

Boom!

The resulting frenzied shock wave spread out in all directions from the impact point, turning the atmosphere around it into a cloudless area.

"Argh!"

Tragic screams sounded from afar as the six of them were smashed downward from the force of the blow. A large area of tall buildings shattered and collapsed. Looking from outer space, it seemed that six mushroom clouds had suddenly grown on the surface.

"You didn't kill them, right?" Kasuyi was worried.

"I didn't even use my strength. How could this sort of attack kill anyone?" Han Xiao did not put much thought into it.

Kasuyi immediately rolled his eyes.

He had already realized that Black Star had obviously made some significant improvement, and yet he deliberately pretended to be modest and hid it. Did he think that everyone around him was blind?

The Mechanical Deity turned around and flew off, crossing the starry sky and moving away from the planet.

At this moment, Farlite and company crawled out from the rubble on the ground. Everyone was wounded, and as they watched the Mechanical Deity disappear from their vision, they could not help but feel a lingering fear.

The blade just now had given them the feeling of an extremely terrifying threat to their lives, and they almost thought that it would be the end of them.

The group surveyed their surroundings, and upon seeing that the city they were guarding had turned into ruins, they could not help but burst into anger.

"What do we do now?" someone asked.

"The two of them are 'Supreme' Ranked experts and are not people we can deal with," Farlite said angrily. "Their appearance is just too weird. I suspect that they will interfere with the World Reset Plan. Immediately report up to the Celestial Star Alliance Superpower Security Department. Ask them to send a hunting team and issue a universal arrest warrant!"

The secondary dimensions were strange and had their own laws of operation. But this secondary dimension was similar to the environment in the main universe, with a boundless galaxy that was rare even in the secondary dimension world.

While this dimension had the environment of the universe, the star map of the main universe could not be used at all. After Han Xiao controlled the Mechanical Deity to leave the planet, he used the parts and materials of the mechanical soldiers to build an astronomical observatory to plot their surroundings. He discovered an asteroid belt, so they went over there to camp there temporarily.

Very quickly, the asteroid belt appeared in front of his eyes. Han Xiao released the Mechanical Deity, turning it back into soldiers to guard his surroundings while he boarded one of the asteroids with Kasuyi to discuss their next countermeasures.

"…This secondary dimension is too exaggerated. I don't even know where the end is. What about you?" Kasuyi frowned.

"Same here. This feels like an actual universe." Han Xiao opened his hands.

Kasuyi paced as he thought aloud, "Could it be that the secondary dimension is actually a giant wormhole that transferred us to an area of the universe not controlled by the three Universal Civilizations. Could we have come to another corner of the universe?"

"I doubt that's the case." Han Xiao shook his head. "My Dimension Factory is locked, as is the Void Dimension. This sort of unique characteristic is not like returning to the main universe."

"That's true…" Kasuyi suddenly thought of something. "Your Dimension Factory can't be opened? Then it means we're trapped here since you cannot retrieve your mechanical suit?"

"You don't have to worry about that." Han Xiao fiddled with the compressed orbs hanging on his neck. "I have a habit of carrying spares. There's enough to get us both out."

Spacetime anchors naturally restrained his secondary dimensional army box, so he would not be unprepared. He would always leave some of the more critical machinery on his body for quick access.

"Then I'm relieved." Kasuyi breathed out. He did not wish to leave just like that, but he was worried that he did not have any routes of retreat.

"By the way, this secondary dimension seems to be completely isolated from the outside world. I cannot even contact my main artificial intelligence through the quantum network," Han Xiao said.

Because Phillip's mainframe was in his base camp, Han Xiao had been cut off since he entered the secondary dimension. He could only replace it with Phillip's backup sub-body that he carried with him and use it as a local area network connection. However, he was unable to lock onto his avatar outside the secondary dimension to return to the main universe.

He opened up the quantum network vision, connecting to the quantum network in this secondary dimension. He had tried it during the battle just now, finding that the coded language of the quantum network in this dimension was different compared to the main universe. This situation was similar to that of the Virtual Mutiny Virus, where the basic code had to first be deciphered before his virtual intrusion methods could be used.

"By the way, what about your senses regarding the God's Trait Transformation?" Han Xiao asked.

"It's still present, but it has turned blurry," Kasuyi helplessly replied. "I feel as though my senses are pointing to this entire space, with no determined direction."

"This isn't good. Without your locator, given the size of this secondary dimension, how are we going to find it?"

Han Xiao shook his head.

If his senses were still accurate, that would be easy for them to just follow the directions to obtain the opportunity and then use the King to escape. But now, without a direction, it was a lot more troublesome.

"We can only find it slowly." Kasuyi looked hopefully at Han Xiao. "You don't have anything to do, right?"

"I don't, but if this takes too long, I can only choose to retreat temporarily."

Han Xiao shrugged.

He did not need to worry about the Pro League of the players and originally intended to grind his skills here. The Kunde Race's Spacetime Splicing Technology was a good choice, and this secondary dimension might even hold some black technology that he could obtain.

That's right, speaking of the players…

Han Xiao had a thought and opened the forums to check. He discovered that everything was working as usual, and he could still see the posts that the players had put up.

Currently, all sorts of external communications had failed, so the forums had become his only channel to receive information from the outside world.

Kasuyi paced back and forth as he pondered, "Black Star, what's your next step?"

Han Xiao threw him a glance before replying, "We are still unaware of what is happening in this secondary dimension. I recommend we treat it as another universe for now. We're outsiders and thus have to collect information.

"Give me some time to decipher their coded language of the universe quantum network before I hack in to collect information… Before that, though, we need a temporary star map. I'll just draw this. The observatory can solve this problem…

"In addition, the degree of danger is unknown. I'll expand the current machines to find some resource rich planets, establish temporary strongholds, and make engineering equipment to collect various materials, creating a new assembly line…"

Han Xiao rattled off a series of plans.

Since his Dimension Factory was frozen, he planned to open up a base in this secondary dimension, copying a set of military factories to solve the problems of combat, logistics, detection, and concealment.

Kasuyi listened for a long time before he could not help but ask, "What do I need to do?"

"You…" Han Xiao stroked his chin as he sized up Kasuyi before saying with confidence, "Just don't cause trouble."

Hearing this, Kasuyi could not help but let out a bitter smile.

It was no wonder that among the five Super systems, the advanced civilizations were the most afraid of the Mechanic class, which was basically a mobile interstellar war system!

He secretly rejoiced that he had brought along a Mechanic. If he had brought a Pugilist that could only beat people up, they would only be able to stare at each other right now.

The Pugilist system was really unreliable!

In a metallic machinery room, a man with pipes all over his body slowly opened his eyes. He had two pairs of green eyes, a pair larger than the other, which were symmetrically distributed on the left and right of his face. A vertical scar ran along the left side of his face, only leaving the two eyes on the right side of his face open.

His breathing was labored, and only after a long while did a deep mutter sound through the room.

"There's finally another outsider… This person had better be of use this time…"

[1] There’s this saying that ‘scolding means I care; beating you means I love you’. It’s mainly used to describe the hidden care of the parents toward the child.Back

Chapter 1195: Unbelievable Discovery, S Ranked Hidden Mission

"The Caliste Civilization sent over an anomaly report, claiming that two unfamiliar experts at the 'Supreme' level had violated the ban, appearing out of thin air in the capital of Tudor Province. They refused to obey the handling, and after a fierce battle, both of them fled into space, disappearing without a trace… This is the image data they recorded."

The huge conference room designed like stairs was filled full of people. Everyone was watching the video on the virtual screen carefully. What was displayed on the screen was Han Xiao and Kasuyi's battle with the guardians of Tudor Province.

The video duration was not long, and it soon ended with the shocking blow delivered by the Mechanical Deity.

The screen went black, and the room was enveloped in silence for a while before discussions heated up.

"There's no doubt. Both of them are at the Supreme level."

"The database does not hold their information at all. They are of unknown origins, identity, and ethnicity, and there's no recorded activities on them."

"That's strange. Even for our Minister of Superpower Security, people with such strength will get the authority to head a department. To think such experts would actually be willing to endure loneliness and be obscure."

"Well… they've been concealing themselves up till this point, so their intentions for the big picture are probably huge."

"Could it be related to the World Reset Plan? Otherwise, why would they only appear at this crucial point?"

"This matter has to be taken seriously. No factors that may interfere with the World Reset Plan will be allowed to intrude."

At this moment, a senior executive who seemed to be a department head knocked on the table to interrupt the discussion. He spoke in an indisputable tone.

"This matter will be handled by the fifth, seventh, and eleventh divisions. Directors of these divisions, please arrest these two and carefully review their origins."

Three of the executives stood up, nodding slightly to accept the mission.

The department head slowly nodded as he said, "This is a pressing time. There's no time to play hide and seek with them. To end this quickly, I approve the use of the Cosmic Treasure 'Positioning Star Map' to lock in on their coordinates."

Hearing this, everyone on scene let out a faint smile.

The Positioning Star Map was the trump card of the Superpower Security Division. It was a Cosmic Treasure that was formed from unknown means. A complete star map of the universe was stored inside, and as long as one entered the target data, they could locate their coordinates in real time.

All fugitives had nowhere to hide in front of such a tool!

…

A couple of days later…

On a certain gray, barren planet, the underground had been transformed into a temporary base by Han Xiao. There was automated mining equipment that went deep into the veins of the planet to collect various ore resources, transporting them to undergo material processing through assembly lines. The refined ores were made into various raw materials and then put on the production line.

Because of the current shortage of materials, Han Xiao only assembled the basic assembly line, of which the majority were collection and assistant machinery to expand his initial production capacity.

In the central control room of his temporary base, Han Xiao sat in a simple quantum network view magnifier, surrounded by dense virtual screens. Amazing data streams flashed through the screens constantly. He had spent several days deciphering the coded language for this quantum network.

Kasuyi sat on the alloy bench beside him, leaning back against the rock wall as he watched Han Xiao in boredom.

With Black Star doing all the work, Kasuyi had nothing to do, and he could only give moral encouragement and eye power.

At this moment, Han Xiao's eyelids trembled, and he opened his eyes as he exhaled.

"I've cracked it."

Kasuyi's spirits perked up. "That quickly?"

"It's not too bad. Their coded language is not complicated. As long as you find the entry point, the rest is easy."

Han Xiao waved his hand.

The difficulty of cracking the code this time was much lower compared to the original Virtual Mutiny Virus. The Domino Virus was a weapon that contained multiple keys, with no reference target. One could only utilize trial and error to succeed. In contrast, the quantum network shared similarities with the network of the main universe, and because it was open source, there were many references. Han Xiao also had the [Virtual Technology Innovation—Manison] skill, which enhanced his own Virtual Technology and made it easier to crack.

Having finished the deciphering, his own virtual intrusion means could finally be used.

"What are we waiting for? Use your invincible Virtual Intrusion to collect intelligence," Kasuyi urged.

"Hmm." Han Xiao nodded, closing his eyes before sinking into the quantum network field of vision, collecting data on a large scale.

After pacing around and around, Kasuyi saw Han Xiao reopen his eyes and immediately asked, "How is it? Did you find anything?"

Hearing this, Han Xiao's expression turned weird.

He took a deep breath before suddenly exploding. He grabbed Kasuyi's neck with both his arms, shaking him repeatedly as he screamed, "F*ck your ancestors! What sort of hell did you bring me to‽"

Kasuyi's head was shaken so fast it formed an afterimage, and he had an expression of confusion.

"What… what do you mean?"

"See for yourself!"

Han Xiao flicked his hand, opening a virtual screen, and dumped all the information inside.

As Kasuyi scanned it, his eyes grew wider, an incredulous look spreading across his face.

"This… How is this even possible‽"

Kasuyi retreated involuntarily after he understood the information.

This intelligence was not the top-secret files in the universe but basic information that Han Xiao had collected. But the content was out of all their expectations.

The area in this secondary dimension was even wider than the entire explored universe! There were thirty-three Star Fields, six to seven hundred Star Clusters, and countless Civilizations of all levels!

As for the ruling party, it was a civilization known as the Celestial Star Alliance. Just the introduction told them that it was stronger than the three Universal Civilizations and had a longer history. Even if they looked at the oldest of the three Universal Civilizations, the Arcane Church, its civilization age was but a fraction of the Celestial Star Alliance's.

There were also five different types of Superpower systems present: Mechanic, Psychic, Pugilist, Esper and Magic. However, their term of 'Energy' was known as 'Source', and even their realms were separated differently. They called their Beyond Grade As 'Saints' and the pinnacle Beyond Grade As 'Supremes'.

In terms of individual strength, this secondary dimension also trumped the main universe. According to the data, there were nearly ten thousand 'Saint' level experts recorded in their universe! The equivalent of Beyond Grade As numbered almost ten thousand, of which there existed hundreds of pinnacle Beyond Grade A! The reaction of the duo was that this was unbelievable!

What did this mean? Although Beyond Grade As had long life spans, most people still grew old and died. To have nearly ten thousand living Beyond Grade As, how long exactly had this secondary dimension existed?

The two of them had thought that this secondary dimension was at best a universe that had managed to develop itself, but they did not expect that there was actually a civilization many times stronger than the three Universal Civilizations.

"Black Star, are you joking with me? You made this material up, right?" Kasuyi had a look of shock.

"Why would I joke with you at this time? All of this was picked from their web, and it's all the most fundamental intelligence you can find."

Han Xiao had frowned the first time he saw all this material online. He had actually doubted its veracity, but after repeated searches, he had discovered that it was all true.

Could this secondary dimension actually be stronger than the main universe itself? Was the Celestial Star Alliance stronger than the three Universal Civilizations? This was too exaggerated! How could there be such a freak in this secondary dimension?

Or could this actually be an unexplored area of the main universe?

Then how did Kasuyi and Manison go back the moment they arrived there‽

Han Xiao's mind ran quickly. Because the information from his past life was limited, he did not know what was going on for a while.

Kasuyi had not recovered from his shock at this point. He was murmuring to himself, "If the people in this secondary dimension run out into the main universe, then…"

Hearing this, Han Xiao's eyes gleamed, and he hurriedly went back online. He decided to scan the internet to search if this universe had any information regarding secondary dimensions. If the Celestial Star Alliance truly existed within the secondary dimensions, then it would be impossible that they had never explored the outside world.

Han Xiao soon found what he wanted, but the result surprised him yet again.

This universe had no secondary dimensions!

There was no division between the 'main universe' and the 'secondary dimension'!

All they had was a single cosmic plane, without any 'outside' in which they could explore. They too were unaware about the Space Lice swarm and the Supreme Guardian that was stationed outside.

Strange!

This is too strange!

Han Xiao's curiosity grew stronger.

"By the way, when we first came in, those six Beyond Grade As seemed to say something about martial law in the universe. Let's see what's that about…"

Han Xiao hurriedly entered the keywords, and his vision was soon replaced with a headline.

'World Reset Project'!

The announcement stated that this was a universal-level plan launched by the Celestial Star Alliance. This was a special measure to prevent any future disasters that could not be solved.

The intelligence Han Xiao discovered was all from announcements and news, and it only provided a general outline. It seemed as though the Celestial Star Alliance was planning to utilize a sort of new Information Form technology to reproduce the data of the entire universe as a data library, treating it as tinder. If there would be an irresistible disaster in the future, they would restart the universe based on the tinder data library.

This re-engraving process was during the period of martial law throughout the universe. The Celestial Star Alliance required everyone to stay in one place and not move around, to prevent interference with the construction of the tinder library. Thus, the interstellar area was deserted, without any spaceships.

As for the specific plan, the Celestial Star Alliance did not disclose it to the public, so Han Xiao was still unaware of the details.

"I have a feeling that this plan is not some insurance…" Han Xiao muttered before going up to knock on Kasuyi, seeing him still stunned. "What shall we do now? The space in this area exceeds your imagination. Your senses are also malfunctioning, so even after hundreds of years, you might not find your so-called opportunity."

In his opinion, this should be the reason the difficulty of the mission was expressed through the astronomical sum of 450 billion experience.

Kasuyi came back to his senses, but his expression was uncertain, and he did not speak for quite a while.

Seeing his reaction, Han Xiao also sighed to himself.

It was alright for him, since he had a different growth system and also knew about the existence of the World Tree. Thus, while shocked, he felt nothing else.

But Kasuyi was different. It had taken him countless years to finally become a hegemon that had reached the pinnacle of the universe, but he suddenly discovered that there were many more people outside his world that were as strong as him. It was no wonder that his mentality would be shaken up.

Han Xiao thought about it before consoling him. "Old Ka, don't be depressed. We don't even know how long this secondary dimension has existed. This number of Beyond Grade As has been accumulated over so many years. There's nothing to envy. If you want to be jealous, why not be jealous of me? It only took me a few decades to reach this point, surpassing your accumulation of thousands of years. How hateful is that?"

Are you really trying to console me?

The words 'f*ck you' come to mind, but I'm not sure if I should reply with that.

Seeing his constipated expression, Han Xiao was about to continue comforting him when he received a message alarm.

Beep beep…

"You've received a new message."

"Eh, who could it be at this time?" Han Xiao spoke subconsciously before he reacted.

That's right, no one has my contact details here. How were they able to find me!"

Han Xiao's expression changed, and he opened the quantum network, finding an email within. The sender was shown as a bunch of garbled code. The sender had manipulated his address to cover up all traces.

Frowning, he opened the mail and found out that it contained a set of complicated blueprints as well as a short message.

"Learn this technology as fast as possible, or else there'll be no escape for you. If you can avoid the pursuit of the troops, then go to a place and wait. I'll contact you again then. The coordinates are…"

"Who is this guy?"

Han Xiao wanted to communicate with the other party, but without a path, he had no method to send a reply.

He could only browse through the blueprint sent by the mysterious person. It recorded a kind of weird instrument, which seemed to have some sort of special hiding function. He did not know what sort of detection device this was guarding against.

"Things have become more interesting…" Han Xiao's eyes flashed.

From the strange 'Supreme Guardian' outside the secondary dimension to the unexpectedly powerful Celestial Star Alliance and now this mysterious man contacting him, things were getting more confusing, and he seemed to be getting involved in some unknown storm.

He decided to stay and explore, not just to aid Kasuyi but also to collect more technology and discover the truth behind this space. Otherwise, not just Han Xiao, the entire explored universe would also remain uneasy.

However, this trip to the secondary dimension was always out of his control. He was lacking in intelligence, and he was only receiving poor information, only able to see the surface level.

Ding!

At this time, a notification popped up on the interface.

You have triggered an S-ranked hidden mission: A Relay Across Iterations!

This mission is part of a Chain Mission. This is currently the first of many parts.

Requirements: Escape from the hunting team and succeed in meeting the mysterious person who sent this message.

Failure Condition: The mysterious person dies.

Reward: 100,000,000,000 experience, unlocking of the next mission.

Warning! This mission may result in unpredictable effects, please choose carefully!

Chapter 1196: The Pursuing Soldiers

"This mission…"

Han Xiao was shocked. Not only was it an S-rank hidden mission, it was even a chain mission. The experience reward in just the first mission already matched with what Old Man Manison gave, so the overall difficulty might really be through the sky.

In the absence of any intelligence, the mission guidance was one of the few reliable sources of information, especially since the name of the mission was quite intriguing.

No matter what, this mysterious person took the initiative to contact me. He seems to have some special information in his hand. That will require us to meet. As for the hunter team in the mission introduction…

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

While he was searching online previously, he had discovered a wanted order issued by the Celestial Star Alliance Superpower Security Department, offering a reward for the two wanted people. Their bounty was worth 300 million units of their common currency, its name different from the term 'Ena' used in their main universe.

Since his whereabouts were a secret and he had yet to encounter any alarms or detection device scanning, it was logically difficult for them to discover their location. However, the mission reminder as well as the content of the mysterious person's message seemed to imply that the pursuing team would definitely locate him.

Upon thinking of the weird concealment device left by the mysterious person, Han Xiao guessed that the pursuers might have a precise remote location detecting method, including but not limited to the possibility of prediction, technological means, or even Universal Treasures…

The mysterious person sent me a blueprint but did not explain in detail what sort of methods the soldiers would use. This feels more like a test…

Han Xiao stroked his chin and fell into thought.

This technology had to be studied, but Han Xiao did not intend to put it to use immediately. He wanted to test whether they could be found by the pursuers first. If that was confirmed, then he would utilize the device again in order to verify whether the device really had the effect of concealing its target. As a Mechanic, he believed more in the results of experimentation rather than what people told him.

On the other hand, Han Xiao wished to contact their pursuers, obtaining information from them… Of course, while he was confident in his own strength, he would still arrange some insurance to stabilize any rough waves that might appear.

Currently, both of them were illegal immigrants, and they did not even possess an account in the Intergalactic Bank, let alone the universal currency. They suddenly fell from being the wealthiest in the universe to abject poverty. Han Xiao could only resort to collecting the resources himself, and for the time being, he could not scrape up enough materials to make a new King mechanical suit. Thus, he could only resort to using the King that he had brought with him. He had already placed some of the corresponding Thrones on different coordinates in the universe, acting as fixed-point transporters, whilst some of his King mechanical suits still had the Thrones with them, ready to be positioned at any time.

Having been in the universe for so many years, and with the example given by Manison, Han Xiao was now well versed in the saying 'a sly rabbit has three burrows'. Days ago, a few of his mechanical troops had scattered the different Thrones around this universe at suitable locations, leaving him with a way out.

The biggest problem currently was not personal safety but his mechanical army. Because his secondary dimensional army box was frozen, he could only transport his troops through the normal method. His portability was severely affected, so if he chose to teleport away, his mechanical army would still be left in the area, and he would be unable to recover them.

Based on reasoning, since there was no secondary dimension that existed in this universe, all mechanics should be the same. However, he found through the internet that because of the lack of secondary dimensions, the five Super systems seemed to have some subtleties in their Class skills.

For example, the Beyond Grade A Mechanics still had the ability to summon mechanical armies on a large scale. However, because they had not crossed paths yet, Han Xiao could not see their combat information and thus did not understand the principle.

"Just the technology alone makes it worth the trip." Han Xiao was ecstatic.

In his opinion, this place was akin to a huge material library, stocked with endless new technology and different applications and development paths for one's Class related skills. These were all extremely valuable resources.

The Manison of his previous life must have learned quite a bit when he came over, further increasing his own power.

And now, this rare learning opportunity had been taken away by himself.

"Rest in peace, Old Man. I'll study hard on your behalf."

Han Xiao had a solemn expression.

The destroyed mentality of Kasuyi had finally recovered from Han Xiao's 'comforting blow'. Seeing this, Han Xiao explained the situation and his plan.

Kasuyi was surprised, and after hearing everything, he said, "You mean… we're now waiting for our pursuers to come knocking before we negotiate? If not, we'll fight?"

"That's right. This is in order for us to obtain more information. Don't be scared by the number of Beyond Grade As here. I've checked the cases from the Superpower Security Department over the years, and the majority of them consist of teams formed by three to five Beyond Grade As. There are dozens to hundreds of people there, but they are responsible for a large area, and thus, manpower is limited. Furthermore, I've also arranged a path of retreat in case things go awry," Han Xiao said.

Old Ka was his only companion here, and it could be said that they could only truly depend on each other. While the other party did not have his limitless MP any longer, he was still a pinnacle Beyond Grade A and was a great source of combat power.

"… Alright, then don't bother me during this period of time. I'll prepare an ace in the hole and strive to heavily injure a pinnacle Beyond Grade A," Kasuyi solemnly said.

Han Xiao was startled. He sized him up before curiously asking, "I really didn't expect that, but you have such ability?"

Kasuyi immediately rolled his eyes.

Who are you looking down on? At our level, who doesn't have a trump card or two in their hands? When I was roaming the universe, your grandfather had probably yet to be born!

…

In the pitch-black universe, a wormhole suddenly opened, and three spaceships appeared as they exited the hyperdrive. All three were special spaceships that belonged to the Superpower Security Department, led by three 'Supreme' level directors to capture the offenders.

"The Positioning Star Map at the headquarters shows that the two targets have been stationed on the target planet and have not left in the past few days."

"We are still unaware of the intentions of these two people. Do not lower your vigilance."

Milton stood in front of the porthole, listening to the communication channel. His face had nary a smile on it, and his entire person exuded a serious vibe.

He was the director of the Fifth Team from the Superpower Security Department and the temporary captain of this special pursuit team.

Every established division would consist of one Supreme level Director, four deputy directors of the Saint level, and a large number of middle tier officers. Milton had brought two deputy directors with him this time, and the other two directors used the same configuration. Thus, there were nine people at the Beyond Grade A level.

Because of the lack of the strength data for the target, in order to make it a quick fight, the Superpower Security Department equipped the nine of them with the special combat suit, which included a mechanical suit, with melee, long-range, and imprisonment equipment of Gold Grade. With such special equipment, the staff from the Superpower Security Department would have an advantage among people of the same level.

Their opponents were only two Supreme level experts, but they had mobilized nine people on their side, alongside equipment. Milton felt that this mission should be a piece of cake.

He stared at the arrest warrants of Han Xiao and Kasuyi, muttering to himself.

"What year is this? To think that there are still people who dare to openly violate the universe ban of the Celestial Star Alliance, trying to whatever they want with their strength. Do you think it's like the old era? Such good times are long gone…"

…

Time passed quickly, and another three days passed in the blink of an eye.

Han Xiao had been constantly studying the blueprint provided by the mysterious person in seclusion. It was not difficult to make, but the principle behind it was quite incomprehensible. In some areas, he could not understand it at all, and he did not know what sort of effect the combination would produce.

After a few days of research, there was still no progress. Han Xiao felt that he might lack the key Research Theory or Knowledge, so he simply stopped his research, building the device according to the blueprint given. The process went smoothly, and his failure to understand theory did not hinder him from turning the blueprint into machinery error free.

Ten palm-sized pieces of green and gold metal lay quietly on the workbench. They appeared smooth, but when Han Xiao swiped them with his fingers, he could feel the dense lines engraved on them, filled with countless nano-level energy circuits.

Han Xiao picked up a piece of the alloy, playing with it carefully. Traces of electrical arcs jumped now and then as he extended his senses deep into the metal, feeling the structure within.

"The manual states that so long as the concealment function is activated, objects within its range would be freed from tracking. The more energy inputted, the greater the range…"

Han Xiao was a little skeptical as he had mastered a variety of concealment devices but was unable to see through the principles behind this blueprint.

Even the interface did not give any detailed introduction but rather simply naming it as a 'Special Cloaking Device'. It said that this would take effect under certain conditions but did not state what those conditions were.

Just as he wished to further study it, his expression changed as he sensed an unexpected situation.

The space exploration buoys he arranged around the planet were destroyed.

"They've really found us…"

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed, and he put away the ten Cloaking Devices. He left his base with his mechanical troops, heading to the surface.

Whoosh!

Before long, three spaceships appeared in outer space. Nine figures descended from the sky and landed on the wasteland not far in front of Han Xiao in a fan-shaped encirclement, not bothering to conceal their energy fluctuations.

Seeing this, Han Xiao revealed a knowing expression.

Nine Beyond Grade As, with three of them being pinnacle Beyond Grade As…

The strength of this team was not small. Their overall combat power was higher than the level shown during the attack on Hila. Furthermore, this group of people would not be like the original Kasuyi, where they pulled their punches.

He also discovered that their equipment was extraordinary.

Both sides confronted each other from afar, sizing each other up without moving.

Milton surveyed the area before casually asking, "Where's your accomplice?"

"Since you can come knocking, how could you not know where he is?" Han Xiao crossed his arms.

Over the past few days, he had purposely devoted a little time to learn the interstellar lingua franca online, so communication was no longer a problem for him.

Milton looked at him from top to toe before nodding and speaking in a business-like tone.

"I advise you not to have any thoughts of resistance. Obediently put on the Source restraints and come with us. Confess your origins, abilities, and reasons for violating the prohibition before undergoing a public review and going to jail for five to ten years. After completing that, you will regain your freedom. The current punishment is considered light; you don't need to aggravate your crimes."

Han Xiao did not agree nor refuse, returning with another question. "May I know your identities?"

"You don't recognize us?" Milton frowned. "I am the Director of the Fifth Division under the Superpower Security Department, Milton. These are my assistants…"

He briefly introduced everyone before asking about Han Xiao's identity.

"You can call me Black Star, and for my comrade, you can just call him Kakasu…"

"Call me Void Overlord!"

Kasuyi suddenly appeared before Han Xiao, correcting his words in a dissatisfied tone.

"Any name is fine." Milton did not care, only taking out two sets of mechanical devices similar to collars and throwing them in front as he said, "Hurry up, put on the Source imprisonment devices and go back to settle this business."

Han Xiao pondered for a while before he spoke.

"I believe there's a better choice. My friend and I have been in retreat all this while, and we're unaware of the so-called ban. We are not deliberately causing trouble. Maybe there's room for discussion. For example, we're willing to join your Superpower Security Department. Is it possible for you to inform your superiors…"

From his point of view, Kasuyi and him did not commit any major incidents. With their strength, they should be able to enjoy this treatment.

However, Milton did not buy it at all. He bellowed, "I'm ordering you, not negotiating! If you have any words, then wait till we return! And no matter what you say, don't think you can escape the punishment just like that. Even if you're a Supreme expert, so long as your stain is not removed, we will not accept you!"

Hearing this, Han Xiao's brows twitched.

He had spoken not because he was trying to prevaricate; rather, he did not intend to be limited by the mission. While cooperating with the Celestial Star Alliance might not be the best option, Kasuyi's mission was simply looking for a needle in a haystack. If he could obtain help from the Celestial Star Alliance, then it would definitely make things easier, and there would be more opportunities to access their secrets.

There were two possible ways to cooperate. One would be to expose his identity as an outsider from another world, while the other was to pretend to be a local… Obviously, Han Xiao could not choose the former. Until things became clear, he would never reveal the existence of the three Universal Civilizations, otherwise it would be bad if the opponent began to covet his universe. That was no different from being a traitor.

Thus, Han Xiao could only choose to pretend to be a local in order to join the Superpower Security Department. He originally felt that with his and Kasuyi's strength, the other party had no reason not to accept it and would wipe their slates clean. However, the other party did not seem to show them any face at all.

This should not be the case here. With over ten thousand Beyond Grade As, we're a force to be reckoned with. However, for the advanced civilization to not have any thoughts of stabilizing us with better privileges and treatment, instead treating us all fairly, aren't they afraid that these people would revolt?

It was impossible for Han Xiao to put on the source restraint and go to the headquarters of the Superpower Security Department. This was tantamount to handing over his own fate to the other party. He frowned before asking once more, "Is there no room for discussion?"

Milton pointed to the two sets of Source restraints on the ground. His meaning could not have been clearer.

Boom!

At this moment, extremely condensed and violent Psychic power suddenly shot out from the side. It was Kasuyi's trump card that he had been preparing for the last few days!

Boom!

Milton suffered a heavy blow, his eyeballs bursting and his nose spurting blood as he was sent flying out like a comet.

Turning his head, Han Xiao only saw Kasuyi revolving his Psychic power, shooting forward while snapping at him, "What the f*ck are you still waiting for? Just take action!"

Chapter 1197: Cosmic Treasure Loses Effectiveness

The Void Racial Talents were an important part of Kasuyi's strength, and now that most of these talents were frozen, his combat power was far from the peak, and his damage had declined, so he gave it his all in that one strike.

The killing move that Kasuyi had been brewing for the last few days was an explosive skill, and the mechanism was a little similar to [Charge—Endless Potential]. During the accumulation period, Kasuyi could not utilize any of his Psychic power, instead compressing it in his brain area while continuously replenishing the energy gone into compression through his cells. He would then use his Psychic power to dam up the compressed area before releasing the floor when he faced an enemy. It was akin to constipating for a few days before releasing everything in one go, and it boasted a high attack coefficient bonus.

This single blow not only brought high damage but also various forms of negative statuses, which could induce a state of [Soul Weakness] in the opponent, reducing their attributes by a percentage. Depending on the target's strength, it would last for several hours to several years.

Because Milton was ambushed and hit hard, his aura weakened in an instant, and could only show a part of his strength. Kasuyi came prepared, and under his calculation, he weakened the opponent's overall combat power.

As this violent Kasuyi hit the opponent's leader, the other eight were furious, immediately counterattacking. Various forms of Beyond Grade A attacks smashed toward Kasuyi's head and face, including Pugilist flames, Magic, Energy Cannons, and Esper Abilities.

Seeing this, Han Xiao sighed, and his body flashed as he stood in front of Kasuyi.

When the duo was first sighted, the natives had already come to the conclusion that Han Xiao was basically there as a meat shield.

How could Kasuyi's delicate body be able to withstand the ravages of eight strong men? He still had to rely on Han Xiao's unplowed field to be the tank.

All sorts of weird thoughts flashed by, and in the next instant, the tyrannical attacks of the eight fell on him.

Boom!

The various energies exploded, instantly swelling up into a giant ball of light. The earth collapsed, and matter was annihilated and evaporated. The entire planet now resembled a fruit that had been bitten.

A huge pit appeared in the field, extremely deep and wide, and the underground base they had created naturally collapsed.

However, Han Xiao had already relocated his troops when he was spouting his excuses, so what was destroyed at this time was only a shell.

As the smoke and dust quickly settled, Han Xiao was seen hovering in the same place. He patted the dust on his body casually. "This strength won't do. You've all got to practice more."

The eight who were preparing to pursue their advantage stood stunned with incredulous expressions.

They had witnessed their opponent taking the firepower of eight people and felt that even if they were not dead, they would still probably be seriously injured. At the very least, they would be injured and embarrassed. However, they never expected this guy called Black Star to be able to casually take on such a round and still appear unscathed!

How was this possible? The information showed that this guy was a Mechanic!

This could not be blamed on them. The explored universe was aware of Han Xiao's ability, but this was the first time they had encountered the 'Indestructible Body'.

Even while they were shocked silly, Kasuyi's actions did not stop in the slightest. After using Black Star as a shield to block out the firepower, Kasuyi's Psychic power was like wave after wave of floods, exerting an AOE effect as it smashed into the eight of them. It infiltrated their mental realms, outputting tons of damage and blasting out three of the slightly weaker Saint experts.

He was long accustomed to Black Star's fleshiness and did not take it to heart. He naturally would focus all his attention on this window of opportunity, immediately reversing the attack onto his enemies.

At this moment, Han Xiao also controlled his mechanical soldiers through Mechanical Force. The overwhelming number of soldiers wandered around the horizon like a swarm of locusts continuously providing covering firepower. The huge lethality continuously bound the enemies' hands and feet, putting them in a dangerous spot.

Furthermore, there was even a milestone that Han Xiao did not expect would come in handy at this time…

Lothaire's [Civilization Leader Slayer]!

The defenses and various resistance of all enemies would be reduced by three to seven percent, making them weaker.

"I never expected that I would become a wanted criminal. This ability will come in handy now though…" Han Xiao felt helpless.

While the process of fighting between both sides seemed to be quite long, with the speed of a Beyond Grade A, from negotiation to war was merely the span of a few seconds.

A fierce battle broke out in an instant. While the nine led by Milton had the advantage in numbers and overall combat power, they lost the initiative from the beginning and failed to obtain any benefits in the hands of Han Xiao and Kasuyi. However, they still had their Gold Grade equipment, so the two sides were quite evened out, unable to distinguish a winning party early.

"I feel that the strength of these people seems to be a little weaker…"

Han Xiao multitasked, gazing at the combat information shown in his interface.

The three Supreme powerhouses were supposed to be equivalent to the pinnacle Beyond Grade A in their universe, but it did not mean that these three had the same number of God's Trait Transformation layers. In fact, out of all of them, only Milton had activated the God's Trait Transformation route.

Earlier on, when Han Xiao had advanced to level 300, he had already entered the pinnacle Beyond Grade A level. When his Energy Rank exceeded the 78,000 threshold, achieving an Energy Level of twenty-one, he had activated the God's Trait Transformation route. There was a barrier to entry, so not all pinnacle Beyond Grade A would be able to activate this God's Trait Transformation.

While Han Xiao did not know what Kasuyi's Energy Rank was, he conservatively estimated it to be above 90,000, with his God's Trait Transformation at least being at the tenth layer. Milton, the strongest party in the enemy team, probably only had an Energy Rank of close to 80,000. Thus, even with their extra Beyond Grade As, the combat power advantage they held was not as high as imagined.

As for the other six Saint class powerhouses, Han Xiao only saw two people who were Grade S+ with Energy Rank above 52,000, while the rest were little kids with Energy Ranks below 50,000.

"The quantity is quite ridiculous, but as for the quality…" Han Xiao shook his head.

Thinking about it, it made sense. He and Kasuyi were people who were standing at the peak of the strongest in the explored universe, among even those pinnacle Beyond Grade As. There was no need to belittle themselves.

Of course, the Celestial Star Alliance had nearly ten thousand Beyond Grade As, and there would naturally be people who were comparable to them. However, whether such people would be willing to work in the Superpower Security Department was questionable, and even if they were, they would not easily be deployed. After all, the two of them did not show much strength previously, so the other party imagined that sending out nine Beyond Grade As would be overkill.

Hu!

One of the Saint Pugilists suddenly rushed in, coming right in front of Han Xiao before lifting up a Gold Grade blood-red halberd and piercing it toward his eyes.

Han Xiao was calm, slightly tilting his head to avoid it, and the light reflecting off the blade illuminated his eyes, filling him with nostalgia.

It had been so many years since someone tried to smash his face. He had almost forgotten what it felt like…

He even had the chance to spare a glance toward his opponent. The next moment, he brought up his arm so quickly it left an afterimage, counterattacking the Pugilist. His Strength and Dexterity made this attack even surpass the speed of the Pugilist.

Boom!

This powerful fist slammed into his opponent's head, and the person felt as though a symphony had gone off in his mind. He shot off as though he was a baseball that had been hit hard by the batter, flying out of Han Xiao's sight in the blink of an eye.

Seeing this, Han Xiao lightly nodded.

"It seems like even in this place, the life of a Pugilist is still pretty difficult…"

They had only exchanged blows for a short period of time, but Han Xiao had already concluded that this pursuer team could not pose a substantive threat. Thus, he leisurely observed the opponent to collect intelligence.

The opponent's team consisted of two Espers, three Pugilists, two Mages, a Mechanic, and a Psychic. This team configuration was quite complete, with all five Systems present.

The bulk of Han Xiao's attention was focused on the only Mechanic of his opponent, a Supreme expert.

Because there was no secondary dimension present, the Class abilities and skills of the five major Superpower systems changed accordingly. While there were some alternative abilities as a result, their strength in general was not as strong as that of the main universe, such as the utilization of certain special energies only found within the secondary dimensions.

Because there were no secondary dimensional army boxes, Han Xiao was wondering what sort of method the Mechanics would use to summon their machinery on a large scale.

After careful observation, and with the information given by the combat information, he quickly came to a conclusion.

Their compression technology has undergone some innovation, giving out some special Mechanical Force Vigor Resonance. After which, an ability similar to Machinery Apostilization is carried out, giving the Mechanical Force new characteristics to alter a portion of one's cells and transform it into an empty space akin to the army boxes. The Mechanical Force blessing allows the compressed orbs to be further compressed and stored in the body, providing an effect similar to that of the secondary dimensional army box… However, this ability has a limitation, which is the same drawback as the Machinery Apostilization. The more the machinery stored, the higher one's load, which will reduce the upper limit of one's life span and Energy…

This was a feasible method. The idea could not be said to be novel, but there were also merits. The main problem was that the Mechanical Force conversion skills were complicated, most likely automatically obtained through Promotion or Class Advancement. Due to the difference between the systems of their universes, the abilities generated during Class Advancement would be different. This could be described as a situation where they existed as different branches of the same system.

However, the secondary dimensional army boxes and Dimension Factories were better for usage, as there was no need to bear any load as well as a lack of limit on the troops stored, which made it far superior. However, this method of storing troops in one's body also had an advantage, which was not being affected by any sort of spatial interference devices.

Understanding the opponent's method did not mean that Han Xiao had cracked the principles; he had yet to be able to learn this technique.

Both sides fought fiercely, not caring about the aftermath. The planet was soon crushing into a stream of dust within the universe, and their battlefield moved toward outer space.

Just as Han Xiao was busy observing the rest, Kasuyi's voice rang out in his mind.

"Black Star, why are you not activating your Mechanical Deity? Quickly, we need to get rid of one of two more!"

"What are you anxious about? Aren't we maintaining the stalemate well. Let me gather more intelligence first."

"I'm out of energy," Kasuyi replied.

Are you kidding me‽

This thought subconsciously floated past Han Xiao's mind.

But he quickly reacted… This time, Kasuyi might really be out of MP.

Of course, because this battle only lasted for a short time, it was an exaggeration to be out of MP. But from a long-term view, Kasuyi had limited skills to allow him to recover his MP, and his current MP reserves would not allow him to fight against nine opponents. If they fought a war of attrition, they would fall into a disadvantage soon, so he did not want Han Xiao to continue wasting time. He decided to get some results whilst he was still able to fight, shaving off the enemy's strength.

"Fine, since you've asked…"

Han Xiao did not think much. Just as he was about to activate his Mechanical Deity…

Everything changed.

The nine of them suddenly stopped attacking, retreating quickly with complex and exquisite blue magic patterns illuminating on their mechanical suits.

Whoosh!

The next instant, the figures of the nine disappeared without a trace.

"Hmm?"

Han Xiao's movements stalled. He swept the surroundings with his senses, but he did not find a trace of their targets.

With the disappearance of their opponents, Kasuyi also paused and scanned the area with his Psychic powers, but his search yielded no results.

The nine experts that came to hunt them down suddenly seemed to have activated some teleportation magic runes to run away.

Both of them shared a glance in confusion.

What‽

"They couldn't have… run away, right?"

The Great Mechanic Han was dumbfounded.

Wait, I haven't even tried!

The opponents had no casualties, basically retaining their complete combat strength. It was just a slight disadvantage, so how could they run away so decisively?

Could it be that the Beyond Grade As there were the people only heard of in stories, that would only fight if they were guaranteed victory?

Kasuyi also left his mouth agape, totally speechless.

This group of pursuers had come in an aggressive manner, letting them think that they would stop at nothing to achieve their goals. They did not expect them to escape so skillfully. They did not even leave any final words.

"Black Star, do we chase them?"

"… I'm a Mechanic, not a Mage. Locating people isn't one of my strengths. Besides, theirs is a strategic retreat; it's too arrogant of us to chase after them."

"So, what do we do now?"

"Forget it. Since they've run away, I'll test out this Cloaking Device."

Han Xiao shook his head in resignation, taking out the alloy pieces. He carefully inspected the device as he inputted his energy, but he did not feel any change through his senses. So, he just kept them on himself in this activated state.

He had collected all the intelligence he needed and also confirmed that any cooperation between himself and the Superpower Security Department was impossible. Thus, he could only choose the option of the mysterious man.

The two of them quickly tidied up the battlefield and did not dally, leaving the scene quickly. They headed for the location given by the mysterious man.

…

Somewhere far from the battlefield, nine rays of light flashed as Milton and his party teleported over.

With a sigh of relief, Milton endured the splitting pain in his head and spoke in a deep tone through the team communication channel.

"There's a slight error in the judgement made by the department. The targets' combat strength is frightening, likely at the forefront even among Supreme experts. This is especially so for the person called Black Star, who commands an unbelievable recovery speed and resilience. Our attacks could hardly threaten his life. With just the nine of us alone, the success rate of arrest is too low. Requesting the headquarters for reinforcements."

The others nodded. "Understood."

While they could still continue to fight, they felt it unnecessary.

After a few clashes, they had already sensed that their manpower alone would not be able to allow them to capture the target. Thus, they retreated decisively and prepared to call for reinforcements.

The Superpower Security Department's modus operandi did not advocate aggressiveness. Since they were evenly matched, it would be settled if they got more people. Clashing head on was not only a waste of time but also carried the danger of sacrificing someone.

So what if the enemy is powerful? We have so many people. We can simply overwhelm you!

Nine people isn't enough? Then double it! Still not enough? Double that! I do not believe you can last forever!

Since they were a law enforcement department, there was no need to speak about morality with wanted criminals!

The staff of the Superpower Security Department had always operated in this manner, and the reason behind this was because of the existence of the Positioning Star Map.

No matter where the target went, the Positioning Star Map would be able to relocate them. Thus, there was no fear of them running away.

However, at this moment, an emergency communication was sent by the headquarters before they could contact the other party.

Milton received the communication only to see the face of their department leader appear, solemn with a trace of irritation.

"What have you two done to the fugitives‽" the leader bellowed.

Milton did not know how the leader got angry and could only reply honestly.

"We fought with them, but our team agreed that they were too strong. Thus, we made a strategic retreat and decided to call for reinforcements… What happened?"

"I want to know that too!" The leader's expression was ashen. "Just a moment ago, their coordinates disappeared from the Positioning Star Map!"

Milton's eyes widened, his expression shocked.

The moment we retreated, their coordinates vanished?

Impossible!

What did those two do!

His confidence was instantly shattered.

Chapter 1198: Secret News (1)

Planet Jardinger was a rather prosperous interstellar port that was in the neutral faction, with a complex web of organizations and people that would pass through it every day.

On the bustling street, two tall men were strolling as they shopped. They occasionally walked into the shops on the side of the road, looking left and right.

These two were precisely Han Xiao and Kasuyi.

It had been more than half a month since the last time they fought with Milton's team. Han Xiao had led Kasuyi to Planet Jardinger, following the coordinates left by the mysterious man. They had waited here for several days, but there was no movement.

"It's already been so many days. Why is the mysterious person you mentioned not responding yet? Oh, I want this, thanks."

Standing in front of a self-service vending machine within a food store, Kasuyi pointed at the green can of an alcoholic beverage.

"They should be observing if we managed to get rid of our pursuers."

Han Xiao shrugged and activated his Virtual Intrusion, instantly hacking into the entire store. The next second, two cans of drinks popped out of the vending machine.

Because they were illegal immigrants, without even a bank account to their name, they were naturally penniless. He could only utilize Virtual Intrusion to bypass payments like these, just like taking out cannons to kill mosquitoes. With his current level, there was no way he would leave any traces.

"Sigh, I haven't been so poverty-stricken in such a long time. To think I'm reduced to drinking such inferior wine…" Kasuyi pulled off the tab, sipping the pale green wine in a graceful manner.

"We can survive for a decade without eating. I think you're just greedy."

Han Xiao rolled his eyes, emptying the can in one mouthful before squeezing the can into a small ball and throwing it into the garbage bin beside them.

Neither of them had anything to do, and thus, they wandered about the streets, trying to learn about the customs.

At first, the two of them were still on guard, but their enemies never came to look for them, proving that the Cloaking Device given by the mysterious person was useful.

While they were chatting, a piece of news suddenly appeared on the virtual screen within the store, attracting their attention.

"Urgent News: The Celestial Star Alliance Superpower Security Department has issued two new arrest warrants. The contents are as follows…

"Bounty Target - Black Star, Supreme level Mechanic, reward of 1.6 billion Star Alliance Coins.

"Bounty Target - Kasuyi, Supreme level Psychic, reward of 1.6 billion Star Alliance Coins.

"These two wanted criminals have committed many crimes and are extremely dangerous. They have succeeded in repelling the pursuit team sent by the department. If you find their whereabouts, please report it immediately. The contact information is…"

Seeing this news, Han Xiao could not help but laugh. "Oh, the bounty has gone up again. It seems like they really cannot find us."

Kasuyi, however, had a face full of black lines.

Every time he saw the name on his bounty, he would flare up uncontrollably.

No matter how he looked at it, it was the imposing nickname of 'Void Overlord' that would suit his status as a top powerhouse! Why did those idiots ignore his claim and take Black Star's words so seriously‽

"Oh right, speaking of wanted criminals, I surfed on the internet yesterday…" Han Xiao stroked his chin in interest. "Our added bounties currently put us in second place of all the fugitives within this universe."

"We're number two just like that? We didn't even do anything heinous." Kasuyi frowned. "Plus, our bounties should not be considered high as well. There aren't any more ferocious criminals than us?"

"It seems like there really isn't anybody. The Celestial Star Alliance has experienced many years without chaos. Not only is their governance stable, most of the Beyond Grade As here are like obedient babies. We're anomalies." Han Xiao waved his hand.

"Then, who's at the top of the bounty list?"

"It's an organization named [Eye of Insight], with a six-billion-dollar bounty. However, I couldn't find what sort of criminal record they had online." Han Xiao shook his head.

The two of them walked out of the shop as they chatted. Before long, they came across a store that was full of liveliness and clamoring, causing them to head over in curiosity.

The interior was shaped a little like a board game cafeteria, but everyone was playing the same game, a card game known as 'Myriad Souls Card'.

It seemed like an event was currently ongoing, with four people each seated at a game table, playing against each other while the spectators crowded around them. In the middle of the room was an exhibition cabinet with three exquisitely-made cards floating. The host constantly added to the atmosphere, emphasizing that the winner of the game could walk away with these three limited-edition cards.

As both of them leaned over a table to take a look, their expressions turned weird.

"Do you feel that this is rather familiar?" Kasuyi whispered.

"You don't say…" Han Xiao said this as his mouth twitched.

How could it not be? The playing style of this card game was exactly the same as the Wayne Cards in their universe. It was just that the characters were different.

Why would there be similar card games here? Could it be the will of the universe, ensuring that card players would always be present in the world?

At this moment, the senses of the two picked up something. Turning their heads at the same time, they discovered a person staring at them from among the crowd, his gaze indeterminate.

Seeing them look at him, the man put his hand into his pocket, slowly taking out a piece of green metal to shake it before leaving.

"That was the device given by the mysterious person…"

Han Xiao recognized it immediately before exchanging a glance with Kasuyi. They stepped up to follow.

The person walked and stopped along the way, glancing back as though leading the way. They walked along the streets, soon coming into a slightly older docking terminal.

The guide opened a hanger, which revealed a plain, general-purpose spaceship. He then opened the hatch, turning back to look at the two as though inviting them up.

Seeing this, Han Xiao and Kasuyi scanned the spaceship with their senses. Finding no abnormalities, they stepped onto the gangway, entering the spaceship.

Very quickly, the hull vibrated slightly before moving off. The view of Planet Jardinger from the porthole slowly shrank.

Han Xiao finally retracted his gaze, turning back to look at the silent guide before taking out a similar piece of green-gold alloy as he asked, "Can you explain who you are exactly? Why did you bring us on board?"

Hearing this, the guide straightened his clothes before slowly speaking.

"Let me introduce myself. I'm a senior officer under the Eye of Insight, Lucidias. It was my leader that asked me to meet up with you."

Eye of Insight… Isn't that the wanted organization with the highest bounty?

Kasuyi glanced at Han Xiao meaningfully.

Han Xiao's eyes flashed, and he replied, "In that case, it means that your leader was the one who sent me the anonymous messages, right?"

"My job is only to escort the two of you. I was told that as long as I showed the Heaven Concealing Apparatus, you would follow me. As for the rest, I'm also unaware." Lucidias shook his head.

"Heaven Concealing Apparatus?" Han Xiao raised the alloy piece on his hand. "You mean this?"

"That's right. It is the core technology of our Eye of Insight." Lucidias nodded.

"What exactly does your Eye of Insight do?" Han Xiao was curious.

"Apologies, but without express permission from our leader, I cannot disclose too much information. If you have any questions, please direct them to our leader." Lucidias refused to answer, diverting it to his boss.

Seeing that he could not dig out more intelligence, Han Xiao also stopped asking, beginning to come out with his own hypothesis.

During this period of time, he was also guessing the identity of this mysterious person. In the original message sent, it was revealed by the mysterious person vaguely that he was aware of their identities as outsiders.

In view of the fact that this place was isolated from the outside universe, Han Xiao felt that the mysterious man might have been someone who had accidentally trespassed into this secondary dimension as well. As for why he was looking for them, it could be because he was trapped here and thus needed more helpers.

Since the Celestial Star Alliance was still unaware of the existence of the outside universe, then this mysterious person probably did not reveal anything about the main universe, instead lurking around, creating this organization in secret.

The more Han Xiao thought about it, the higher he felt the likelihood of that. In his theory, the only suspicious point was the Eye of Insight as there was little information about them on the web. But looking back, it seemed like the Eye of Insight had existed for a long time and did not seem to be created by an intruder.

Since the mission prompt has connected me to this mysterious person, the other party will probably be a friend, not an enemy. It is useless for me to overthink right now. It will be more convenient to ask things directly later.

…

The spaceship travelled for over ten days before reaching the destination. They arrived at a huge mothership resembling an asteroid, which maintained its stealth as it wandered through outer space.

Swoosh!

As the hatch opened, the two followed Lucidias to step into the mothership.

They passed through various areas, seeing a large number of staff and mechanical guards. The entire mothership was heavily guarded.

The group passed through authorization certifications one after another, going deeper into the core area of the mothership before finally arriving at a huge metal door.

"The leader is waiting inside. He wishes to see the two of you only, so I won't be entering."

Lucidias suddenly stopped walking.

Kasuyi and Han Xiao exchanged looks before stepping forward. The metal door automatically swung open, allowing them to enter.

Once they entered, the door closed behind them.

Han Xiao sized up the layout of the room. Pipes protruded from the ground and the walls, connecting to a figure in the center of the room.

This figure was tall, but his shape scrawny and shriveled, with tubes inserted all around him. He had two pairs of green eyes, one pair larger than the other. There was also a scar running through his face, blinding the eyes on his left.

Upon seeing the two, the person slowly spoke. His voice was deep and hoarse.

"We finally meet… outsiders!"

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed.

He indeed knew that we came from the outside universe.

He had anticipated this and thus did not feel surprised. Kasuyi was the same.

"Since you have invited us here, can you explain the situation? Who are you, why do you know about the existence of the outside universe, and what's your reason for contacting us?"

During this period of time, Han Xiao had suppressed too many questions. Now that he had met someone who looked like they knew something, he spewed out all his thoughts.

The mysterious man listened quietly but did not answer them directly. He instead softly said, "I know that you guys have a lot of questions, but before that, I hope you can answer some of mine… What era is it outside now? Has the exploration era war ended?"

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

To actually ask about the war during the exploration era, could this person trapped here be a Primordial One?

As this thought flashed past, Han Xiao briefly described the ending of the exploration era war and issued his own question.

"Are you a Primordial One?"

"No, I'm not." The person laughed. "I'm not what you call Primordial Ones, but I've met them."

"Then who are you?"

"I understand your confusion. You believe that I came in like you… but you've guessed wrongly. I belong here."

The mysterious man's tone was calm.

At this moment, many more possibilities appeared in Han Xiao's mind.

If what the mysterious man said was true, and his source of information came from the Primordial Ones who had intruded here, then could his objective be to leave this world? Furthermore, where were the Primordial Ones that this person had once met? Why was there no record of them on the internet? Could it be that they were also taken in by the Celestial Star Alliance?

At this moment, the mysterious man once again spoke, his tone solemn.

"I know what you are most interested in right now. That's exactly why I invited you… I require helpers, to eradicate this world and set me free. This… is also the only method through which you can leave!"